Chapter 2

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Don't want to get too repetitive but a big thanks to the usual crowd, IP especially helped me get this chapter smoother. Also, my warnings about updates were merely to inform you that I have no intentions of "forcing" myself to write just to meet a self-imposed deadline (which is how I wrote Browncoat). This story will come as my time and muse permit. Just for those unclear thinking it was anywhere near its conclusion, I'm guessing this fic will be well over twenty, maybe over thirty chapters long. We've only scratched the surface of this one.

The large black dog took a big sniff of the young man in front of him.

Harry just smiled as the dog glanced up at him and sniffed again. Finally having reached a conclusion, there was a soft pop and the dog was replaced with an overjoyed Sirius Black.

"Harry!" Sirius screamed at the top of his lungs. He grabbed Harry in a hug and pulled him tight.

Harry returned the embrace and was patting his godfather on the back. "Hi Sirius."

Sirius was not going to let go, as tears were actually in his eyes. He knew better than to let that get out.

"Umm… Sirius?"

Sirius sniffled and hugged tighter. He shook his head, making it clear he wasn't going to be letting go from this hug any time soon.

"Sirius," Harry pleaded. "Come on. You're poking me."

Sirius wiped his eyes and pulled away, forgetting that he'd been 'cleaning' in public. "Sorry," Sirius said, unable to stop grinning. "I guess I'm just real happy to see you."

Harry groaned. "Way to stay classy, Padfoot."

Sirius let out one of those familiar barks of laughter. He stepped back and playfully frowned. "You grew up on me! Merlin's balls, you're old, Harry!"

"It's been ten years," Harry admitted ruefully. "And… bugger me. You look younger than I've ever seen you!"

"I know!" Sirius agreed and looked around them. "Crap. I didn't exactly look both ways before transforming just now. You don't think anyone saw us, did you?"

Harry glanced around and didn't see anyone staring at Sirius in awe or fear. "Don't know."

"Let's hope not," Sirius nodded grabbing Harry by the arm and beginning to walk down the street. "You don't have to be anywhere, do you?"

Harry sighed, falling into step with his godfather. "Yes, Sirius. I've followed you into a brand new dimension, managed to locate you, and now have to cut it short for a board meeting before lunch."

Sirius grinned at the thought Harry came after him. "Excellent! We've got lots to catch up on. You ready to go get drunk and trade stories?"

"It's ten in the morning!"

"You're right," Sirius nodded. "The bars probably aren't open yet."

Harry couldn't stop himself from smiling at his godfather's priorities. "Where are you living?"

"Oh good idea! Moony's got some firewhiskey and a bunch of muggle stuff."

"I do want to catch up, Sirius, but are you sure drinking this early is the best idea?"

Sirius led Harry across the street. "I don't know. Are the last ten years of your life anything like the first five at Hogwarts were?"

Harry paused and agreed. "You're right. We need alcohol."

They were on the steps of the flat next to the magically warded cellar when a man dressed like a Ministry Obliviator came scurrying up. "Did you guys see anything like a man-dog around here?"

"He went that way," Sirius and Harry answered in unison, both pointing in the same direction down the street.

The Obliviator hurried off in the direction they pointed without giving another look back at the two men who weren't exactly dressed like the average muggle.

Sirius and Harry grinned at each other. Sirius pointed out, "Great minds-"

"There's nothing great about your-"

"Get inside," Sirius ordered, interrupting Harry right back.

Harry jogged up the steps to the door, shaking his head in disbelief. "I can't believe I found you."

Harry walked into the modest home while Sirius shut the door behind them. Next to the door, Sirius triggered a simple ward that would silence the home from neighbors and the outside world.

"Harry!" He once more screamed as he jumped onto his startled godson's back.

Harry stumbled forward but caught the edge of a chair and kept from falling. He let Sirius hug him again this time from behind, grateful not to be poked. But he drew the line when Sirius started to give him a noogie. Immediately his invisible magical arms sprung to life and lifted Sirius off his back and held him in place a meter off the ground.

Harry crossed his arms and turned around smirking as Sirius was struggling in air, confused as to what was going on.

Sirius saw the look on Harry's face and realized this was intentional controlled magic. "How the hell are you doing this?"

"Wouldn't you like to know," Harry smugly retorted.

"Yes, yes, I would like to know," Sirius answered while kicking his legs back in forth in the air.

Harry set his godfather down gently and shrugged. "I think that'll come up a little further into my tale. But I've only been in this dimension for about a day, and I slept through most of that, so you get to go first."

Sirius nodded and was smiling brightly. "Fair enough. First off though, you can relax. The war here's not half as bad as it probably is for you."

"You'd be surprised," Harry offered.

"Oh yeah?"

"Yup."

"Nice," Sirius admitted thinking of all the friends he left behind. "Oh! Drinks! You want a beer?"

"Sure."

While Sirius ran off towards the kitchen, Harry took a better look around the place. It looked like Moony's kind of place, but you could tell there was a lot of Tonks' influence with some of the brightly colored shelves. There were quite a few pictures of Tonks, some with Remus, some without, and even a few with people that Harry realized were his parents of this dimension. Some of the ones of Tonks and Remus were from when Tonks was frighteningly young, but Harry couldn't deny the happiness in their eyes.

One picture immediately caught Harry's eye and he picked it up to examine it closer. The two people waving in the back were undoubtedly, James and Lily Potter, but the two people in front, Harry realized, were what could have been his brother and sister. Harry doubted he'd managed to have an older sister or reddish brown hair, so he got the feeling the Harry Potter of this world died a long time ago.

"Am I dead, Sirius?"

"I hope not," Sirius came back and handed Harry a beer. "Oh… yeah. In this world, you died Halloween 1981."

"And you?"

"Your loving, caring, valiant godfather tried to hold off Voldemort and protect you, but he was killed moments before you did that night."

Harry sipped his beer wondering how he felt about that. "That was twenty-five years ago, wasn't it?"

Sirius grinned as he sat back on the couch and put his feet up on the coffee table. "Feels like only fifteen, if you ask me."

"Fifteen?" Harry asked. "Are you telling me the Ministry obliviated the ten years you spent in between worlds in the Kingdom of Sensual Pleasure?"

Sirius looked at Harry in surprise and wonder.

"Someone took their gullibility potion, I see," Harry victoriously muttered.

"That's not fair," Sirius argued realizing he may not have spent a decade in a place Harry may have made up. "Because for all the good those Unspeakables did, I still think they obliviated me."

"How's that?"

"Alright," Sirius decided. "So you saw me dueling my cousin, right?"

"More like mocking her and not taking-"

"Yes, yes, that's right," Sirius interrupted. "Not my finest moment. Anyways, she hit me with that blood freezing curse that sent me flying into the veil."

"Blood freezing?" Harry repeated. "Is that what it was?"

Sirius nodded. "Nasty bugger. Very dark because untreated or countered it'll kill you in about five minutes. Paralyzes you immediately and just slowly gets colder and colder. I saw Moony holding you back as I fell into the veil. It all went black for me then. Next thing I know, I'm waking up in a hospital bed in a new dimension. They tell me I've been unconscious and healing for three weeks. The Unspeakables informed me that they interrogated me with veritaserum."

"You don't remember being interrogated?"

Sirius shook his head. "They said I was real messed up but able to talk. I don't know. I don't remember. But they have been a damn sight better than the Ministry back in our world. Set me up with a full nutritional regiment to get me back to pre-Azkaban health, including some expensive mind healing cheering potion treatment, all on their tab. It's why I'm still a little doped up now. Got three more days of progressively weaker doses."

"Expensive cheering potions?"

Sirius shrugged. "I didn't understand it, but there's no denying the end result is a sexy beast."

"You don't remember anything of your time in the Exit?"

Sirius shrugged. "The Unspeakables told me I probably moved through time not just into a new dimension."

"They're wrong," Harry retorted. "You were probably stuck in between dimensions for just shy of ten years."

"How do you figure that?"

"The day you showed up in this dimension was the day I activated the Exit back in ours."

"You know how to activate it?"

Harry shook his head. "Not really, but I've been studying the damn thing for four months."

"Bloody hell, Harry! I just realized you jumped into the Veil! What the hell were you thinking?"

Harry looked a little ashamed at the return of the over-protective godfather attitude. "It wasn't intentional. Besides we're getting sidetracked. The Ministry here fixed you up, drugged you, may have obliviated you, and then what?"

Sirius took a long drink and answered. "I'm a free man, in a new dimension, with absolutely nothing to my name. While I was still healing and staying in St. Mungos they asked if I wanted anyone to come see me. I asked for Moony. I hadn't even considered the possibility that your dad might have been alive."

"Or me?"

"Last I saw you, you had enough problems. Anyways, Moony came to visit me and got the abridged story of my life. Tonks came to visit almost as much and she knows it all too. When the Mediwitch said I could go, Moony said I could always stay with him. Considering he bought this flat with the money he inherited from my death in this dimension, I figured I'd take him up on the offer. Some nights I'll crash on Tonks' couch, but yeah. That's been my life so far."

"Sirius?" Harry asked curiously. "What about James and Lily? You haven't talked to Prongs?"

Sirius pouted and didn't look Harry in the eye. "I met him, but that pillock is nothing like the James Potter that was my best friend."

Harry held back a smile at Sirius' childish behavior. "How is he-"

"He doesn't even like pranks!"

Harry bit his lip at how outraged Sirius was. "That complete bastard."

"He came over with his son, James, junior," Sirius grumbled. "I was all set to surprise him and reveal to him who I really was, where I was from, the works. He didn't even know me, and he was telling his son about how an attitude like mine would never make it in the aurors."

"Well I don't think it would ma-"

"That's not the point," Sirius interrupted. "It's the way he looked down on me just because Moony and I were goofing around. Moony thinks he was probably the same James I knew up until that Halloween."

"So he doesn't know?"

Sirius shook his head. "He thinks I'm some cousin of this world's Sirius Black." Sirius frowned and sipped his beer. "Of course he'll probably figure the truth out when you meet him."

Harry was watching his godfather. "Are you… jealous?"

"Well I just got you back," Sirius pointed out. "And you've got the chance of a lifetime to meet your parents."

"You're pathetic."

"I missed you," Sirius whined. "And now that I've met the monstrosity he's become, I miss Prongs too."

"Monstrosity?"

"He's everything we swore never to become."

"A Death Eater?"

"No," Sirius said with distaste. "Worse. He's a mature adult. A cautious, careful, responsible person who lost his sense of humor and got a stick jammed up his-"

"Egads Padfoot," Harry stopped him. "I think you're getting a little ahead of yourself starting up negotiations with bizarro Prongs over joint custody visits with me. Do you even want to stay in this dimension any longer?"

"As opposed to going back? Or looking for a better alternate dimension?"

"Damn," Harry cursed. "I never even thought about looking for another one."

"Wait, so you know how to get back?"

Harry shrugged. "I was going to suggest the two of us jump into the Exit and see where it takes us."

Sirius rolled his eyes. "Boy you really have unraveled the mystery of that thing, haven't you?"

Harry realized this plan would fall under the stupid category and grimaced. "Not to mention you missed out on the fun of that ride."

"It's that pleasant?"

"Probably the worst form of magical transportation I've encountered and I've hated just about all of them, so that's saying something."

"You think maybe you'd want to stay here?" Sirius asked hopefully.

Harry winced a little. "There's a Voldemort here. There isn't one at home. He's kind of a pain in the ass."

"But there isn't a Boy-Who-Lived here. Nor a dangerous but innocent Azkaban escapee either. I know for a fact they're both pains in the arse."

"We're broke. We have absolutely nothing."

"I'm working on a home, and something tells me we'd be able to get by."

"What about our friends back home? You've got family too."

"Who are all already convinced I'm dead, and apparently have been for ten years. I mean I know you'd be starting from scratch, but on the plus side, you would be starting from scratch. No stares, no preconceptions, no ulterior motives, no one will have a clue what that scar on your forehead is from."

Harry was rubbing his chin in thought. "I really don't have any idea what jumping into the Exit will do or where it will take us."

"Why are we even having this conversation then?" Sirius declared. "As far as this world's Voldemort goes, I say fuck him. Don't even give him a second thought."

"I really can't find it in me to care about him," Harry admitted in slight shock. "I suppose he did kill us in this dimension, but by the same argument we may have never been able to come here, if he hadn't."

"Exactly," Sirius agreed before thinking about what Harry said. "What?"

"It's possible that we came to this particular dimension because our counterparts were gone, meaning that just about any dimension we can get to will be one where we were Death Eater fodder," Harry explained. "Maybe."

"Why?"

"Well I mean, maybe we can only be here because our other bodies are dead."

"You've crossed a gateway to a new dimension and you're thinking about the limits to what's possible?"

"Okay fine, whatever, I thought you were trying to convince me to stay."

"Hey, you believe whatever you want and if it works for you," Sirius said with an exaggerated shrug. "All I know is it's a lot harder to pick up chicks who've spent a decade thinking I was the Dark Lord's favorite and a psychopathic killer. Even then sometimes the ones I could pick up aren't exactly the safest way to spend an evening."

"Good point, Padfoot," Harry nodded. "We should definitely base this decision on where we're going to get the most play."

"Well, if you were willing to use your fame," Sirius argued, "then maybe I can see-"

"I was being sarcastic."

"So are you up for staying here?" Sirius asked. "You could get to know your parents."

"Now they're a selling point?"

"No, but I figure a pitiful little orphan boy who never got a chance-"

"Bite me, Sirius. And don't be so melodramatic and jealous. The James and Lily Potter of this world are a middle-aged married couple that had to bury their infant son 25 years ago. Meeting them won't tell me hardly anything about my parents, two people who died so I could live. And now I have to placate your fragile ego despite the fact that I just chased you, my real godfather who did inadvertently die to protect me, across dimensions."

"Whoa now! You don't get to trip and fall into the veil claiming you chased after me."

Harry was smiling brightly getting the chance to just bicker back and forth again with Sirius. "Why do you think I cared so much about the Exit and spent the last few months studying it?"

Sirius grinned back. "Fine, if you chased after me, then I died a bloody hero protecting you, not inadvertently."

"I'll get started on your medal right away. Getting hit with a blood freezing curse directly in front of the Exit because you were taunting your cousin sounds like at least an Order of Moron, Second Class."

"Second Class?" Sirius demanded. "What do I have to do to get a First Class?"

"Stay dead," Harry smirked.

"Ouch," Sirius chuckled. "Merlin it's good to see you, Harry."

"You're not going to hug me again, are you?"

Sirius stood up threateningly. "No, I'm going to get another beer. Ready for your next?"

"Sure," Harry agreed handing Sirius his empty bottle. When Sirius reached the kitchen Harry's eyes were drawn to the picture he'd set down. "Hey Padfoot, you never mentioned anything about Lily here. Or their kids."

"I met James Jr. just briefly," Sirius called out. "Seemed like a nice enough kid. Didn't care if I called him Jimmy, though the pillock was as annoyed by that name as he used to be back in school. Seeing you now though, I mean you've got Prongs' hair more, but you don't look like him near as much as you used to. James Jr. looks more like his dad than you do."

"How old is he?"

"Seventeen I think," Sirius answered handing Harry another beer. "He's finishing up his sixth year now. Moony figures he's a shoo-in for Head Boy. Come to think of it, were you Head Boy?"

"I didn't go to Hogwarts for my seventh year," Harry explained. "Had more important things to do."

"What?" Sirius gasped. "I can't believe Dumbledore would let you get away with that."

"Dumbledore was dead by then," Harry flatly stated. "And you haven't finished telling me about the Potters of this world. Lily? The girl's name?"

"Sarah Potter, twenty years old, studying healing and apprenticing to Madame Pomfrey at Hogwarts. Lily's teaching Muggle Studies there. I've not met either of them, but Tonks and Moony insist they're both delightful people. Of course they think the same thing about the anti-Marauder. Now your turn. Go."

"Wow," Harry slowly drawled. "The warmth of the family I never knew is overwhelming in your descriptions. But if that's how we're going to play this game. Let's see fifth year, Department of Mysteries, you died. Dumbledore told me the prophecy that night. Pretty crappy night all around. Sixth year, learned a little about horcruxes and Voldemort. Dumbledore got killed by Snape-"

"What!"

"Yeah, Snivellus," Harry agreed. "Some cocked-up plan where Dumbledore sort of made him do it. But things went to hell in a hand basket after that. Me, Ron, and Hermione ditched school to track down the horcruxes so that Voldemort could at least be theoretically killed. Some good times, some bad times, a lot of studying, took our NEWTs, but six years later all three of us survived and we'd pulled it off. Voldemort was dead for good, I'd killed a number of the more pesky minions along the way, and the rest were easy enough for the Ministry to round up. Since then, the last couple of years have been peaceful and well… boring to be honest."

"No, no, no," Sirius said shaking his head. "You don't get to gloss over everything like that. I need some details."

Harry sighed. "You're really going to force me to relive some of my worst memories?"

Sirius stared at Harry and saw a mixture of amusement and a little bit of genuine apprehension. "Dammit. Fine. I'll get more stories from you as I can dig them out. But give me something at least. Killing Voldemort, how'd that feel?"

Harry took a big drink of his beer and carefully considered his words. "Truthfully? It felt fucking fantastic. Every other time I've been responsible for a death or had to take a life I've felt sadness and anger at the situation. But killing him was better than grabbing the snitch from right under some prick's nose. I felt alive more than I ever have. It was disgusting, gory, messy, and hurt like hell, but to kneel over what was left of his body and to watch it burn was amazing and cleansing and therapeutic and blissful. There really aren't words for the complete and total sense of righteousness I felt. I won, he lost. I lived, he died. And I did it without stooping to half of the shit he did."

"Damn," Sirius whispered watching Harry's little monologue.

"What?"

"You looked a little scary there."

"Might be because I am a little scary."

"Damn."

"What now?"

"I just realized you're not going to be able to leave this world's Voldemort alone."

Harry shook his head. "No no. I'm more than happy to leave him alone. This world's Voldemort hasn't done anything to me."

"Besides murder you as an infant?"

"The Voldemort who crapped on my life has been dealt with. Maybe there's a dead baby Harry with a score to settle with this Voldemort, but right now this particular Harry couldn't care less."

"And what happens when you start to care about the people in this dimension?"

Harry sighed. "We'll burn that bridge when we get to it. But if we're starting from scratch, then we're not carrying any old grudges."

"Sorry, I still hate Wormtail and Bella."

"If this world's James seems so different, why's it so hard to believe others might be even more different?"

"But Harry…" Sirius moaned.

"Fine, I hate them too. I'm just saying this Voldemort's done nothing to us, Harry and Sirius the dimension travelers, so I have no desire to have anything to do with him."

"Us?" Sirius grinned. "I'm automatically included in your inevitable quest for vengeance?"

"Everyone I give a damn about in this dimension so far is in this room," Harry shrugged. "I'm grateful to the Unspeakables, Moony, and Tonks for taking care of you, but yes, us. And as low-key as this world's Voldemort has been, there stands a decent chance our paths will never cross."

Sirius just laughed at Harry, making no attempts to calm down.

Harry pouted silently and drank his beer.

"Whatever happened to Peter?" Sirius asked softly before adding louder, "Or Bella?"

"Dead and dead," Harry said. "That's one of the nastier memories."

"Feel up to sharing that one?"

"When's Moony or Tonks getting home?"

"Moony's off work at five and apparates home, so right around then. Tonks' schedule fluctuates a bit more, but usually checks in on me before six."

"You want to go get us something a little stronger and I'll tell you this one?"

Sirius agreed without question and hopped back towards the kitchen to fetch the firewhiskey.

"First thing you should know is the prophecy," Harry yelled down the hall towards Sirius.

"Either must die at the hand of the other?" Sirius called back. "That the one?"

"Yeah. How'd you know that?"

"Same prophecy here," Sirius explained as he poured two small glasses of firewhiskey. "Only people think it's about Neville. Or it used to be."

"Neville? Used to be?"

Sirius took a small sip of his firewhiskey and lay down on the couch. "Long story. Yours first."

Harry nodded and began. "There was a line in the prophecy about he will have power the Dark Lord knows not. The moment Peter and Bella died was the moment the Dark Lord found out a little about that power."

"Is this that thing where you lifted me up and held me there?"

Harry smiled and sent an invisible arm towards his godfather.

Sirius yelped rubbing his shirt. "That's awesome! You have got to teach me how you cast a wandless nipple twisting curse."

"I doubt I'll be able to because that wasn't a spell," Harry said with a shake of his head. "Not exactly."

"Well it sure smarts like one," Sirius said tenderly pushing on his chest.

"After we'd taken our NEWTs," Harry explained. "I needed to focus my studies and wanted to get really good at a field or a style of dueling. I'd heard my mum was pretty impressive at charms and my dad at transfiguration. I'd seen Dumbledore using transfiguration in a duel and it was… it was on a whole different level."

"You transfigured my nipple?"

"No, transfiguration I was decent at, probably as good as Hermione, but it would've taken years to reach even McGonagall's level of mastery. No, after a few days of musing I decided I wanted to master the summoning charm. I'd always been pretty good at that one and I wanted to see how far I could take it."

Sirius was mumbling in confusion to himself. "You summoned my nipple?"

"First I learned it silent, then wandless. After that silent and wandless both was a piece of cake and within just a couple weeks I could summon with only a thought, no hand motion, no movement, no words."

Sirius was impressed listening to Harry.

"After summoning I figured I'd try banishing. Took a bit of work, but pretty soon I could change a light bulb without ever getting off the couch, or even looking up."

Harry grinned at his godfather. "I could completely control nearly all physical aspects of my immediate environment. The more complicated things got the more focused I had to be but it was fun searching for limits. Distances took a lot more control and tired me quickly. After a while we asked Professor Flitwick for advice on directions to improve my talent for this particular branch of charms."

Harry chuckled. "That little bugger was squeaking and chirping with joy. He couldn't believe the level of control I had and it was his idea to take a look at the magic being cast. Are you familiar with any oculamagi spells?"

"Yeah," Sirius said pulling out the wand Tonks had given him. He cast the spell and asked, "What am I looking for?"

Harry cast the same spell and saw their bodies were softly glowing indicating they were wizards. "Can you see the magic glowing around my body?"

Sirius nodded before jumping back in surprise as a ghostly magical hand shot out from Harry's body straight towards him. It stopped just before Sirius and grabbed his beer before he could spill it.

"Careful there Padfoot," Harry grinned. "You almost spilled your beer."

"What the hell is that?"

Harry had extended his usual half dozen arms and they were all floating gently in the ambient waves of magic. "These are what my magic manifested due to my constant combination of summoning and banishing charms." One of his extended arms tweaked Sirius on the nose and patted him on the back.

"I'm not sure if there's a limit to the number of arms I can call up, but I did extensive training keeping six of them always up."

"You've got some extra arms," Sirius said. "Did you really need to train yourself how to use them?"

"I'm still figuring out uses for them," Harry said and pushed himself up into the air with three of them.

Sirius could see them lifting Harry in the air, but it was weird seeing only the magic without anything physical behind them. He could see how it appeared Harry could hover at will.

Harry swiftly and smoothly held his physical arms out and pretended to fly in the air towards Sirius stopping just before him. His magical arms extended as he arced backwards away and landed gently right in his seat. "In most duels, I don't even get hit with a spell," Harry added as suddenly six nearby objects began hovering protectively around him each held in magical arms that overlapped and crisscrossed as they floated.

"Damn," Sirius admitted canceling the oculamagi spell on his eyes. "Without seeing the magic it looks even more impressive."

Harry set all the items back where they belonged and let his magical arms dissipate. "And they saved my life when I was captured and held by Death Eaters."

"Bugger," Sirius admitted pouring himself a little more firewhiskey.

"Draco fucking Malfoy," Harry spat the name out, "put Dobby under the Imperius and forced the house elf to slip me a Draught of Living Death. I woke up chained in a magically warded cell. Three days of listening to a few of the idiots spew their usual rubbish, shoving me around, spitting on me, and trying to act superior. But it was clear that I was to be saved for their Master. Finally, Bellatrix put me in magic inhibiting cuffs and led me towards a small meeting room.

"To this day, I'm still slightly curious at what the Dark Lord was going to say but I never gave him the chance. As soon as she led me up to his horribly clichéd throne, I saw the two other Death Eaters already standing by him were Lucius Malfoy and Wormtail. She was about to hand Voldemort my wand when I made my move.

"The magic inhibiting cuffs stop magic channeling out from your hands and wrists but my invisible magical arms were free. And all of my magic had woken up ready and waiting as soon as I got out from the wards of that cell. Voldemort reached out to take my wand from her when he picked up on my magic in the air and stopped short. He looked me straight in the eye right as all six of my arms grabbed their targets and pulled. Three simultaneous cracks echoed around the room as Bellatrix, Lucius, and Peter's heads twisted violently. They all fell to the ground dead from their broken necks while I just stared at Voldemort."

Harry took a large gulp of firewhiskey. "I felt a little sick at the sound, but I saw fear in Voldemort's eyes." Harry shrugged and finished anticlimactically "Then I grabbed my wand, found a broom, and alternated between blocking spells and throwing objects at Voldemort. I took quite a few wrong turns, but eventually escaped."

"Fuck a little scary," Sirius whispered to himself. "You're a lot scary."

"On a completely unrelated side note, if you ever happen to try apparating while wearing magic inhibiting cuffs, you should know that you'll splinch your hands off at the wrist."

Sirius laughed out loud. "Totally unrelated, I'm sure."

"The best part, aside from taking out those three, was Voldemort got a lot more cautious and his attacks slowed down to a trickle." Harry took another drink. "It was when I got back that I found out Voldemort had been busy in the three days he had me locked up."

"That doesn't sound ominous at all," Sirius pointed out in an effort to ease the tension.

Harry sighed tiredly in remembrance. "He drew the aurors to Azkaban in a bit of misdirection and attacked personally in Hogsmeade, during a Hogsmeade weekend."

"Oh," Sirius winced at the thought of students.

"Thing is, you remember the DA?"

"Rebellious little study group you started up, sure."

"Well, after me, Ron, and Hermione didn't return to Hogwarts a few members took it upon themselves to keep the group going, one of those being-"

"Holy crap! Ginny?"

Harry looked at his godfather in surprise. He was about to answer affirmatively when he realized Sirius wasn't even looking at him.

A soft familiar voice spoke up from over Harry's shoulder. "Hi Sirius."

Harry closed his eyes not even wanting to look up. "Aww… bugger."

Chapter 4

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: For those wondering, I've not seen Elfen Lied but it's not a horrible comparison for how Harry's magical arms can act. Started to watch an episode and quickly realized it wasn't the sort of thing for me. Additionally, I reckon I should credit ChuckDaTruck for sharing the 'half your age, plus seven' rule, but I don't think he made it up himself either. And for those wondering, this fic will be similar in style to Browncoat, in that some chapters will be much funnier than others as it's about the story I'm telling more than simply getting as many laughs as possible. That's why this chapter may not be as funny as the last one, but more along the lines of amusing and hopefully interesting. All reviews are always welcome and appreciated.

"A halfbreed! A mudblood! A bad Master!" Kreacher shrieked excitedly. "Oh good Master! You even brought your own dead muggle-lover!"

"Kreacher," Harry snapped trying to shake the elf loose. "Stop humping my leg. That's an order."

"I'm so sorry, Master," Kreacher pleaded. "Kreacher will do better. Do you want Kreacher to put away your things?"

"You rotten little crap-bubble," Sirius chuckled at the insane elf. "We're not his things."

Kreacher looked confused and turned towards Harry. "Master?"

"They aren't my things," Harry instructed still uncertain how he felt like dealing with Kreacher. "Remus and Tonks are friends and guests. Sirius is not the same Sirius you used to know. And Ginny… well I guess she is my very own dead muggle-lover."

Ginny's cheeks brightened in a ghostly blush and whispered towards Tonks, "Harry said I'm his lover. He's so cute when he's possessive."

"He is kinda cute," Tonks admitted conspiratorially.

Ginny glanced between Tonks and Harry. She leaned in towards Tonks, "You know now that you're not married to your dad, you could morph to look like me and go out with my Harry. I'd be fine with that." Ginny was doing a fair impression of Dobby, she was nodding so fast.

Tonks saw Ginny was a little too enthusiastic at the idea.

"I wouldn't mind," Ginny explained. "I could even help you with all the bits and parts that you can't see. Stupid ghost robes."

"Maybe later," Tonks said silently adding 'or never.'

Tonks noticed how dust covered the kitchen and back entrance were. "Hey Harry, you mind if I go exploring?"

"Knock yourself out," Harry said waving towards the entry hall and living room. As Tonks left the room, Harry whispered to the two Marauders, "I'm curious if the troll leg umbrella stand is in this dimension."

A loud crash and clang indicating the Auror tripped was followed by a shout of "Son of a-"

Tonks' yell was interrupted by a familiar screeching voice. "Mudblood! Filthy mudblood whore!"

"Guess so," Harry grinned.

"Home sweet home," Sirius exclaimed with a wistful smile.

"A warmer welcome you'd be hard-pressed to find," Remus said.

"Shut up, you bloody hag!" Tonks yelled from the front hall.

"You're going to die, you filthy mudblood whore!"

"You hear that Moony?" Sirius said with a playful elbow. "You're the proud father of a filthy mudblood whore."

"Bad Master?" Kreacher questioned curiously at this new attitude from his other Master.

"I'm not a Sirius Black you've ever met before," Sirius explained to the little elf as he walked out of the kitchen.

Sirius reached into the entryway and spotted the offending portrait. "Hello mother."

The portrait stopped her incessant shrieking at Tonks and looked at Sirius in wonder. "Can it be… Sirius?"

"Sirius, as in your dead son who secretly pledged himself to the Dark Lord and has only just now been reborn under the Dark Lord's awesome power?" Sirius offered seeing the hopeful smile on his painted mother's face. He chuckled happily, "No."

Mrs. Black huffed. "You clearly have the disappointment's attitude."

"There's the pet name every child wishes their mum would call them," Sirius retorted with a sigh.

Harry followed behind his godfather and added, "For what it's worth, one time she called me the disappointment's disappointment."

Mrs. Black frowned. "When did I…?"

"You didn't," Sirius said dismissing the confused portrait. He looked towards Harry inquisitively. "I hope you responded in kind to my dear old mum's portrait."

Harry shrugged. "I did piss on her."

Sirius couldn't help it and burst out laughing.

"In my defense I was drunk at the time. She didn't bother me too much after that."

Sirius tapped his chin in thought. "I wonder if Dad knew it was that easy."

"Old Master knew," Kreacher answered immediately. "Old Master did it quite-"

"Kreacher!" the portrait hissed indignantly.

"Mistress?"

"Yeah," Harry interjected. "We really didn't need to know that."

"Would you like to punish Kreacher?" the elf asked hopefully.

"No," Harry answered without pause. "But I would like to see this place cleaned up some. You are capable of cleaning, aren't you?"

"Oh yes Master," Kreacher cheered enthusiastically. "I shined and polished all the muggle torturing tools. Even put fresh batteries in some of the muggle ones."

"Really?" Tonks perked up curiously.

"Down girl," Sirius jumped in. "Not in front of your father this close to his time of the mo-" Sirius let out a squeak and turned to run as Tonks and Remus both attempted to curse him.

"Why don't you work on cleaning the rest of this place, Kreacher, starting with the kitchen," Harry stated firmly. He saw the confusion on the elf's face and added, "Think of this entire house as one big muggle torturing device."

"Yes Master," Kreacher accepted happily and popped away to begin scrubbing.

Harry walked over towards the fireplace and stuck his head under the hearth. "You guys know if this is connected to the floo network?"

"Doubt it," Tonks answered. "No one's used it in twenty-five years, so even if the monthly upkeep is covered, it's still cycled far enough out of use that you'll probably need to get it reconnected."

"We should definitely get it reconnected," Sirius answered showing his face now that Remus and Tonks had given up chasing him. "But let's set it to default deny."

"You know," Harry suggested. "I can put up a Fidelius charm for us."

"You can cast a Fidelius?" Remus asked, slightly impressed.

Harry nodded. "It's one of the charms I've gotten quite good at."

"I'd rather not a Fidelius, if it's all the same to you," Sirius said. "We can ward it plenty, but we're not exactly prime targets of the Dark Lord here. And I'd like to be able to bring home a muggle without dealing with too many questions."

"Couldn't you just memory charm them?" Harry asked, pulling the curtain across Mrs. Black's portrait before she could start up a rant about muggles.

"I'd rather not," Sirius explained with a grimace. "Something about bringing home a girl and ending the evening—or morning more likely—with a memory charm just feels a little like rape."

"You don't rape her, I hope."

"No, of course not, it's just… it still just feels wrong. A violation of her rights or something."

"You're weird," Harry decided. "But even if you don't want a Fidelius charm, I still want to pick up some blank anchor stones."

"I don't have much money," Sirius began.

"You don't have any money," Remus corrected.

"Yes and that's not much now is it?" Sirius agreed. "So maybe we should hold off on the big magical purchases."

"Umm, if this dimension is anything like our old one," Harry stated. "They only cost about forty galleons for a set of eight and two discs. I've got that covered and it'd make me feel a lot better. I'd settle for four and one disc, if you're that worried about it."

"It's your money," Sirius said not understanding how anchor stones made Harry feel better. "If we're lucky there might be a set in the family vault."

"I know I'm the old man around here," Remus said. "But it is almost four in the morning and I've got to be up for work in three hours. You sure you want to stay here tonight?"

Sirius nodded. "We'll be fine. Get your beauty sleep, grampa. You look like you could use it."

Remus smiled seeing how much happier Sirius was now that Harry was here. "You guys are welcome to make breakfast at my place, but please don't steal everything from my kitchen."

"Yeah, I'm gonna head out too," Tonks said walking down the stairs. "This place is pretty big, which means you guys got a lot of cleaning to do and I need to make myself scarce. I wouldn't mind digging into some of those books in the—Dammit!" Tonks cursed as she once again tripped over the troll leg umbrella stand.

"Whore!"

"Painting!" Tonks yelled back at the portrait thoroughly confusing it. Tonks snickered seeing the curtain had flung open and Mrs. Black looked befuddled. "I'll catch up with you guys tomorrow night."

Sirius was chuckling after Tonks was gone, leaving the two dimension travelers alone. "She still trips over that thing every time."

Harry was laughing just as much. "You know it's cursed, right?"

"What?" Sirius looked at Harry in confusion.

"Oh yeah," Harry snickered. "That umbrella stand is jinxed to trip her up."

"No," Sirius said doubtfully. "Really?"

Harry nodded. "I think it was something one of your cousins or maybe mother did to Andy, and Tonks inherited it from her mum."

"Oh I bet Tonks was pissed when she found that out," Sirius said thinking of all the times she'd tripped over it throughout the years.

"Who said Tonks ever found that out?"

"Mr. Black," the old goblin grumbled as he looked up from his desk. "I hope you're not here to waste more of my time."

"Not at all, Elder Rahdoh, not at all," Sirius said with a grin. "I've even brought my very own ancient Lord with me this time."

"Indeed?" the goblin said leaning over to look at Harry.

"Harry," Sirius greeted. "I'd like you to meet Elder Rahdoh the Moderately Sane, the Director of Ancient Family Affairs and occasional amateur singer. Elder Rahdoh," Sirius turned and introduced. "I'd like you to meet my godson, Harry."

The goblin saw the young man wave meekly and turned towards Sirius. "Mr. Black? You failed to recall that you had a godson who was an ancient Lord?"

"I couldn't find him until just yesterday and only then found out that he was an ancient Lord."

The goblin tilted his head down and was peering over his glasses at Harry. "And just what family are you the head of?"

"You don't have to know that," Sirius jumped in before Harry could answer. "Do you?"

"I suppose not," Elder Rahdoh agreed. "But for your sake I hope the magic accepts him."

"Not a problem," Sirius nodded immediately. "Magic is Harry's bitch. We just need you to take us there and invoke a test of nobility."

"Blimey Sirius," Harry blurted out. "You can't expect to pass any test of nobility."

"Ironic isn't it?" Sirius grinned. "It used to be accepted that it was a test of the bloodline or purity but people from other families have been designated heirs, even muggle-borns, so they renamed it nobility."

Elder Rahdoh pressed a button and spoke some Gobbledegook into a magical intercom. A perfectly clear voice said something in Gobbledegook back and Elder Rahdoh sighed. "Well, let's get this over with so I can get back to work. I figure this will either work or you shall die. Come along."

Harry saw the smile on Sirius' face falter for a second as they got up and followed the old goblin out of his office and down towards a cart. The three of them fit into a single cart and they began the fast and bumpy ride down the track.

The wind was rushing in their ears, but Harry's curiosity got the better of him. "Elder Rahdoh, you said this will either work or he'll die. Do you have a preference which?"

Elder Rahdoh kept his hand on the lever and turned towards Harry and Sirius. "Well, there's a lot more paperwork if he dies," the goblin smiled wickedly. "But on the other hand, I wouldn't have to worry about seeing him again. So each side has its advantages and disadvantages."

The blunt honesty of goblins always amused Harry, almost as much as the overwhelming enthusiasm of house elves. He chuckled at Sirius' frown and Elder Rahdoh's complete indifference to them.

A few minutes later the cart slowed to a stop in front of a very different looking vault than Harry had ever seen. It appeared to look more like a cave with a solid, smooth block of onyx for a door. Two goblins were waiting on either side of the door, one of them leaning against the wall in irritation. Two large spikes had been crudely slammed into the ground in front of the goblins. Topping the obviously magical staffs were small chambers of constructed metal and clear glass resembling lanterns. Inside each chamber was a glowing ball of magic that arced within its confined space.

"I do not have all day," Elder Rahdoh grumbled urging them to hurry up.

"Harry," Sirius instructed. "You've got to stick your Family ring in the lower corner of that square on the wall. Don't stick it in the center."

"Why shouldn't I stick it in the center?" Harry asked walking over towards the carved wall that had etchings indicating where to place his fist.

The goblins exchanged curious looks, beginning to think they may get to watch an ignorant wizard or two die today.

Sirius saw them all visibly perk up and explained, "The center is for the Black family ring and it will simply open the vault. The bottom right is where acceptable ancient families can nominate others after the family goes headless."

Harry shrugged and pushed the ring onto the spot. "If you say so."

The vault suddenly became active and the two spikes in the ground began flaring up and sparking like crazy. Currents of magic were bouncing back and forth between the two magical conduits while the inky black onyx of the door rippled into a blurry clear haze.

Sirius took a breath and walked right through the magical current and his body began to glow and flicker on its own. He didn't even slow down as he walked straight through the solid wall and into the Black family vault.

Harry turned towards the goblins all watching curiously. "Am I supposed to leave my hand up here?" When no goblin answered, Harry sighed and propped his arm up holding it in place.

Sirius walked straight into the vault and saw everything was obscured from view other than a small pedestal with a ring box on it. He strolled right up to it and opened the box. "Yes!" Sirius cheered when he discovered there was still a Black family ring. Without hesitation, Sirius removed the ring from the box and slipped it over his finger.

Harry was watching the other goblins when his ring let out a flash of white light that reflected off the wall. "Whoa!" Harry exclaimed holding his arm still in place. "The magic's asking me for permission. What do you think, boys? Should I make him sweat it out?"

Elder Rahdoh had looked up at the flash of light and replied. "I've never heard of the sponsor being questioned. This isn't right."

"It's okay. This actually kind of makes sense." Harry explained before playfully yelling loudly, "Should I or shouldn't I?"

"Dammit Harry!" Sirius yelled out from inside the vault. "If I die, I'm going to haunt you and be even more annoying than-"

Harry encouraged the Black family magic to accept Sirius and effectively shut Sirius up as the ring molded to his finger, confirming him as the new Lord Black.

Sirius came skipping out of the vault and stopped just before crossing through the magical current again. "We're good!" he exclaimed, proudly showing off his new ring.

"Finally," Harry said dropping his arm from where he was holding it.

Just as he did, the door to the vault rippled and became solid black. The two spikes of magic fizzled down to the beginning levels, and the two silent goblins wiggled them free from the ground in disappointment.

Harry stuck his ring in the center of the square and much to the shock of the goblins the door slid straight open revealing the contents inside.

"Cool," Harry agreed pulling his hand away. He stuck it right back again and this time the vault door slid shut with a heavy clang.

"Let me try," Sirius called out placing his ring where Harry's had been. As expected the door slid open again. "That's brilliant."

The two goblins carrying the magical spikes walked away into the darkness of the tunnels, while Elder Rahdoh sat back in the cart to wait on the two still living wizards.

Sirius strolled over to a small chest and found it about a quarter full. "Nice. We got about… eight hundred galleons here or so. Give me your money pouch. I'll fill 'er up a bit."

"Let's take a couple hundred galleons each," Harry stated tossing his pouch to Sirius. "That should be enough for some clothes and food and other immediate necessities." He was looking through an old box of parchments. "Hey! Did you know we got a seat on the Wizengamot? And the Hogwarts Board of Governors?"

Sirius was stuffing handfuls of galleons into both his and Harry's pouches. "Yeah, I remember something about that. Don't remember who it was that was using them, but they're probably not exactly in line with our ideologies. Go ahead and grab whatever you got that looks interesting. We've got a day of shopping ahead of us."

The two Lord Blacks packed up everything they felt like taking and walked out of the vault. Harry put his fist over the center of the square and the vault door slammed down, sealing shut. They hopped into the cart and Elder Rahdoh began the journey back to the surface.

"So you are Lord Black," Elder Rahdoh said looking at Sirius.

"Yup." Sirius said bobbing his head up and down, resisting the inner urge to stick his head off the side of the cart and let his tongue hang out as they flew down the track.

The goblin turned to Harry. "And you are…?"

Harry smiled and answered, "Lord Black."

Elder Rahdoh just sighed and went back to looking forward.

"Does this happen often?" Harry asked curiously at the lack of surprise from the goblin.

Elder Rahdoh shook his head. "I don't think it's ever happened before."

"Aren't you curious?" Sirius asked with a mischievous grin.

"Will it prevent me from having to do double the paperwork I now must?" Elder Rahdoh retorted at the two stupidly grinning wizards. He turned back to face forward as they remained silent. "I thought not."

"Why are you buying a bottomless bag? I've got my satchel," Harry said patting his man's purse.

"Well that's yours," Sirius said. "We both need a lot of stuff and I don't want to get our things mixed up."

"Do I have cooties?"

"I want my own, okay?"

"Why not just charm a bag rather than paying the extra for a magical one?"

"Do you know how to charm a bag to be bottomless?"

Harry opened his mouth to answer when Sirius interrupted him and clarified. "I'm not talking space expansion charms that just make little things bigger, but the proper ones where everything is easy to reach, cushioned, and protected."

"Buy your bag, you big baby," Harry grumbled. "Let's hit Ollivanders next though. I want to pick up this dimension's version of my wand if it's there."

Sirius nodded and got in line for the cashier.

"I'll wait for you outside," Harry stated, stepping out to look at the noon day sun. He was quietly watching the people walk by, completely oblivious to the nonchalant way a wizard was sneaking up behind him.

Harry couldn't even identify the whispered word but the moment the spell washed over him, he immediately knew the word the man had said.

Imperio.

Harry was scolding himself for not having been more vigilant or aware of his surroundings. His magic was jumped and ready to attack, but he didn't want to waste the energy it would take to snap the hold of the Imperius Curse blindly.

His confidence never wavered knowing with certainty that he could overpower the will of the caster. It just was immensely easier to do when you're actually given a suggestion or command that you could respond negatively to. So far the man behind Harry had only cast the spell and was waiting for something else to happen before giving instructions.

Harry saw people continue on their way, completely oblivious to his predicament.

After two and half very slow-moving minutes through which Harry kept reconsidering just expending his energy and snapping the spell, Sirius finally exited the shop. He walked over towards Harry, glancing briefly at the man standing just behind Harry facing away.

"So when Ginny went away, is she just invisible and around us? Or does she actually go somewhere else?"

Harry just stood there pointedly ignoring Sirius.

"Harry?" Sirius repeated. "Are you even listening to me?"

Just as Harry had hoped, the caster of the Imperius Curse mentally ordered Harry, 'Tell him to go away.'

'That was a mistake,' Harry mentally sent right back, snapping the hold of the curse instantaneously.

The wizard suddenly turned to Harry, who was spinning around to get a better look at his attacker. Before the man had even managed to fully draw his wand from his sleeve, both of his arms were jerked out to the side and his wrists were bent back snapping loudly as they broke. He yelled out in pain and Harry quickly cast a silencing spell over the wizard.

Sirius had drawn his wand and saw two other men apparate away immediately.

Harry was pleased to see how quickly Sirius reacted and petrified the silently screaming man. "Sirius, can you call the Aurors to come arrest this man for casting an Unforgivable on me?" Harry levitated him up and down an alley. "I'm going to get him out of sight so as not to disturb the people shopping."

Sirius just watched Harry calmly follow the man around the corner and ran back into the shop he'd left moments ago. They let him use the floo to call the Department of Magical Law Enforcement who were going to be sending some Aurors within the minute.

Harry led the man away and pushed him up against the wall. He spun him around and ripped the sleeve off of the man's robes and shirt, exposing the Dark Mark.

The man was in shock, pain, and was terrified, feeling helpless with two broken wrists. Harry didn't seem to have even needed any effort to hold him in place, snap his bones, and reveal the Dark Lord's symbol. He could see the power in Harry's eyes and didn't even realize that his thoughts were running beyond his control.

Harry held eye contact and attempted to Legilimens the wizard. He found the man's name was Gordon Smith and that he was going to use Harry to destroy the post office. Two other Death Eaters were there with the same instructions.

Smith discovered what Harry was doing and expelled him from his mind, demonstrating an average talent at best for the mind arts.

Harry sighed and stunned the man, "You're supposed to pick someone at random, and you picked me. That's bloody hilarious."

"Harry," Sirius called out as he jogged down the small alley between buildings. "Alright?"

Harry nodded and saw two uniformed aurors following behind Sirius, looking alert as they took in the situation.

"I'm Auror Billings, this is Auror Anderson," the man said, introducing himself and the female partner with him. "You say a dark wizard cast an Unforgivable on you?"

"I don't know him well enough to call him a dark wizard, but he cast the Imperius on me about five minutes ago," Harry explained and handed Billings the wand that Smith had dropped. "Pretty sure it's the last spell he got off."

Billings accepted the wand and checked it using Prior Incantato. As indicated the last spell was an Imperius Curse and the ghostly effect matched Harry's appearance indicating he was the target.

"Both of his wrists are badly broken," Anderson stated, inspecting the downed wizard.

Billings could see the Dark Mark clearly on the man's arm and so far had no reason to doubt Harry's story. "Care to explain his wrists?"

"I didn't want him to attack me again. I have no idea how proficient that man may be at wandless magic and I didn't know if he had any portkeys with him."

"So you broke his wrists?"

"Is there a preferred response to being subjected to an Unforgivable?" Harry retorted looking at Auror Billings.

"Ahh Harry?" Sirius jumped in. "As Lord Black, I know you're always allowed to defend yourself in kind. So a clear attempt on your life like an Unforgivable, means you could kill him perfectly legally."

"You think I should kill him?" Harry asked glancing back at the unconscious wizard.

"Since he's stunned, it might be hard to convince the two Auror witnesses that you were defending yourself," Sirius felt like the obvious needed to be stated.

"Lord Black?"

"Yes?" Harry and Sirius both said turning to the Auror.

"Damn," Billings cursed. "I've got to call my boss in on anything involving the head of an old family." Billings cast a couple of spells on a small card he kept in his pocket.

"There's a mediwitch coming to deal with the suspect," Anderson explained. "Would you like her to check you out first, Lord Black?"

"Naw, I'm good," Sirius said knowing she wasn't asking him. "What about you, Lord Black?"

"People are really this anal over the pureblood and Lord crap?" Harry asked looking at Sirius.

Sirius nodded. "Might as well use it to our advantage, Lord Black. Now are you sure, you're okay?"

"I'm fine," Harry said nodding towards the confused Auror Anderson. Harry saw Sirius looking at him expectantly, waiting to be addressed. Harry shook his head. "I'm not going to call you 'Lord Black.'"

"You have to," Sirius argued back. "I've got the ring and everything."

"Wait, so you're Lord Black?" Anderson said, addressing Sirius.

Sirius nodded.

"We both are," Harry added. "Though I've got more experience at it."

"Somehow, I'm not surprised to see you here," a new voice jumped into the conversation.

Harry did his best not to stare at the man.

Sirius bit his lip, not having expected this. "Nice to see you too, Assistant Director Potter."

"Mr. Black," James Potter greeted tightly. "Unable to stay out of trouble, I see."

Harry could tell Sirius was uncomfortable and jumped in, "If you're here in an official capacity, I believe Lord Black may be more applicable than Mr. Black."

Sirius resisted the desire to cheer out loud and point in James' face.

James Potter turned towards Harry and was obviously sizing him up. He didn't seem to recognize Harry or have any idea why he felt so familiar. "And who might you be?"

"I'm another Lord Black," Harry answered more calmly than he felt. "And I don't believe we've met."

James was not amused. "Which one of you is the real Lord Black?"

"We both are," Sirius explained showing him his family ring while Harry made his visible and waggled his fingers at the Assistant Director.

"Lovely," James mumbled making no effort to hide his sigh. "How is this possible?"

"Why is this relevant?" Sirius retorted.

"I'm going to need to explain how there are two Lord Blacks in my report on this incident," James argued.

"You really don't like us, do you?" Harry bluntly asked.

"I don't believe the fact that you happened to have been born in a certain family means the rules should be different for you."

"What rules exactly are so different? A clearly marked Death Eater cast an Unforgivable on me. Should I not have defended myself?"

"My apologies, Lord Black," James said the name dripping with false sincerity. "Now if you're going to refuse to share with me just how there are two Lord Blacks, can you at least explain exactly what happened here?"

Harry could see Sirius was very irritated with confronting bizarro Prongs, and proceeded to once again recount the details, beginning with feeling the curse wash over him and waiting until he was issued a command. He glossed over some parts indicating he simply used magic to restrain the wizard and break his wrists, not offering anything specific like the lack of spells required.

Auror Anderson left with the injured wizard and mediwitch while James and Auror Billings continued asking Harry and Sirius question after question.

"Are we ever going to get our shopping done," Sirius mumbled.

"Of course Lord Black," James said giving Sirius a condescending look. "I'm sorry the Department of Magical Law Enforcement consumed so much of your time. We will most likely contact both of you for the trial, and it's possible you will be required to testify."

"Come on, Harry," Sirius said beginning to walk away.

Harry turned towards them noticing James' eyes had widened slightly at his name. "We're done, right?"

James quickly composed himself and nodded. "Yes, we're done." He turned from them without even saying goodbye and apparated away.

Auror Billings nodded at Harry and followed after his boss with a soft pop.

"You think we can make it to Ollivanders without you causing another scene?" Sirius muttered in irritation.

Harry shook his head and fell into step with Sirius. "Boy you really don't like him, do you?" Harry said echoing his earlier comment.

"You couldn't tell what a pillock he's become?" Sirius snapped back.

Harry shrugged adding, "I'd never met him before."

Sirius paused realizing just what that statement meant and looked back at Harry cautiously.

"For Merlin's sake, Sirius," Harry grumbled hurrying towards the wandmaker's shop. "Don't waste the whole day pouting like a Malfoy. Your face might get stuck like that."

"I'm not pouting," Sirius pouted. "So what did you think?"

"I think… I think you're being a little unfair to him," Harry answered opening the door for Sirius to lead the way in.

"Whatever," Sirius grumbled. "All I know is the James Potter he was twenty-five years ago would be horrified at what he's turned into."

"Welcome," Ollivander greeted coming out from the back. "Lord Black and… Lord Black?"

"How do you do that?" Sirius said always getting a bit weirded out by Ollivander.

"We're wearing the rings, Sirius," Harry pointed out dispelling some of the old wandmaker's mystique. "And you need to remember that twenty-five years ago he lost his son and best friend, another best friend stabbed him in the back, and the last remaining Marauder was forced to grow up and be responsible for his new eight year old daughter."

"I know," Sirius grumbled.

Harry turned and addressed the slightly confused older man. "We could use a couple wands, holsters, and some polish."

"Which hand is your-"

"Right," Harry and Sirius both answered in unison lifting their right arms up.

"Creepy," Ollivander whispered softly.

Harry ignored the idea that he was creepy to Ollivander and added, "I was looking for perhaps a phoenix feather wand in Holly, maybe eleven inches or so. Got anything like that?"

"You know it is not the wizard who chooses the-"

"Yeah, yeah," Harry nodded. "Call it a hunch that a wand like that will choose this wizard."

Ollivander harrumphed not particularly liking the lack of respect he was receiving, and unable to unravel the mystery of these two Lord Blacks. "That is an unusual combination, but I do happen to have a wand fitting that description." Ollivander turned and went into the back.

Harry turned to Sirius. "I'm not saying James should be our best friend, but considering what he's been through I guess losing his sense of humor isn't surprising."

"This is most disconcerting," Ollivander stated returning from the back. "But I'm sorry to say I do not have the wand you seek."

"No?" Harry asked curiously. "Did you sell it?"

Ollivander shook his head. "I doubt it."

"What do you mean?"

"The wand is not where I last recall it being, but I haven't thought about it in many years."

"Did you lose it?" Sirius asked curiously.

"I do not lose wands, Lord Black," Ollivander stated with certainty. "I suspect I was the unwilling recipient of a memory charm. Had you not asked for that exact combination, I may never have thought about that wand again. Factoring this in, it is possible I did sell the wand, but I doubt it."

"You want some help seeing if there's a block that can be removed or a charm broken?" Harry asked.

"No thank you, Lord Black," Ollivander stated turning down the offer of help. "If there's anything recoverable I should be able to locate it myself. Now, was there anything else I could do for you?"

"I suppose I'd still like to purchase whatever wand you have that best suits me," Harry answered.

"Same here," Sirius said pointing towards himself. "For what it's worth, my last wand was twelve inches, driftwood, with a dragon heartstring."

"Curious," Ollivander whispered inspecting Sirius closer. "That is the exact same wand Sirius Black used to have. What did you say your name was again?"

"Sirius Black," he answered happily.

"Just a coincidence, I'm sure," Harry added with a firm nod.

"Of course," Ollivander said giving Harry a long look. "So says the other Lord Black who was inquiring about the brother to the Dark Lord's wand."

"Huh," Harry said slapping his leg in surprise. "I didn't know that. Small world, isn't it?"

Ollivander harrumphed and began going through the many wands he had in stock. For the next hour he kept handing new wands to Sirius and Harry to try, all with varying degrees of failure and on occasion slight success. The process continued until Harry felt a strong connection with a wand he tried out. Not as nice as his proper wand, but far more compatible than any others he'd waved that day.

Sirius found it hilarious that big, bad Harry was now the proud owner of a dainty little nine inch ash wand with a unicorn hair from a particularly vain male unicorn's mane.

Sirius' amusement lasted about ten minutes, until an 8 and a quarter inch wand made of driftwood and unicorn tail hair produced some musical, pink sparks when he swished it.

"Not a word, Harry. Not one word," Sirius warned as he paid for his wand and holster.

Harry was just smiling widely staying silent.

Ollivander was under no such threat and explained, "Your connection produced very rich, though high-pitched tones. That wand should be exceptional at delicate work."

Harry made no effort to hide his snort. He glanced at Sirius and turned to Ollivander, "Is my wand not so suited to… delicate work?"

"Harry," Sirius said warningly.

Ollivander shook his head and explained, "Your combination is less precise but capable of channeling more magic easily."

"And I didn't get any pretty sounding delicate tinkling bells," Harry said with a straight face, pointedly not looking towards Sirius.

"No, Lord Black, you didn't," Ollivander said while completely aware of how Sirius was taking the reminders. "It takes a special person and special circumstances to get any sort of positive response other than sparks."

"Let's get out of here," Sirius grumbled already halfway out the door.

"In case you need a reminder," Harry said to Ollivander. "You have a memory charm on you. And if you find anything out and feel up to sharing, I'm interested in what happened to that wand."

"Good day, Lord Black," Ollivander nodded as Harry chased to catch up with the once again pouting Sirius.

"Shopping sucks Slytherin's balls," Sirius grumbled into his drink.

"I hear that," Harry agreed munching on his fish and chips. "I don't know why I thought Hedwig might be in this dimension waiting for me to buy her. I'm going to miss that mothering little bird."

Sirius shrugged. "I think the owls we got are going to be fantastic. I can't believe no one had bought Smokey."

"Your owl has gas," Harry reminded. "I'm not sure there's a lot of demand in the market for owls with digestive difficulties."

"You're just jealous," Sirius said haughtily. "And where did you come up with that name for your new owl?"

"He picked his own name," Harry said. "I was just making up names until he responded to one. And if he says his name is Kid Killer McGee, who are we to say it isn't?"

"Kid Killer McGee," Sirius repeated. "That's almost a better name than Smokey."

"It is a better name. We got some clothes, owls, wands, personal things, a little bit of food," Harry recounted. "Next we should get a clearer idea of what we already have at Grimmauld Place before we work on redecorating."

"Remember I'd like it to pass for a muggle place on the surface so that we can entertain guests from all walks of life. Confine the obviously magical stuff to a few rooms."

"We'll have to do something about the portrait of your mother then," Harry said finishing the last of his food.

"Did you ever figure out a way to remove her?"

Harry shook his head. "Never tried too hard. Didn't really need to."

"Why not?"

"Oddly enough it was Dudley who provided the simple and often overlooked solution."

"Dudley?" Sirius exclaimed. "I wouldn't think you'd want to have anything to do with the Dursleys."

Harry shrugged. "Yeah well, Dudley gave the constables my name when he got arrested one time, and I was intrigued enough to bail him out."

"What'd he do?"

"He went streaking with some of his mates at a West Ham match," Harry grimaced. "He was the ham."

Sirius shuddered having remembered what Dudley looked like in Harry's third year. "So what did Dudley do to my dear sweet Mum? Punch a hole through her or something?"

Harry shook his head. "Nope. He just moved a book case in front of her."

"Oh," Sirius said anticlimactically. "I guess that would solve the problem, wouldn't it."

"You know where we're meeting Tonks and Moony?"

Sirius nodded. "It's a muggle bar about a block from where Tonks' apartment is. Decent place with some friendly regulars."

Harry stood up and vanished his garbage. "Let's go unload our spoils and change into muggle outfits." Harry saw Sirius was still sitting there with a frown on his face. "What is it now?"

Sirius sighed. "Just seeing you use your proper wand makes me want mine that much more."

"There's nothing wrong with your new wand."

"I don't care about that," Sirius retorted. "Well not too much. It's just, as good as this wand feels compared to the others I've used, I can still tell it's not as perfect a match as my proper wand is."

"What happened to your original wand?"

"The Unspeakables said my clothes were destroyed and there wasn't one with me when I came out the veil."

"What about in this dimension? Do you know where that one is?"

Sirius nodded while chewing on the inside of his cheek. "Yup."

"Where?"

"Same place it's been for a quarter of a century, Godric's Hollow."

"Ahh," Harry said in understanding. "And you couldn't get it back unless you made your peace with bizzaro Prongs, and convinced him of the truth of who you are."

"I suppose if you wanted to do things the hard way," Sirius explained as his face split into a bright grin. "But personally, I think it's going to be much easier to simply steal it."

Chapter 5

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: I don't expect future chapters to take as long to finish as this one, but feel free to remind me to update quicker if you like.

"So now you're both Lord Black?" Tonks asked in between sips.

"Yup!" Sirius and Harry cheered in unison.

"That's going to get so fucking old."

"Hey!" Sirius whined.

"What's next? You're not joking, you're Sirius?"

"He was probably thinking it," Harry agreed.

"And I suppose you shaved this morning, but you're already Harry?"

Sirius stretched his waistband out and peeked down the front of his pants. "What if I'm seriously hairy?"

Remus cringed swallowing the beer in his mouth. "Can't we have one evening without your kibble or bits coming up?"

Harry didn't even pause before asking, "Does half mast count?"

Remus groaned while Tonks muttered, "As if one of them wasn't bad enough."

"Hey there's actually two of everyone to keep straight from our point of view," Harry argued.

"Yeah," Remus recalled. "How're you doing with that? Because Sirius still likes to break down sniveling like a little baby."

"One time!" Sirius insisted. "One time a bug flies in my eye."

"A bug no one could ever locate," Tonks added.

"It must have flown away," Harry mockingly suggested.

"Thank you," Sirius agreed. "That's exactly what it did."

"Although come to think of it," Harry said scratching his chin. "I think it flew back in your eye when I found you yesterday. Pesky reappearing bug."

"Bugger off," Sirius grumbled with a smile.

Remus sighed in the silence that followed and looked at Harry. "We're doing our best not to encourage those sorts of puns."

"By ignoring him though, he takes it as a challenge and will try to come up with worse puns," Harry pointed at Sirius. "See? Even right now, his warped little mind is searching for something that will provoke the right reaction. Something about the bee in your bonnet? The bug stops here? No ifs, ands, or bugs about it?"

"Oooh, good one," Sirius grinned.

"For crying out loud," Tonks jumped in, emphasizing her own addition to the pun-fest.

"Not you too," Remus groaned.

"I could say that was accidental," Tonks smiled. "Bug I won't."

Sirius nudged Harry. "Maybe you could teach Moony a buggle repelling charm?"

"This is why," Harry addressed Remus while pointing at Sirius. "This is why you have to rub his nose in it, right away. It's the only thing that works."

Remus was intrigued. "And just how would you rub his nose into a pile of bad puns?"

"Yeah," Sirius wondered. "How would you?"

Harry shrugged. "For something like this? I'd say just pinch him anytime he makes a pun."

"Oww!" Sirius yelped and clutched his ear. "That's not funny."

Tonks grinned and pinched Sirius too when he was looking at Harry.

"Oww!" Sirius yelped again.

"Huh," Remus said while considering the efficacy of this plan.

Sirius jumped up from his seat. "Dammit Harry! Leave my bum alone. It's too pretty for that."

"Sorry," Harry grinned unrepentantly. "Thought I saw a bug there."

Sirius growled.

"He was just trying to get a little revenge for you," Tonks sweetly argued.

"Before you somehow manage to lower the level of maturity in this conversation any further," Remus interrupted.

"I'm not sure that's possible," Tonks said.

"Shut up you fatherfucking traitor," Sirius snapped before slapping the back of his pinched neck. "Oww! Dammit Harry!"

"He took that as challenge," Harry demonstrated. "But now pinched and mollified, he's uncertain. He wants to curse me, but the potential of being pinched again is holding him back."

Sirius just narrowed his eyes at Harry. "He knows where you live. He knows where you sleep. And he is a Marauder."

"The Marauder name just doesn't carry as much weight as it used to," Harry commented warily noticing Remus looked as indignant as Sirius. "But that reminds me, what happened to Wormtail here?"

"Are we talking about Death Eaters again?" Tonks whined.

"Sorry," Harry shrugged. "Still trying to catch up with this dimension. We can talk about something else."

"He's alive," Sirius said answering Harry's question. "A wanted Death Eater and the Aurors know his animagus form."

"Fair enough," Harry nodded. "So what are some more pleasant topics of discussion? Chudley Cannons still blow unicorn balls?"

"Juicy ones," Tonks added. "But they've already won more games this year than last."

"How many have they won this year?"

"One," Remus answered. "By forfeit."

"Some things stay the same," Harry commented noticing Sirius was staring at an attractive brunette at the bar.

"Yeah," Remus saw Sirius wasn't even paying much attention. "Those brave few fighting the effects of evolution we can always count on. Right, Padfoot?"

"Right," Sirius agreed absently before turning back towards the table. "Wait, what did I just agree to?"

"A duel," Tonks answered. "The three of us against you."

"Hey, that's not a bad idea," Sirius cheered.

"Really?" Harry asked curiously.

"Not you three against me," Sirius corrected. "I was thinking you two against the Lords Black."

"Ahh," Remus paused and glanced at Harry. "You killed your Voldemort, right?"

Harry nodded.

"Yeah, that's not happening," Tonks answered.

"Just a friendly duel," Sirius argued. "You can even start with Harry's wand."

"Hey," Harry complained.

"You've got another," Sirius muttered out the corner of his mouth.

"Good point."

"No duels, no Voldemort, no Death Eaters, no Quidditch," Remus interjected. "I want to get to know you, Harry. I never had the chance here. What do you do for fun? What are some of your hobbies?"

"I like Quidditch, but you already said no to that."

"Do you play?"

"Not professionally, but I like to think that I could make a pro squad. Unfortunately, I dislike people too much to play for a crowd."

"You hate people?" Tonks asked curiously.

"Only in large groups," Harry clarified. "Specifically, large groups who told stories about me before I even knew magic was real. And seem to think the death of my parents was some sort of fairy tale happy ending."

"They told stories?"

Harry nodded. "Ginny forced her dad to tell it every night when she was five."

"It was when I was four!" The ghost suddenly appeared and argued. "And it was only every night for about six months."

Harry jumped to block her from view, harshly scolding. "Ginny! Get the hell out of here!"

"Why?" Ginny frowned, having just appeared.

Harry peeked over his shoulder and whispered angrily, "Because this is a muggle bar."

"I won't drink much," Ginny offered.

"No! Go away!" Harry whispered forcefully.

"Umm… Harry?" Tonks interrupted. "You know muggles can't see ghosts, right?"

Harry snapped his head towards Tonks. "Ix-nay on the uggles-may."

"They can't?" Ginny shrieked. "All this time, you've-"

"Shh," Harry hushed. "But they can certainly hear them, so shush!"

"Let her stay," Sirius urged. "The muggles can't see her, and she'll stay quiet, right?"

Ginny nodded with a grin at Sirius, keeping her lips sealed and silent.

"Need I remind you," Harry argued, "that while Sirius and I may have been dead for twenty-five years, there is another living breathing one of her walking around right now? She's a lot more likely to be recognized than either of us."

"I think in a muggle bar we should be pretty safe," Tonks said with a roll of her eyes.

"Alright, so you like Quidditch," Remus said redirecting the conversation back on track. "What else do you do for fun? Or do you have a job?"

"No job. I've had a fair amount in the bank from my folks and an award from the Ministry. I think they retroactively put a bounty on Voldemort to buy some good press, but," Harry shrugged. "It was free money."

"How much they pay for something like that?"

"Fifty thousand galleons," Harry answered. "They knew I'd turn it down, so they also awarded all the DA members a thousand galleons each, if I happily accepted the award at a ceremony."

"You'd just refuse fifty large like that?" Tonks asked curiously.

Sirius rolled his eyes. "I could've told you that."

"Of course now," Harry answered, "in a new world where I don't have any savings, I don't think I'd endeavor to be quite so noble if someone were to offer me free money."

"So no job, likes Quidditch," Remus summarized. "Any hobbies? Maybe a special girl in your life?"

Ghostly Ginny harrumphed loudly, staring at Remus.

"Present company excluded," Remus added at Harry's exasperated look.

"Nope," Harry answered. "No special girl."

"You're not a…" Sirius paused unsure if he should voice the last word.

Harry looked at his godfather curiously before realization dawned on him and he blurted out, "No! No, nothing like that. I mean I have done it before."

"Really?" Sirius asked in surprise.

"Sure," Harry nodded. "Lots of times. That was when I first realized if I was angry enough I could will Ginny away."

"I didn't want to watch that!" Ginny shrilled. "And yes, Sirius, many times."

"Huh," Sirius said shaking his head. "I never would have pegged you for that."

Harry looked at Tonks and Remus who were both looking at Harry appraisingly. "So you expected me to be a twenty-five year old virgin?"

"What?" Sirius asked in confusion. "What are you talking about?"

"Weren't you asking me whether I was a virgin?" Harry said, and glanced over seeing Ginny nodding with him.

"No," Sirius said with a bark of laughter. "I was asking if you were gay. And apparently your answer is no but you have done it before."

"Many times," Tonks helpfully added.

"No special girl," Remus grinned.

Harry blinked. "Sorry Moony. I don't swing that way no matter how well kept your moustache is."

"There are other straight men with moustaches, I'll have you know," Remus tiredly pointed out.

"So in answer to your question," Harry said turning to Sirius. "Nope. I'm not. Never have been."

"Well there was-"

"Ginny, shut it," Harry warned pointing his finger.

"It counts."

"You want me to banish you?"

"Dennis apologized, or should I say Denise apologized?" Ginny stopped at the look on Harry's face and hurriedly floated over to hide behind Sirius. "I'll be quiet now."

Harry sighed and looked at the other three brightly smiling faces. "Don't ask."

"Can I picture it?" Sirius grinned happily. His grin faltered when Harry narrowed his eyes and Sirius felt a sudden painful poke. "Oww! My eye! Dammit Harry."

"You know, come to think of it," Harry continued ignoring Sirius' angry muttering. "Since we're staying, the history of that world is like a figment of our imagination with very little relevance here. So I think it's my turn to learn about this world."

"Fair enough," Sirius agreed. "What do you want to know?"

"I'm guessing Death Eaters are going to be unavoidable, but you mentioned something about Neville Longbottom?"

"The Chosen One," Tonks agreed. "After you were killed, the Order quickly moved to hide the Longbottoms away. It was known for years that the Dark Lord wanted to kill Neville Longbottom. Considering, he'd gone out of his way to murder one baby born in late July of 1980, and was trying to kill the other, the story and prophecy eventually became common knowledge."

"And I take it Neville's not still in hiding?" Harry asked, hoping to avoid any uncomfortable questions.

Remus winced. "It was early summer of '87 when the contents of the prophecy became public. Knowing there was a savior in the form of a six year old growing boy, a lot of people wanted to help him. Whereas before he only had very limited contact with the wizarding world, that year he was inundated with birthday gifts: lots of weapons, cloaks, armors, books, that sort of thing. People assumed he was the next Dumbledore and when he was ready, he'd lead the fight to destroy Voldemort."

"I can empathize with the pressure," Harry wryly added.

"Thing is, no one knows what happened to him," Tonks continued. "March 21, 1988 he disappeared. Completely. No trace of him. No sign of his existence. Not even an indication whether he's dead. Just… gone."

"No one's seen nor heard from him since he was seven?" Harry clarified.

"Nope," Remus sadly answered as he took a drink of his beer.

"Nothing confirmed," Tonks corrected. "But there are plenty of unconfirmed accounts."

"Unconfirmed?" Harry asked askance.

"About a year after Neville disappeared, a wizard dressed in black, stood up to the Dark Lord and stopped him," Tonks explained. "Ever since then, it's been like Voldemort is on the defensive. Our spies say he's had several major plans fall apart before the Order even heard about them. Not quite as extreme as the way your first war ended, but before Neville's disappearance and after is like the difference between a war and a skirmish."

"It does seem sort of… cautiously relaxed around here," Harry added.

"A lot of people believe Neville got some special training and has been protecting us," Tonks continued. "They say he is waiting until he can defeat Voldemort before returning to his family. I'm not sure about that, but a lot of people have seen a wizard in black fighting off Death Eaters."

"As an eight year old?" Harry repeated, making sure he understood. "Do you believe that?"

Remus was hesitant but answered, "It's one of the nicer things to believe in, when the other options usually include Neville's death."

"If he's really the Chosen One," Tonks pointed out. "I mean what was the point of that prophecy for the downfall of the Dark Lord, if it got you killed and Neville killed too before anyone was marked, right? Neville being alive was the only possible option for it… well, until you-"

"No!" Sirius said slapping a hand over Tonks' mouth. "We discussed this."

"I know," Tonks grumbled. "We swore the damn oath not to tell anyone, didn't we?"

Harry had a guess about this. "What's going on?"

Sirius never even considered keeping this from Harry. "In case it's escaped your notice, Harry, these two Lupins are members of the Order. And the knowledge that a Voldemort killer and prophecy-approved person is in this dimension might be kinda relevant to the Order."

"Yeah," Harry nodded. "I pretty much assumed that was unavoidable when we decided to stay here."

"Well I'm not ready to give up the hope that it's avoidable," Sirius insisted. "I made these two swear oaths to not divulge any secrets about your past."

"Really?" Harry said grinning brightly and earning small smiles from Remus and Tonks in return. "You guys would cover for me like that? You don't even know me."

"I know you well enough," Sirius retorted. "And they've gotten to know me."

Tonks shrugged. "It sounds like Voldemort was a lot worse in your dimension than here. He'd never dream of strolling down Hogsmeade openly murdering children."

Remus nodded. "You're the son of a James Potter. I'll protect you even if it's from Dumbledore."

"Does he know about you?" Harry asked looking at Sirius.

Sirius waffled in his answer, finally saying, "Yeah I think he does. He never outright said anything, and he was trying to trap me in couple of questions, but he asked me to join the Order and I declined. He could certainly tell I wasn't the same Sirius he remembered."

Tonks smiled at Harry. "So we're keeping quiet about you, but back to the discussion. With you here now, I'm a bit less likely to believe Neville's alive, but before you, the answer was definitely yes, I believed Neville was the mysterious black wizard."

"I've seen weirder things than an eight year old powerful wizard," Harry figured.

"You know we're going to come up in the next Order meeting," Sirius said gesturing at Harry.

"You are?" Remus asked curiously. "I thought Harry managed to arrive without raising any red flags?"

"That was before this afternoon though," Sirius added. "When Harry managed to thwart a Death Eater attack, requiring the Assistant Director of the Department of Magical Law Enforcement to come to the scene and take our statements."

"You met James?" Remus asked. "How was he? And, also, umm… Death Eater attack?"

"He was a prat."

"He was fine," Harry said giving his godfather a scolding look. "He was professional, though I'm not sure if he was staring because he was suspicious of me, or because he thought I looked familiar."

"Are you the stuffy Head of Family that tossed off the Imperius Curse?"

"Stuffy?" Harry repeated indignantly.

Tonks grinned. "I didn't connect that 'til just now. Yeah, Potter called you stuffy. You put him in a pretty grumpy mood all day."

"Go Harry," Sirius cheered quietly while letting his eyes drift towards the brunette seated at the bar.

"I'm not stuffy," Harry grumbled. "He's a judgmental pillock."

"Hey, that reminds me," Sirius suddenly asked, doing his best to act innocent. "The day after tomorrow's the second Friday of the month?"

"Yes," Remus slowly agreed.

"And don't the midget Potters go to the Order meetings too?"

"Why do you ask?" Remus warningly replied.

"No reason," Sirius grinned and winked at Harry.

"Hmm," Remus scoffed.

"Those meetings always last a good hour and a half, right?"

"Sirius," Remus warned.

"It's not what you think, so relax," Sirius argued.

"Well then what is it?"

Sirius failed to come up with a quick response and faltered at the sight of the attractive brunette looking right at him. She was whispering something to her friend. "Who is that Tonks? She's talking to your friend."

Tonks turned towards the bar and spotted. "Melissa?"

"Melissa's the one you introduced me to, right?" Sirius clarified. "Who's her friend?"

Tonks furrowed her brow. "Don't know." Tonks caught Melissa's eye and waved her over.

"Hey Tonks," Melissa greeted calmly approaching the group of wizards. "Sirius, wasn't it?"

Sirius just nodded.

"Okay, Sirius, listen up," Melissa began. "Don't be obvious about looking, but you know the brunette I was sitting next to that you were eyeing like a piece of meat?"

"34C, yup," Sirius answered.

"Lovely," Melissa grimaced. "That's wonderful. Because she got out of a long term relationship a little over a month ago and is now desperate for some unconditional sex. So I just need you to pretend that I've been subtly trying to figure out if you have any—Sirius, what are you doing? Don't get up. Don't go over… oh god."

Sirius had jumped to his feet and was determined to be a good Samaritan, not even waiting for Melissa to explain the situation. There was an attractive woman desperate for sex, and that was all Sirius needed to know.

"Liz is going to kill me," Melissa mumbled.

Harry shrugged. "It sounds like locating sex was her first priority and ding-ding-ding, she struck gold."

"Gold?" Remus repeated doubtfully.

"Well, asbestos, anyway," Harry corrected.

Melissa shook her head, not particularly wanting to know. "I don't believe we've met."

"Sorry about that," Tonks said in sudden realization. "Melissa, you may remember my dad, Remus, and this sweet young hunk of man is named Harry."

"I think you've made my godfather's night," Harry grinned in greeting. "Or Liz will soon."

Melissa smiled weakly, before turning straight towards the ghostly form of Ginny. "And you are?"

Ginny let out an eep of surprise. "You can see me?"

"Crikey, Melissa," Tonks said smacking her forehead. "I forgot that you're a squib."

Recalling Melissa's question, Ginny answered, "I'm Gin-"

"Ginny!" Harry interrupted before he could stop himself. "That's Ginny."

Melissa glanced between Harry and Ginny. "Is Ginny short for anything?"

"Vaginny!" Harry answered immediately hoping his voice wouldn't crack. "It's short for Vaginny."

Melissa looked at Harry oddly. "Not Virginia?"

Ginny huffed.

"Or Genevieve? Ginnifer?"

Ginny harrumphed.

"Nope, she's our…" Harry paused and furrowed his brow. "Vaginny."

Sirius came running up to their table. "Melissa, it's been smashing seeing you again. Harry, you may want to stay on the other side of the manor tonight. Good evening ladies." Sirius finished without wasting a single breath and hurried towards the door of the bar where Liz was waiting.

Melissa tried not to think about what that meant. "So Harry, is that short… for anything?"

Ginny scoffed at how unsubtle the squib was acting.

"No, not short," Harry grinned proudly. "Personally, I think Harry's plenty long."

Ginny turned and scoffed at Harry.

"You're as shameless as your godfather," Melissa playfully mocked.

"You never know," Harry countered. "I could be far more shameless."

Melissa's eyes widened and she glanced at Tonks and Remus. She saw they were as amused as she was. "You're a wizard, right?"

Harry just grinned and winked at her, as a pair of his magical arms began to massage her shoulders.

"Oh goodness," Melissa stumbled for a moment at how quickly she relaxed. She had to turn her head both ways to verify there wasn't anyone there. "Tonks, Remus, it was a pleasure seeing you again. Harry? I must admit, I'm a little worried about Liz. I think the best thing will be for you to take me back to your place." She closed her eyes and groaned softly at Harry's impromptu ministrations.

"I think we'll catch up with you Lupins later," Harry stated as he got up and walked out with Melissa.

"I couldn't even tell when he cast magic," Remus finally admitted, trying not to think about how quickly they'd been ditched. "What was Harry doing to her?"

"No idea," Tonks shook her head and bit her bottom lip. "But I think I'd like to find out."

"The words of a disturbed and fanatical portrait come to mind," Remus groaned not wanting details of his adopted daughter's sex life.

"You're one to talk, filthy half-breed," Tonks retorted and stuck her tongue out playfully. "What do you think they're gonna do at the Order meeting? Do they even know where we meet?"

"I don't know," Remus answered. "But I think for the sake of plausible deniability we're better off not knowing."

Tonks sighed. "Maybe, but I bet that's not as fun."

Harry slowly made his way down the stairs, still a little groggy getting up this early.

"Good morning, Harry," Sirius boisterously greeted as he was inventorying the kitchen.

"You're not a morning person, are you?" Harry asked fearfully.

"It all depends on the night before, now doesn't it?" Sirius cheerfully retorted. "I hope you weren't too upset that I ditched you?"

"Certainly didn't seem it," Melissa smugly answered as she walked into the kitchen.

Sirius saw the look on Melissa's face, and glanced over at Harry, exorbitantly pleased with his godson. "Good morning, Melissa. I certainly didn't expect to see you so soon."

"Ugh," Melissa grimaced and looked to Harry helpfully. "He's a morning person."

"Actually, I think he may still be drunk." Harry corrected looking around the kitchen. "I see Kreacher cleaned this place up. We got anything for breakfast around here?"

"If you mean food," Sirius said looking in the last pair of cabinets in the row, "then no."

Melissa looked at Harry curiously. "What else would you-"

"Don't ask," Harry shook his head.

"I'd offer to run out and get something," Sirius shrugged. "But I don't really know my way around the neighborhood."

"Just apparate somewhere in the alley," Harry suggested. "Wizarding restaurants can get your carry-out meals ready a lot faster than most muggle places."

Sirius' eyes bulged. "Umm… Harry?"

Harry saw the worry on Sirius' face and glanced over at Melissa. He suddenly remembered with a wry smile. "That's right. You left too quickly last night before Melissa here spotted Ginny, and Tonks was kind enough to remind us that Melissa's a squib."

Sirius nodding in understanding before asking, "Where is Ginny?"

"She went away," Harry succinctly answered.

Melissa shrugged. "I don't think she likes me much."

"If I were to take a guess I'd bet it was probably more of a matter she didn't like what you were doing to Harry more than it was you personally," Sirius offhandedly remarked.

Harry sighed having halfway expected something like that.

Melissa clarified. "If you want to get technical, I think Harry was doing more things to me than I was doing-"

"Breakfast anyone?" Harry interrupted.

"Diego's okay?" Sirius asked looking at Harry and Melissa.

Harry nodded and saw Melissa looked indifferent. "Make sure to get muggle food and we've gotta watch what we say around Liz."

"Who?" Sirius asked in confusion.

"Oh Merlin," Harry groaned while Melissa just goggled at Sirius. "That's her name, Sirius. Liz. 34C? Up in your room still?"

"Huh," Sirius said with a smile. "You learn something new every day. Alright, I'll be back with four breakfast platters. You might need to wake… umm, what was her-"

"Liz," Melissa angrily supplied.

"Liz," Sirius repeated with a lecherous grin leaving them to wonder if he was pretending to have forgotten her name just to irritate them. "You might want to wake her up. She went back to bed, after calling in to take the morning off."

"We got a phone?" Harry asked.

Sirius shook his head. "She's got a mobile. Speaking of, we should probably get one of those. I mean we just moved in, so not having a phone hooked up works for now. But it won't make much sense for too long."

"I'm going to wake Liz," Melissa stated as she left them alone in the kitchen. "She may be able to take the morning off, but I can't."

Harry watched Melissa glance over her shoulder back at him and grinned to himself.

Sirius saw the extra sway Melissa was putting into her hips and the look she flashed at Harry. When she'd disappeared out of view, Sirius punched Harry playfully on the arm. "You dirty man-whore, you!"

"Like you're one to talk," Harry chided. "Liz who?"

Sirius sighed happily feeling like a part of his life was back in order. "Merlin, I missed you James." The moment the name tumbled from his mouth Sirius knew it was wrong.

Harry could only arch an eyebrow at the obvious slip of the tongue. He was highly amused and planned to poke fun at Sirius for this later.

Sirius shook his head. "Don't read too much into that. Okay, breakfast."

Just before Sirius could apparate away, Harry added. "And get some good juice. I don't want pumpkin."

"What's wrong with pumpkin juice?"

"It tastes like pumpkins."

"Fine," Sirius grumbled. "I'll get some muggle juice, Harry."

Remus and Tonks were sitting next to the four known members of the Potter family, James, Lily, James Jr., and Sarah. Tonks was having a whispered conversation with Sarah when the Headmaster stood up and addressed the Order.

"Welcome friends and allies," Albus began looking towards all those assembled. "It pleases me when we get together because it is convenient and not out of necessity."

"Sturgis?" Albus inquired. "Would you like to start us off with some good news?"

Sturgis Podmore stood up and nodded at everyone. "Hagrid and I just got back from our annual visits with the giants. All four leaders of the biggest clans all said the same thing: they would have said no, if there even had been an inquiry from the Dark Lord. But there weren't any."

"That is good news," Albus agreed. "And of the lesser clans?"

Sturgis shrugged. "Vondal doubted any of them would support the Dark Lord. To do so may incur the wrath of the other giants who wish to stay neutral. He said it with a lot more grunts and perhaps a few shorter words, but that was the gist of it."

"Excellent," Albus said. "And Grawp?"

"Doin' great," Hagrid answered enthusiastically. "He's, eh, still datin' that strange Chang woman."

"Love comes in many forms," Albus wisely added. "Emmeline? Have we heard back from the vampires?"

"Yes," Emmeline Vance answered. "I had the misfortune of a surprise visit last week. Nothing has changed in their neutrality and they still can't stop flirting like they're in the theatre. And I have one personal message I'm supposed to deliver."

Emmeline turned to the side to address the man standing in the corner. "Julius said, 'Severus, stop writing. We're not going to turn you.'" She turned back towards the rest of the Order and finished. "That was it."

Albus could sense the anger and humiliation in the Potions Master and quickly continued. "Thank you, Emmeline. Remus, have you heard anything?"

Remus was holding in his laughter at the face Severus Snape was making and shook his head. "The only organized packs are all in Eastern Europe and they'd contact me before dealing with the Dark Lord."

"Tonks?" Albus turned to the metamorphmagus. "I don't know what details of your new assignment are classified, but is there anything you would like to share?"

Tonks' eyes widened and she glanced over at James, who only shrugged in response. Tonks began, "Alright. Thing is, a few days ago some blonde bird showed up in the Department of Mysteries. The Unspeakables weren't even sure where she came from, but she was asking a lot of curious questions about Lucius Malfoy."

Everyone there was familiar with that name as the man had bought his freedom too many times to count.

James saw Tonks didn't want to give out too many details, and continued for her. "What's notable is that she stunned and obliviated three Unspeakables before escaping. And all we have to go on is a description of a young to middle-aged blonde woman, who bears a passing similarity to Narcissa Malfoy but more… veela-like."

Tonks snorted at how large breasts consistently translated into veela-like. "So far she's not really committed any crimes that we know of other than assault on Ministry representatives when she escaped, but they got a lot of questions for her."

"The Department of Mysteries specifically requested Tonks for this job," James continued. "Indicating she was uniquely qualified for it, and instructing us not to ask why that is. Any interest in voluntarily offering answers to questions I'm not going to ask?"

Tonks smiled and shook her head knowing the real reason was because she knew Sirius, a recent confirmed dimension traveler. "Sorry. It's a pretty cushy assignment and I don't want to mess it up."

"If there were any danger or relevant threat," Albus jumped in. "I have no doubt Miss Lupin would inform us."

Tonks nodded heartily.

"I know James has a Death Eater attack to report on," Albus announced surprising many who hadn't even heard about one. "But was there anyone else with something they wished to discuss?"

Mundungus Fletcher grunted and said, "I heard some talk about worries on the other side, rumors that the Black family didn't just have a new Head, but an actual Lord."

"They are not just rumors," Albus answered, "But that ties into what James has to say. James?"

James patted his confused son on the arm as he stood up. "A couple days ago, three Death Eaters were going to put civilians under the Imperius Curse and attempt to burn down the Post Office in Diagon Alley. The reason this is the first most of you have heard of this is because it was thwarted before it ever got going."

"Was it Neville?" A hopeful voice in the back called out.

James Potter resisted the urge to groan at people jumping to conclusions. "No, it was not Neville. Gordon Smith, a cousin from Austria of that Smith family, is a marked Death Eater now in custody. He put a young man under the Imperius Curse in preparation for the attack only for the wizard to break the curse and subdue Mr. Smith rather severely. The other two Death Eaters immediately apparated away."

Amos Diggory let out a low whistle. "Breaking an Imperius is no simple task. Sounds like he pissed off the wrong guy."

"Considering how things worked out, I'd say he pissed off the right one," James countered. He continued a little pompously, "I was called in because the young man was Lord Black. Now there were a few curious things about this, first being that with him was the…" He paused just before saying the name, "Sirius Black that a few of us have met."

Remus and Tonks were nodding, making no effort to hide that they knew all of this.

"What I still don't understand, but have managed to ascertain from the goblins, is that they are both in fact, Lord Black. Sirius only received the title that morning."

"As fascinating as this is," Severus butted in, making no effort to hide his disdain. "Do you have a point?"

James frowned at the immature man's antics and proceed to ignore the interruption. "The other Lord Black, who I believe is named Harry-"

Tonks and Remus were both nodding affirmatively, surprising James as he continued. "He spoke of the Imperius with familiarity. Not necessarily implying he was proficient at casting it, but at the very least the effects of being subjected to it. And after snapping the Curse on him, rather than simply disarming Smith, he broke both of the man's wrists instantaneously."

James saw he had their attention and added, "Without drawing his wand, saying a spell aloud, or even turning to face the Death Eater."

"Sweet," James Jr. said quietly earning a chuckle from Remus.

"When I interviewed him afterwards, he was as calm and arrogant as you'd expect an ancient Lord to be," James explained. "And after interrogating Smith, I got the feeling this Harry had some power to back-up his arrogance."

"Is he a threat?" Arthur Weasley inquired.

"To Death Eaters it sounds like," Dung answered earning himself some chuckles.

"What do we know about this Lord Black? Or the other one for that matter?"

Albus lifted a hand and answered, "I myself met with Sirius Black a few weeks ago as he bore such an uncanny resemblance to the one many of us remember."

Albus was unconsciously stroking his beard. "But the man I met with had eyes far more haunted than should be. They still sparkled with mirth but he has clearly lived through horrors.

"The Unspeakables are notoriously tightlipped, but I managed to gather that they understood why his eyes seemed so… weathered. Given their attitude towards him, I surmised that they have no worries of him joining the Dark Lord. I perceived his attitude to be far more in line with the Sirius Black we remember than with some of the other members of the Black family. I believe Remus can tell us more. Remus?"

Remus was expecting this and explained. "I'd consider both Sirius and Harry friends. I can assure you all there's no chance they'd ever join the Dark Lord."

"Would they be interested in joining the Order?" Lily spoke up to ask.

"That was why I had approached Sirius to meet with him," Albus answered.

"You approached him?" Moody snapped wondering what Albus was doing with so few precautions.

Albus nodded. "There's undoubtedly a reason the Unspeakables are involved with him at all."

"What'd he say?" Lily asked.

Albus smiled sadly. "I got the feeling he was sick of fighting and seeing friends die. He was not particularly receptive despite lacking direction in his life. But I do not know about the other one, Harry."

Tonks leaned back and grinned. "Something tells me whichever way one of those Lord Blacks goes, so goes the other."

"It's this way."

"No, it's this way!"

"What are you talking about? You've never even been here."

"I can see the wards from here."

"Oh," Sirius said looking in the direction Harry was pointing. "Maybe it is that way."

Harry closed his eyes and sighed. "How did you talk me into this?"

"The Order meeting just started and we know this place is going to be empty for at least an hour. You've got Potter blood and should be able to open up the safe. Cheer up, Harry," Sirius grinned as he began the trek towards Number Three Godric's Hollow. "This will be fun."

"And how much ward-breaking experience do you have?"

Sirius paused for a moment before continuing. "Let's not quibble over the details."

Harry stopped right in front of the first layer of wards next to Sirius. "This isn't asking for trouble at all, now is it?"

"Aww come on," Sirius grinned. "It's not like Voldemort is going to show up and bounce a Killing Curse off your forehead, right?"

Harry sighed once more and was looking at all the layers of wards in front of them. "I'm going get you back for that, you know."

"I know."

"Alright. Let's do this."

Chapter 6

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: I love reading each and every review. I don't always respond to all of them, but I do try and make an effort to answer any questions asked of me. So if you enjoyed a chapter, saw how it could be improved, wanted to point something out to me, had a question, or possibly find yourself extremely offended and upset, then make sure and let me know that in a scathing review. Thanks for all the feedback so far. It is appreciated.

"Now's your last chance to do the smart thing," Harry said taking a closer look at the wards in front of them.

"I'm insulted you even have to ask."

"Sorry Padfoot," Harry said patting the man on the back. "I should know better than to accuse you of being smart."

"Your mum and Moony used to try the same stuff, but I never gave in to their peer pressure."

Harry grinned at his godfather. "I see three different sets of wards. Any ideas on how you want to get around them?"

"Killing Curse?"

Harry turned towards Sirius scratching his head. "Let's try this again. Any ideas on how we can get past the wards without setting them off?"

"Alright fine," Sirius grumbled and cast a spell over his eyes. "The first ward is line-based and it appears to be… muggle-repelling and a wizard detection, right?"

Harry was impressed and it showed on his face.

"I know a thing or two," Sirius said pretending to be offended. "I wouldn't have suggested this if I didn't think we might pull it off."

"I'm just surprised you even know the difference between a line-based ward and an area ward."

"I've cast a few different area wards over the Slytherin table and hallway in my day," Sirius explained while experimenting on the ward. "I'm stronger than Moony, and Prongs has always been a bit… accident prone. That's why back in the day, the bigger wards were almost all my work."

"And Wormtail?"

"Wormtail," Sirius bit the inside of his cheek. "He used to be a good lookout. Ah-ha! That's it. You took your potion?"

Harry nodded.

Sirius focused on a simple fuzzy tennis ball and transfigured Harry, and all the things on his person, into the singular small inanimate object. With a pop he transformed into a large black dog. He picked up the tennis ball in his mouth and calmly walked across the first ward set protecting the Potters' home.

He set the tennis ball down and with a pop transformed back into the healthy adult wizard. He sent the transfiguration reversal at the tennis ball, revealing a surprised Harry.

"I was conscious through that," Harry exclaimed in surprise.

"Yeah," Sirius nodded. "Have you never used a Norton's Brew?"

Harry shook his head.

"Oh they're great," Sirius explained. "I'm sure you know most of the common effects, but essentially it just makes your body far more receptive to magic. Spells cast on you are far more effective, especially if you're helping them along."

"All spells?"

Sirius shrugged. "Just about. So be careful, pain spells are all magnified. With the boosted effect on you from the Norton's, as long as I'm casting it and I want you to keep your mind, if you're fully accepting the spell, then it leaves you conscious. We've used that for spying before, but you can't stay that way for too long."

"So to get past the barrier ward, you turned me into an inanimate object and you into a dog. Neither effected by muggle repelling, nor detected as a wizard," Harry said, looking at the ward they had passed through. "You're not too bad at this."

"Why don't you start pulling your weight and get us through the second one?"

"Fair enough," Harry grinned, stepping up to inspect the ward. It was much thicker than the first and Harry could see it was a compound ward. "Here goes nothing."

Harry located the anchor stone and sent a feedback loop into two different parts of the ward. The visible domes of magic expanded and brightened.

Sirius took a step back as everything brightened. "Did you just strengthen those?"

"Yeah, I suppose I did, but this set is a compound ward. I was trying to separate the parts so we could identify them all and deal with them in smaller groups."

"Go Harry," Sirius grinned. "I think you know more about wards than I do."

"Area wards for apparition and portkey," Harry announced. "It's possible we're keyed considering our counterparts but for now we're just going to ignore those. It's this barrier ward for dark magic that may be a problem." Harry dropped to a knee and took a deep breath. "In case, I get dizzy."

Harry sent a spell down a magical arm and into the anchor stone. A large dark purple box flared brightly revealing the walls went dozens of feet up capped by a ceiling at the top, but only a couple feet into the ground.

Harry stood up and let out his breath. "Lovely. I bet it's for keeping out Death Eaters, but a lot of times my scar will set these types off."

"Considering our intentions any sort of emotional detection could pick up on that too," Sirius mused. "Think we can overpower it enough to jump through?"

"Yeah, but let's not," Harry said. "You see those dark wards in the inner set?"

Sirius nodded.

"Those are goblin wards," Harry explained. "All these others are just defensive and alert-oriented. Goblin wards are completely different, and most of the time very nasty. We're going to need our strength for overpowering those."

"You can't get past them?"

"I don't know, that's the thing," Harry said with a shrug. "We could be able to safely walk past them without ever triggering, or we could walk through them and they choose to kill us in a very messy manner."

"Overpowering that one sounds good to me," Sirius said. "So how do we get past this purple one?"

"It'd definitely detect magic so transfiguring ourselves won't work nor would the doggy side of you," Harry explained. "It's only a little bit into the ground, so how about a ward push?"

Sirius shook his head. "Never heard of it. Sounds good though."

"I'm basically just trying to lift the edge and we'll sneak in under it," Harry said summoning a couple of twigs. He cast a basic barrier ward tying its ends to the sticks. Using a pair of his magical arms, he was pushing his makeshift barrier ward up against the large purple walls.

Sirius watched as it slowly rose out of the ground until the two sticks finally got directly underneath the wall.

Harry was sweating and pulling up the edge of the thick ward set. It was arching around the edges of his barrier, straining against the invading ward. "There," Harry whispered in between breaths. "That's as high as I'm going to push it. You've got to stay low."

Sirius dropped to his knees and saw he'd still need to crouch to get under it. He turned back at Harry before crawling, "Are you gonna be okay?"

Harry nodded. "It's not magically tiring, just physically. Go."

Sirius hurried and crawled through. He stood up on the other side, looking through the translucent purple wall. He watched as Harry dropped to his knees and proceeded to crawl underneath while the ward set appeared to be getting heavier. Sirius grabbed a hold of his godson's arm and pulled him through and to his feet.

Harry accepted the help and let his simple barrier ward collapse, the two twigs falling to the ground lifelessly as the purple box flared angrily snapping back into position. "Thanks."

"When did you get so good at wards?"

"Horcrux hunting," Harry explained as they walked towards the final inner set of wards bearing all the brown murky signs of goblin magic. "Voldemort put a fair amount of effort into protecting his little toys with lots of devious and dangerous traps. Hermione and I both were quick learners out of necessity."

"You hunted for his toys?"

"By toys, I was referring to the pieces of his soul that he'd split off, and whose continued existence meant for all intents and purposes he was immortal."

"Oh… those toys."

"Yup," Harry said. "Have you ever tried to flood a goblin ward?"

Sirius shook his head.

"Me neither," Harry admitted. "And something tells me, it's going to be pretty tiring. Did you pack some pepper-up?"

"I got one," Sirius said. "You going to need it?"

Harry shook his head. "I brought four of them."

"Four! That'd kill you."

"Probably, yeah. I took three doses once over the course of about an hour and a half. Woke up eight days later with a muggle catheter in me. Madame Pomfrey was trying to discourage me from getting hurt so frequently. Needless to say, I'll never do that again. I brought two doses for each of us, in case you forgot."

Sirius checked his watch. "Twenty minutes. Forty left. How are we going to overpower this one?"

"You know how to share your power with me?"

Sirius nodded. "You've got the Norton's Brew in you though, so you gotta be careful you don't drain me completely dry. With the Norton's, you'll be able to sap unconsciously."

Harry nodded and connected with the nearest goblin keystone. "Anytime."

Sirius cast a pooling spell and felt Harry start to drain magic from him.

Harry was feeding as much as he could smoothly straight into the keystone. The wards were sharpening in focus and flashing white. "Alright, it's starting to flood it. We need to jump through during one of the white flashes. It may… feel funny."

Sirius nodded and saw the flashes were steadily increasing and lasting longer each time the white appeared. He glanced over at Harry and received a nod in return.

The very next flash, Sirius lunged forward and hopped through the visible white energy barrier. His senses all flared and it felt as if he were being electrocuted for a split second.

Harry jumped through on the very next flash.

Slowly Sirius felt his magic replenishing as Harry stopped drawing from him. He let the pooling spell dissipate and drank the pepper-up he'd brought with him.

Harry downed a vial after seeing Sirius drink his. "You alright?"

Sirius nodded. "That wasn't too bad."

Harry's attention was drawn to the left side of the modest-sized cottage. "What's that?"

Sirius shook his head. "No idea, but whatever's in there is warded pretty tightly."

Harry glanced back at the manor and then the glowing warded and obscured area. "Want to peek?"

Sirius nodded and began to hike towards the wards at the edge of the woods. As he got closer he saw brown intermixed with yellow wards. "Those look like goblin wards from here."

"Yup," Harry agreed. "Looks like it's got some newer strengthening charms that get regular maintenance."

"We going to overpower this one too?"

Harry shook his head. "We just need past the obscuring field so we can see what's in there. We don't have to actually cross the rest of the wards."

Harry located the anchor and felt his way around it, identifying the obscuring spell. He looped the connection back into itself and the obscured area darkened and shrunk slightly. "Whoops, wrong way."

Sirius just watched Harry staring down at the magical anchor stone. Harry flipped the two ends of the loop around and the obscuring ward lightened to a cool grey, expanding outward just a few inches more than the other wards anchored with it.

"Careful you don't cross the other wards, but we can stick our heads through the first ward safely," Harry said before thrusting forward through the grey barrier. "Whoa."

Sirius followed Harry's lead, and just leant his upper body through the ward. "Gulping gargoyles! What the hell happened here?"

Blackened scorched ground that was still steaming surrounded a tree so dead and hollow, it looked like a skeleton. Dry branches snaked upwards, swirling counter-clockwise from the bone white barbed trunk.

Harry was staring at the ground just in front of the tree from which all this death seemed to spread. The wound on the ground was practically screaming ancient magic. Harry turned towards Sirius. "I think I might know what this is."

Sirius shook his head, realizing he'd been entranced just looking at the decaying soil and tree. "What?"

"I think this may be where I died."

Sirius agreed only briefly before indignantly arguing, "Why's it gotta be where you died? Why couldn't it be like this because this is where I died?"

Harry leaned back away from the ward and patted Sirius on the top of the head. "I suppose anything's possible."

"You were a baby and apparently not the one in the prophecy," Sirius argued, sticking his head back in the ward to look at the small piece of desolation. "This is obviously the death of a far more promising and powerful young man, who fought back valiantly."

"Oh really? No ancient archways of death you could've tripped and fallen into around here?"

"You'd better hope not," Sirius joked back. "You've tripped and fallen into just as many."

"Seen enough?" Harry asked pointing towards the warded area.

Sirius nodded. "Yeah. Let's get my wand and out of here before they get back."

Harry removed the loop from the anchor stone and the obscuring ward darkened and shrunk down to its normal size. He grabbed a twig off the ground and hurried after Sirius.

Sirius figured the front door might be protected from an unlocking charm, but doubted they'd bothered to ward the window. A whispered alohomora and Sirius was hopping through the frame and into the darkened living room.

"Sirius!" Harry whispered forcefully. "At least disillusion yourself in case there are portraits."

"Good point," Sirius agreed and tapped the top of his head, casting the spell. "If things are like I remember, then the only wizarding portrait is an old Great Uncle in the dining room, who watches the floo and delivers messages."

Harry had already disillusioned himself as he too climbed up into the living room. "Where are we going?"

"There's a safe in the floor of James' study," Sirius said as he crept towards the stairs.

"Wut choo doin' here, boy?" A frightened little female house elf squeaked loudly.

"Crap," Sirius blurted out immediately.

"How'd choo get in here?" The elf demanded, shaking her little finger and holding herself with a bit more confidence.

Harry knew the elf could pop out of the way of any spell it saw coming. Knowing the easy solution, he snaked an invisible arm around behind the elf, stunning her before she even took notice of the magic in the air.

"Sirius? How many house elves do they have?"

"Just the one," Sirius weakly answered. "Suppose I should have mentioned her earlier."

"That would've required remembering her before, and that appears to be asking too much."

"Nuts," Sirius said looking at the elf. "I don't suppose you know how to memory charm a house elf."

Harry smirked at Sirius.

"You do know how to memory charm a house elf!"

Harry stunned the elf again for good measure. "It's not that different from memory charming anyone else, but we should keep her stunned for now and obliviate her before we leave. You sure there aren't any other surprises you've neglected to mention?"

"Moony said they bought the elf when Lily was pregnant with James Jr. and Sarah was still in diapers. Forgive me for not remembering an elf I'd never met."

Harry followed quickly behind the disillusioned form of his godfather. The magical sight spell made him easy to follow and they arrived in the study of James Potter. Harry laid the unconscious house elf onto the couch while Sirius unrolled the rug covering the floor. A large stone square lay flush with the hardwood floors. This was the magical safe.

There was no visible door, nor any handle, knob, or settings at all. Just the Potter Family crest was carved in relief onto the stone.

Harry look at the solid stone block. "You do know I've never seen this before and have no clue how to open it."

Sirius realized he'd been staring at Harry and waiting on him. "Sorry. You can try just sticking your hand on the crest, but you may need a drop of blood."

Harry placed his hand over the crest and pushed down. He knocked on it, and it felt like solid stone. He used his new ash wand with a unicorn hair and pricked his finger, letting a couple drops fall onto the shield in the Potter crest.

Harry saw nothing happening and looked up at Sirius. "Did I just cut myself for no reason?"

Sirius sighed. "Muggleborns." Sirius raised a hand before Harry could retort. "I know. You're not. But you might as well be. Try putting your hand on it now."

Harry placed his hand over the crest and looked back at his godfather. "Great. Now I'm getting blood all over my hand."

Sirius was looking at magical safe accusingly. "That should have opened it."

"Well it didn't."

"Have you even asked it to open?"

A soft rustle of air blew out as the stone surface dissolved revealing a compartment far larger than possible without magic.

"Oh," Harry said in lieu of an apology.

"Merlin there's a lot of crap in here," Sirius said peering into the safe.

"Accio wand," Harry incanted. A twelve inch driftwood wand came zooming out from the underneath a couple old tapestries.

Sirius lunged forward and grabbed the wand he'd missed so much. Just like the time he first purchased it at Ollivander's, silver sparks and a black mist slowly emitted out from the driftwood wand tip. "That's the stuff."

Harry was looking at Sirius' wand closely and began to transfigure the stick he'd brought with him. He lightened the wood tone, shaped it to resemble the wand, and coated it with a thin layer of lacquer. "Think this'll pass for it?"

Sirius held his wand up next to it. "Nice work."

"We don't want to advertise the fact that anything is missing," Harry explained as he began to push the fake replacement wand further down into the safe. He repositioned the tapestries to cover up the duplicate. "Shall we go?"

Sirius nodded when he saw Harry frowning at him. "What?"

"How do we close the safe?"

"Same way you open it." Sirius answered without pause.

Harry scrunched his face in concentration. He exhaled tiredly. "I'm asking it to close. I'm ordering it to close. I'm willing it to close. It's not closing."

Sirius frowned. "Maybe you need to bleed on it again."

"Bleed on what exactly?"

"Oh," Sirius said looking into the lidless block turned magical safe.

Harry just stared at Sirius silently. After ten quiet seconds Harry suggested, "Maybe it's just a time delayed thing and it'll close on its own."

Sirius stood there silently for a moment waiting on a bright idea to strike or for the safe to miraculously close. When it seemed neither was going to happen, he said, "I'm sure that's it. Just needs time."

The pair of them stared at the safe for another minute in silence.

"You're sure you-"

"I'm still ordering it to close right now."

Sirius glanced at his watch. "We're already going to be pushing it time-wise." He swished around his new wand and directed it at the rolled up rug. The rug unfurled and covered up the still wide open magical safe. "Why don't you obliviate the elf. We've got to work our way back through the wards."

"I was thinking about that," Harry said moving over towards the unconscious house elf. "Most homes don't have any restrictions on the outgoing floo, only on the incoming. I say we sneak past the portrait and just floo somewhere public."

Sirius was getting a headache keeping this magical sight spell on. He just nodded, looking forward to canceling the disillusionment and oculamagi spell. "Works for me."

Harry left the elf with the memories it expected to have this evening. Only that it had done some work and that there were no visitors.

The two Lord Blacks, disillusioned and silenced, crept into the dining room and saw the portrait was audibly snoring. Harry cast a slight obscuration charm in front of the portrait to keep it from waking up and spotting any flashes from the fireplace.

Sirius went first and Harry sent a finishing spell at the obscuration charm, moments before the floo took him as well.

The pair landed disillusioned and covered in soot at the Leaky Cauldron. One pop right after the other and they both had apparated back to Grimmauld Place.

Sirius let out a tired breath and collapsed onto the couch after vanishing the dust from his robes. "That… was fun."

"If there is no other business to discuss," Albus said. "I think that shall conclude this evening's meeting. James, Remus, Tonks? Would you mind staying for a moment?"

All four Potters and both Lupins had not even got up when the other Order members began to trickle out of the meeting hall.

"I wondered if perhaps there was anything more you'd like to share about the Lords Black that you might not have wanted all the other ears to hear."

"Stuffy, arrogant purebloods. What's there to say?" James snidely remarked.

"Their politics could work to our advantage," Albus explained. "Since they carry the title of Lord they can reassign their representatives to themselves or others."

"Their politics?" Tonks asked slightly uncomfortable at the idea of political power in those particular hands.

"The Black family has a seat on the Wizengamot and the Hogwarts Board of Governors," Albus explained. "The other thing I didn't want to bother too many people with was a curious meeting with Mr. Ollivander."

James suddenly jumped to his feet in surprise. He turned towards Albus and frowned. "Excuse me, Albus. It appears someone just exited via the floo at our place. Lily, you stay here until I get back."

Albus looked thoughtful. "Would you like my assistance?"

James shook his head. "It's probably just someone got lost and left right away."

"We'll go with you," Remus said as Tonks stood next to him.

James nodded, mentally choosing to portkey to his bedroom rather than use the floo. "I'm sure it's nothing. Grab on."

Remus and Tonks shared a glance and put their hands on James as he activated his portkey.

"There was no one here when we left," James explained in whispers while immediately checking his bedroom for signs of intrusion. "And the wards never detected anyone breaking in, only that the floo was triggered outbound. Two times in a matter of seconds."

He led the way out of his bedroom creeping through the eerily quiet home. The three of them worked in formation with James in the lead. He was repeatedly casting diagnostic spells that would sense other people even by heat signatures, and was searching for any new magic.

They'd worked their way to the fireplace in the dining room without incident. James looked around and saw absolutely nothing out of the ordinary. He relaxed finally and loosened the grip on his wand. "Whoever it was didn't seem to do anything and are gone now. See if you guys can find anything. I'm going to check out the ward anchors."

Remus nodded solemnly at James and went to check on Peter Potter, the snoozing portrait there in the dining room. He heard James exit out the back door to check out the wards and turned to see his daughter fighting a chuckle.

"I can't believe those buggers would do this," Remus cursed. "And stop finding this funny."

"What do you think they did?" Tonks asked amusement clear in her expression.

"I've no idea. That couch leech is childish enough to go to a lot of effort for some elaborate prank, but even he should know better than break into the bloody Assistant Director's home with a bloody Dark Lord on the loose," Remus snapped. "James and Lily are going to be worried sick for no good reason."

"Well let's allay their worries then," Tonks said, mocking her adoptive father. She knew she was keyed in and grabbed a handful of floo powder. She chucked it in, and said, "Lupin's Loft." As the floo began to activate she let herself get just barely sucked in and apparated right back to the Potters' dining room.

A split second later, another pop sounded James' sudden arrival.

"Did you just…?"

Tonks raised her hand. "That was me, playing with it. Considering nothing seems damaged, missing, or cursed I'm guessing you might have a loose connection or maybe a couple of the Mikes are doing some maintenance on the floo system close enough to trigger your sensors. If I were you, I'd think about changing your address in the off-chance it was bad guys testing your wards. Sounds like they held up though, right?"

"The wards are all up and functioning. They look to be as strong as they've ever been in decades." James nodded in agreement. "Yeah, you're probably right. I'll go get Lily and the kids. Let them know it was a false alarm."

James activated his portkey to the Order headquarters leaving the two Lupins alone again.

"That was well done," Remus said smiling at his daughter.

"I was raised a Marauder," Tonks said with her chin held high. "You always must be ready to lie and cover for your mates, even if it means pretending to have testicular cancer."

Remus had not heard this one and raised a curious eyebrow.

"Some people will believe anything you tell them about a metamorphmagus."

James Jr., followed by his mother and then father all came exiting out the floo.

"Hiya Uncle Moony," James Jr. greeted just as the grandfather clock in the living room chimed the hour. "Oh crap. I gotta hurry." He ran up the stairs towards his bedroom while both of his parents chuckled at his antics.

"Thanks guys," Lily said squeezing Tonks' hand. "Have you eaten? There should be a few slices of cobbler left."

"Peach?" Tonks asked hopefully.

"Blackberry."

"Ooh," Tonks exhaled happily. "Even better."

Remus grinned. "Well, if you're twisting my arm."

"Nappy!" Lily firmly called out.

With a pop, the Potter family house elf appeared. "Yes'm, Miss Lily?"

"Nappy!" James blurted out having forgotten about her.

"Massa?" Nappy said turning towards James.

"Did you see anyone tonight? Or hear them?" James inquired having completely overlooked the sentient being that had been at home.

"No sir," Nappy said shaking her head. "Iza jus' been doin' my cleanin', Massa. I din't hear nuffin'."

James felt a little more secure already. "No one in the dining room or using the floo?"

"No sir," Nappy assured him with smile. She was rubbing her chin in thought. "But Iza been a singin' and a hummin' while Iza workin'. Miss Lily said I could do dat."

"You have such a beautiful singing voice, Nappy," Lily assured the diminutive creature. She recalled the reason she'd first summoned the elf. "I just wanted to make sure we had some cobbler left."

"Blackberry, yes'm. Would choo like me to get choo fo' slices?"

"No thank you, Nappy," Lily said with a smile. "We'll help ourselves."

"Iza gonna clean out the fireplace now then," Nappy said waddling her way over towards the hearth.

The group of four thanked the small elf and went to the kitchen for some dessert. Remus was at the rear of the group and saw Nappy had grabbed her little house-elf sized mop and was pushing it back and forth, singing quietly to herself.

"Day after day, workin' fo' Massa, Massa gonna sell me 'less I start workin' fassa, oh day after day, workin' fo' Massa…" her little voice trailed off as Remus entered the kitchen thinking Nappy was almost as odd as Kreacher.

They finished off the rest of the cobbler and chatted amiably for over half an hour. Remus and Tonks bid them good night and apparated away rather than to dirty the sparkling clean fireplace.

James was thinking about all the paperwork he still had to finish on the two new ancient Lords. He was brought out of his musings when he stepped into the middle of the rug in his study. He and the rug had slowly sunk all the way up to his waist into the Potter magical safe.

"What the hell?"

"The adrenaline, the excitement, the lightheaded feeling you get when you finally turn off your magical sight spell," Sirius argued in between the last bites of his supper. "Admit it, Harry. That was fun."

Harry couldn't have stopped the smile from splitting across his face. "Maybe a little."

"A little schmittle," Sirius waved off Harry's understatement. "You know more than me about that stuff, but we make a good team. What say we hit a wizarding bar and pick us up a couple of wenches?"

"Why are you in such a hurry?" Harry argued sitting back patting his full belly after their large meal.

"Unless someone already has their eye on something," Sirius said before turning to look around the various tables in Diego's. He turned back towards his godson.

Harry nodded over Sirius' left shoulder. "Dark hair over there I've caught staring this way twice already. Not sure about the ogre she's with."

Sirius glanced over his shoulder and had to stifle a snort. The ogre in question just caught the raven-haired woman smiling at Harry and grabbed her to get up and leave.

"Damn," Harry said softly as the attractive woman was side-along apparated away.

"Harry, do you really not know who that was?"

Harry shook his head.

"That ogre, as you call him, was Stephen Parkinson, or Baron Parkinson in most circles."

"That was Parkinson?" Harry asked having never met the man in his dimension, and only knew he had been friends with Malfoy. "Blimey. I didn't know Pansy had a hot older sister."

"She may not," Sirius chuckled. "That was Pansy's hot older Mum."

Harry's eyes widened. A devious glimmer appeared in his eyes. "Parkinson's a Death Eater, right?"

Sirius shrugged. "Don't know for sure, but he definitely associates with the type. Was he one in our old dimension?"

Harry noticed Sirius had readily accepted this as their new dimension, not a new dimension. "To be honest… I don't know. Never met him, but I'd always pretty much assumed." Harry was obviously deep in thought as his eyes kept twinkling despite the dangerous smile on his face.

"Alright, what's that look mean?"

Harry acted completely innocent. "What look?"

"That look," Sirius insisted pointing at Harry. "The one that says you're up to something."

Harry shrugged nonchalantly. "I was just thinking about how we've got to pay that 134 galleon overdue notice before they'll reconnect our floo. And then I was thinking about tonight. You're right. We do make a good team. And it was definitely fun."

Sirius narrowed his eyes. "What are you up to?"

Harry glanced around the restaurant ensuring no one was paying them either too much or too little attention. "What would you think about maybe doing something like tonight… again?"

Sirius furrowed his brow. "You want to steal from Prongs some more? I know a thing or two about tempting fate and that's just not a particularly bright idea."

Harry shook his head slowly, urging Sirius to catch his meaning. "Not from Prongs."

Sirius took a moment to process what Harry was implying when his eyes widened in hope. "Don't you tease me about this."

"We could use the money."

"Harry, you better not be playing with me."

"We've got a little leeway thanks to our ass-backwards noble status."

"I swear to Merlin, if you're suggesting what I think you are, the answer is yes, yes, a million times yes."

"Not just anyone," Harry insisted determinedly as he leaned forward. "Death Eaters."

Sirius glanced over his shoulder where Parkinson had formerly been. "I love you Harry, I really do."

"I mean once we've confirmed they are in fact Death Eaters," Harry rationalized aloud. "It's kinda like we'd be doing a public service, right?"

Sirius couldn't help it and sniffled as he turned away in joy. "Damn bug just flew in my eye."

Chapter 10

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Another chapter for your reading and reviewing pleasure. Thanks for all the reviews and keep the feedback coming.

The two Blacks and two Bones all exchanged looks. The guests looked mortified while the hosts were doing everything in their power not to laugh or give in to the temptation to high-five each other.

Sirius caught Harry's eye and shrugged. "After your accusations of robbing the cradle, can you blame me for shagging such a vivacious cougar?"

Harry winced and translated, "I'm sure that was meant as a compliment, Madame Bones."

Amelia had been taking it as a compliment until Harry had called her Madame and shattered her illusions that the cougar reference didn't have anything to do with her age. She addressed her niece. "This shouldn't be awkward, Susan. You're a grown woman."

"You don't have to tell me twice," Harry agreed before he could stop himself. "Sorry. My mind's been in the gutter since Susan asked for my pants sausage."

"Harry!" Susan exclaimed while checking out Sirius and resisting the impulse to flash her auntie a big thumbs up.

"See? I did it again." Harry said happily.

Amelia found herself fighting a smile. "You did that on purpose, Lord Black."

"Please, call me Harry."

"Amy is fine casually, Harry, but if I ever find out you hurt Susan, I'd prefer that you remember me as the Director of Magical Law Enforcement," she said while calmly flipping through the Daily Prophet. She saw Harry was hesitant to respond. "What is it?"

"Amy, I, umm…" Harry kept his eyes pointed upward. "Susan, you want to tackle this one?"

"Your boobs are coming out, Auntie."

"You don't have to tell me twice," Sirius exclaimed sitting down at the table while Amelia hastily covered up.

The four proceeded to have stilted conversation, awkward silences, and mocking playful barbs back and forth. It started when Sirius passed on the juice and exclaimed he was suddenly in the mood for milk. Amelia then got a cup of coffee and when asked how she took her coffee replied anything but black. Because apparently she tried black and found it unsatisfactory. Harry then passed his eggs and bacon to Sirius deciding it felt like a fresh melon kind of morning. Susan took a second helping of sausage because sometimes one just isn't enough.

Sirius tried a bite of Harry's melon and indicated it was too ripe for him. He claimed he didn't like his melon so freshly plucked, preferring it a bit aged, once it's softer and more flavorful. This was when the tension broke due to the fact that Sirius' mouth was a step ahead of his brain and he kept using the word breast instead of melon among others.

Amelia couldn't take it when Sirius asked her to pass the bacon and the penis.

A couple of frenzied, goodbye shags later and the two Lord Blacks were alone at Grimmauld Place. Harry was giving Sirius an earful in the muggle room.

"What were you thinking?"

Sirius shrugged.

"Padfoot! We have lots of stolen goods, including talkative portraits bound to their frames. And you invited the Director of Magical Law Enforcement to spend the night."

"Well you invited her niece."

"Who was a classmate of mine and isn't responsible for arresting us."

"A classmate?" Sirius grinned. "Did you and her ever…?"

"In the old world?" Harry said. "Nope. I never really had the opportunity as she got killed about a year after her aunt, who incidentally got killed about a month after you."

"But you wanted to, with her, right?"

Harry smiled as he fondly recalled, "She was the first girl in my school year."

"The first what?"

"The first girl to sprout," Harry took a deep breath and proudly finished, "jubblies."

"Sarah Morales," Sirius replied instinctively. "She was the first in my year. You never forget your first."

"So in answer to your question, yes," Harry agreed. "I had a bit of a crush on Susan. There were four or five girls in the DA that I may have been watching a bit closer than the other kids. She was definitely one of them."

"Was Ginny one of them?"

"Ginny was a friend I was watching close anyway. But that reminds me," Harry said turning towards Sirius. "Just this morning I was able to shove Ginny's head through the mattress. It was kinda moist and cold but she was solid to me."

"Further proof we're meant to be together," Ginny said appearing just behind Harry.

"Really?" Harry said turning to her. "And here I thought it was so that I could actually smack you all those times I wanted to smack you."

Ginny floated through the couch and rested herself as if she were leaning on Harry's shoulder. "Our little tiffs just make making up that much more fun."

Harry was trying to poke and push Ginny but his hand just passed straight through as normal. "How'd I do that earlier?"

Ginny shrugged. "Accidental necromancy?"

"There's no such thing as accidental necromancy," Harry grumbled. "Don't be ridiculous."

"Says the Soul-Mate-Who-Lived," Sirius added with a grin.

Harry stood up from the couch and grumbled. "I'm going to take a shower. Try not to seduce any high ranking law enforcement officials while I'm gone."

Ginny stayed there on the couch as Harry walked back towards his room. She grinned at Sirius. "He just needs to wash all that Susan off of him."

"I've not seen you in a while Ginny," Sirius replied settling down in the recliner across from her. "Last time we talked you promised me a good story."

"Right," Ginny said shifting her body to lie down on the couch. "A good story. Anything in particular?"

Sirius shrugged. "I remember you mentioning something about a Dennis-slash-Denise?"

"Oh! That is a good story," Ginny smiled thinking back to that day. "This was after Voldemort was killed. Harry had been trying to recreate some of the magic in the Exit and sort of unmade all of his loose ward stones from existence. So he went to Diagon Alley to pick up a bunch of new ward stones and was coming back through the Leaky Cauldron.

"He walked in through the back door and headed for the muggle side when a woman got up from the bar and stood in front of him blocking his path. She leant forward and whispered into his ear that she wanted to ravish him, right now."

Ginny snickered. "Harry examined this dark-haired smoldering woman who he didn't know, realized she was practically in heat, and quickly agreed. She suggested his place, but Harry said no. He turned right around and got a room from Tom there in the Leaky Cauldron."

Ginny repositioned herself and continued. "Those two went at each other like Pureblood Princess Parpie and her betrothed Heir Cleangood, if you know what I mean. Forty-five wet, sticky minutes later they were both exhausted and just lying there on the bed. You know that sweaty time afterwards, where you keep your distance and cool off. Well the woman still hadn't given her name, but it was clear she recognized who Harry was. So while they're just lying there, the alarm on her watch starts beeping and they turn to each other."

"The look of horror on Harry's face was priceless," Ginny preempted. "Because when that watch beeped, it signified it had been an hour and Dennis Creevey's polyjuice was wearing off."

Sirius was quickly cataloging all the different ways to eternally mock Harry for this.

"But even funnier," Ginny said through laughter, "was the look of horror on Dennis' face when Harry Potter didn't turn into his boyfriend Terry Boot."

"I got the whole story from Dennis later on because all he could do right then was to keep apologizing over and over to Harry. Now stick with me on this tale," Ginny assured him, "because it gets even better."

Sirius briefly considered taking notes.

"So what happened was that Dennis and Terry were looking to spice up their relationship and managed to buy a few Harry Potter hairs off the black market. They were actually at the Leaky Cauldron to do a little role-playing. They went into separate bathrooms and while Terry drank a glass of Harry-juice, Dennis downed a glass of a woman who was supposed to be a surprise to Terry."

"Unfortunately when Terry chugged his brew, he turned into a Harry Potter that was lacking a lightning bolt scar. That's why it took him a couple minutes longer in the bathroom. And while Dennis, polyjuiced to look like the waitress who took their picture on their first date, was waiting at the bar, the real Harry Potter just happened to walk in."

"A couple minutes later while Dennis and Harry are putting up silencing charms in the room they rented, Terry has put the finishing touches on a glamour charmed scar for his forehead and is walking out of the bathroom. He looked towards the bar and didn't see any woman who caught his eye. But wouldn't you know it, right then, Terry's aunt walked into the Leaky Cauldron."

"Oh sweet Merlin," Sirius gasped.

Ginny was giggling happily. "Terry, who everyone can plainly see is Harry Potter, walked right up to the woman he assumed was Dennis and said he wanted to ravish her, right then. She didn't want to go back to her place, so Terry went up to Tom and asked for a room. From what I'm told Tom was very impressed and rented 'Harry' another room, just a minute or two after the first one."

"Less than an hour later, Terry's aunt had fallen asleep with the widest, most content smile on her face. Terry's polyjuice then wore off and when his aunt, stayed his aunt, he flipped out. He grabbed all of his stuff and ran out of the room.

"Right in the hallway, Terry's there with his clothes in his arms and he sees Dennis come sprinting out of the room next door. They look at each other and shriek at the same time: I had sex with my aunt! I had sex with Harry Potter!

"Terry and Dennis agreed to never play polyjuice games again," Ginny finished gleefully. "And not two days later, the Quibbler ran a special front page article written by Betty Boot entitled Harry Potter: Greatest Lover Ever. There were enough juicy details to sell-out three re-printings of that issue."

"That could only happen to Harry," Sirius said shaking his head. "But what I don't get is if Dennis and Terry wanted to pretend with Harry polyjuice, why'd they have to complicate things?"

Ginny smiled brightly. "Actually it was at Dennis' insistence. Because, and I quote, 'Harry Potter is the antithesis of gay. He practically oozes heterosexuality.' Which, considering Dennis is the one who had sex with him, is especially ironic."

"I think I've autographed that issue more than the one proclaiming Voldemort's defeat," Harry said from the doorway. He was only wearing flannel pajama bottoms and was towel drying his hair.

Sirius didn't even know where to start rubbing this one in Harry's face. "So is this the real reason you wanted to live with me when you were thirteen? To take advantage of my sexy prison-fed body?"

There was a knock at the front door and Harry turned to go answer it. He reminded Sirius, "Don't forget I can kick your ass."

Harry draped the towel around his neck and opened the front door. "Hello," Harry curiously greeted two people he was not expecting to see. "Can I help you?"

"Lord Black," Peter Potter greeted. "I was hoping to get some opinions on a few political issues, if you or the other Lord Black had any time to talk."

Harry stepped back inviting them in. "Ahh sure. And call me Harry."

"PJ," the Potter Lord reminded. "And this is my great nephew, James."

"Jimmy," Harry greeted shaking the hand of the little brother he never had. "I think that's what Tonks said she calls you when your Dad's not around."

"Can I just say that calling the Ministry a bunch of stupid muggles was beautiful," James Jr. cheered. "It made my week. I saw Weasleys' Wheezes already had some t-shirts for sale with quotes."

Peter put a calming hand on James' shoulder. "If this is a bad time, Harry, we can talk later. Perhaps we could buy you lunch. The other Lord Black too."

Harry looked down and saw he was shirtless. "Oh no it's fine. I just got out of the shower a couple minutes ago. My cloak's going to be soaking in potion for another hour or so. I'm in no hurry."

"Morning Harry," was the call coming from the kitchen.

"Tonks?" Harry asked back. "Is that you?"

"Err… I'm not interrupting you, am I?" Tonks asked quietly when shirtless Harry walked up to her.

"Naw, you're fine. Come on in," Harry smirked. "Say hi to the Potters."

"Oh boy," Tonks said as her eyes widened.

"Relax," Harry assured her. "Your boss isn't one of them."

Tonks looked over Harry's shoulder and to the front entryway. "Jimmy? What are you doing here?"

"Uncle PJ managed to convince Mum it'd be educational," James Jr. said, clearly indicating he couldn't care less if it was educational.

"Sirius," Harry yelled up the stairs. "Get down here and say hi to the Potters."

There was a brief pause before a voice yelled back, "What the hell is up with your luck today?"

Harry firmly believed fate was a fickle bitch just begging to be tempted and wisely said nothing. He turned towards Tonks, James Jr., and Lord Peter Potter and opened his mouth when there was a knock at the front door. "Excuse me," Harry said to them and carefully peered around the door. "Amy. Long time, no see."

"Don't you start with me, Harry," Amelia said as she moved forward to be let inside. "I got one Lord Black notch in my bedpost already this morning. I don't need another."

Harry didn't quite know what to say, as he was certain everyone behind him had heard her clearly. Harry moved out of the way, revealing Peter Potter smiling brightly. Harry's eyes glimmered in amusement. "Come on in, Amy."

Amelia Bones realized it was not just Harry present, but in fact Lord Potter, her Assistant Director's son, and Auror Tonks were all staring at her with grins. Amelia looked resigned as she smiled weakly back. "Oh this is fantastic. Actually, I think I'm beyond caring right now." Amelia just walked past the four others with her head held high. "If you'll excuse me, I need to go find my bra."

"It's okay, Amy," Sirius said from the top of the stairs. "Kreacher!"

The elf appeared as called.

"Madame Bones is looking for her-"

"I'll get it, Master," Kreacher replied, disappearing with a pop.

"I met you," James Jr. said as he recognized Sirius. "You're Lord Black?"

"I wasn't when we met," Sirius replied. "But I am now. PJ?"

Peter shook Sirius' hand and nodded. "I was hoping not to interrupt you guys, but it seems pretty busy around here."

Amelia found herself agreeing and asked, "What are you doing here, Auror Tonks?"

Tonks stopped smiling at the walk of shame and was reminded this scarlet woman was her boss. "I, kind of, ditched Harry last night. I wanted to apologize and find out how his evening went."

Amelia opened her mouth to respond when suddenly there was another knock at the front door. "Lovely."

"Excuse me," Harry said, turning back to answer the door. He once again slowly opened the door, identified the visitor, and greeted loudly, "Susan. Long time, no see."

"Listen Harry," Susan just started explaining. "I don't care if you did bite all the way through. Those are my lucky panties and I want them back."

"Come on in, Susan," Harry echoed his earlier words and moved out of the way to show five more people than she was expecting to see.

"Susan," Harry cleared his throat and introduced, "You remember Sirius, and this is Tonks, and Lord Potter, and Lord Potter's great nephew Jimmy, and of course-"

Susan reddened. "Hi Auntie."

"Good to see you again, Susan," Amelia grinned mirthlessly with a complexion almost as rosy.

"Not awkward at all, right?"

With a pop, Kreacher appeared with a bright blue lacy brassiere. "Your bra, Madame Bones."

Amelia proudly accepted her bra from the house elf. "This is exactly how I pictured my day was going to go."

Tonks smirked at Harry. "So your night, it went okay, it sounds like."

"Hello?" a voice called out, knocking on the open front door. "Anybody home?"

Peter was impressed his second encounter with the Lords Black was proving to be even more entertaining than the first. "James?"

The latest unexpected visitor stopped in surprise. "Uncle Peter?"

"Dad!" James Jr. greeted happily.

"Boss!" Tonks chimed in just because.

"Assistant Director Potter," Harry said evenly.

"You," Sirius greeted coolly.

"Oh stuff it, Sirius," Harry scolded and turned towards the front door. "Something I can help you with, Assistant Director?"

James saw his uncle was smiling brightly, his son was in good spirits, Tonks looked a bit nervous, and his boss was holding a bra and avoiding eye contact. "Have I come at a bad time?"

"Not particularly, no," Harry said before ordering, "Kreacher, fetch Susan's lucky panties please."

Susan just reddened furthered.

"Yes Master," the elf agreed, happy to be helping the pureblood women.

James looked at his uncle and son, asking, "Did you clear this with Lily?"

Peter and James Jr. nodded with certainty.

James glanced over all the faces again and decided to try and coax some information out of Sirius later. He was thinking perhaps when he wouldn't have his family and boss as an audience. "I'll come back some other time."

He turned to leave and was blinded by a sudden magical flash.

"Wait!" A voice from the front steps called out. "Don't waste film. That's not a Lord Black. That's just Potter, an auror."

"The press," Amelia announced, maintaining her unconvincing smile. "This is… this is great. You know, Sirius, you are quickly becoming the biggest mistake of my life that involved multiple orgasms."

"Auntie!" Susan eeped.

"Amelia!" James scolded. "My son is here!"

Tonks sucked in a breath knowing exactly how true that was.

"Lord Black!" A woman called out as she walked in, pushing past James Potter. "I was hoping to interview both or either Lord Black." She looked around the room at all the smiling faces while her photographer followed her in. "Have I come at a bad time?"

"Hello Rita, Bozo," Harry said through clenched teeth.

Rita Skeeter had just licked the tip of a quill and was surprised that not only was she recognized, but also her photographer. "Lord Black?"

Kreacher suddenly appeared with some shiny black torn material. "Your lucky panties, Miss Bones."

Another flash indicated a picture had been taken. Only instead of wasting film on an auror, this time Bozo managed a shot of a shirtless Harry standing by Susan Bones holding her torn black silk panties, while in the background Sirius stood by Amelia Bones holding her bright blue lacy bra.

"Okay, that's it," Harry said taking charge of the situation. "Rita, take your photographer and go before I let the Manor's magic decide what to do with you. Owl us questions or to ask for a time to meet and we'll answer. But never come here uninvited. Assistant Director Potter, I guess we'll see you some other time."

Having achieved a minor reduction in numbers, Harry turned back towards the Bones women. "Might I suggest a floo call in the future?"

Amelia and Susan bid the others goodbye and left through the Blacks' fireplace.

Peter saw Tonks, the two Lord Blacks. and his great nephew were all that remained. "Are your mornings typically this fun?"

"More often than you'd think," Tonks answered for them. "So you knuckleheads going to kick me out too?"

Harry shrugged and turned towards Lord Potter. "You're the one who wanted to talk politics. Any objections?"

"Please," Peter said, waving his hand. "Nothing so formal, anyone you'd like to join us is welcome. I was merely very intrigued after your unique introductions to the Wizengamot yesterday."

"Well I hate to disappoint you PJ," Sirius grinned. "But we're really not very intriguing. Shall we adjourn to the muggle room?"

Peter didn't move as he turned to Harry and warily asked, "You have a room you keep your muggles in?"

"Doesn't everyone?" Harry chuckled. "But that's not the room he's talking about. We just picked up a new muggle home entertainment center and Sirius likes to waste away in front of the telly." Harry noticed Tonks had run quickly after Sirius heading towards the warded room. "Tonks too."

Peter and James Jr. were both impressed by the setup and amused at the way Tonks and Sirius had already turned everything on, hypnotized by the screen.

Kreacher brought them all beverages while Lord Potter inquired about Sirius and Harry's opinions on a variety of issues. Peter informed them his older brother Chuck had married Dorea Black while Sirius and Harry deftly avoided questions about exactly which branch of the family they came from or how the two of them were related. When the conversation turned towards old family history, it was clear Sirius and Harry weren't particularly proud of the Black legacy. Peter recounted some of the more shameful aspects of the Potter line while Sirius named every old Black he could think of that was worthy of their respect.

Harry saw Tonks and James Jr. were as clueless as he was and asked, "You're pretty quiet there, Jimmy. Alright?"

James Jr. nodded. "I don't know much of the history of the Potters. And my Dad's not all that big on tradition or old family politics either, so Uncle PJ's been trying to teach me all the things he doesn't think my Dad will."

"Traditions were made to be broken," Harry said. "Or was that records?"

"I think you used that same argument about hymens the other day," Tonks interjected.

"Yes, well," Harry considered. "I think I tried it with the spirit of weak-willed morons too."

"Can I ask you something kinda personal, Harry?" James Jr. cautiously inquired.

Harry glanced at Tonks to see if she'd been giving anything away and answered. "Ask anything you want. No guarantees on whether I'll answer though."

James Jr. nodded immediately and saw his great uncle and Sirius were deep in conversation. "I can't help but notice you've got a few scars on your body. And I was curious where you got them."

Harry had forgotten he was shirtless still and looked at the scars on his arms and shoulder. "Yeah, the disfiguring ones you want to heal, but if they just look cool and have a decent story behind them, I'll wear 'em proudly. You want to trade some scar stories?"

"I don't know how much I've got to trade. Wait!" James Jr. pulled up his pant leg. "I got this one from when I flew into a tree but that's about it. And… well… I pretty much just told you the story."

"I've got a few," Tonks grinned, tilting her head and showing one she kept hidden on the back of her neck. "But I've been meaning to ask about that shoulder one you got Harry."

Harry looked over at his rough right shoulder and grinned. "You picked a fun one to start. That one's got a happier memory than some. Let's see… this was over a year ago. There's this magical school, a lot like Hogwarts, and the seventh years had a ditch day where a couple dozen of the most troublesome miscreants were all involved in a scavenger hunt. One of the tasks was to locate… someone and get them to do something on the list. A younger brother of a good friend of mine led two of his classmates to my place figuring I'd be good for their hunt. Well, I made them work for it, teasing them with opportunities to win a drink, and when they failed, I'd down the shot of firewhiskey."

"Oh this bodes well," Tonks grinned.

"My tolerance for alcohol wavers every once in a while and before I realized it, I was quite drunk with three kids your age," Harry continued remembering needing a pensieve the next morning to get answers. "Anyways, Hogwarts was a well-known school to those kids and somehow I came up with one of my less than brilliant ideas. I suppose I should add that when I get bored and drunk, my judgment may stray into unhealthy territory. I think I was dared but I might have dared myself, either way the point is, I wanted to test the Hogwarts motto."

"May stray into unhealthy territory?" Peter questioned with a smile, as he and Sirius had stopped to listen to Harry's tale.

"Refresh my memory please," Tonks asked. "Just what is the Hogwarts motto?"

"Draco dormiens nunquam titillandus," Harry answered just as assuredly as if Hermione was quizzing him.

"In English?"

"Never tickle a sleeping dragon." James Jr. was looking at Harry's shoulder reverently. "That's a dragon bite?"

"No, no, not a bite," Harry said running his fingers over the two valleys that had been gashes. "Just a little tail swipe."

"You took students with you to tickle a dragon?" Peter clarified warily.

Harry winced a little. "I was careful. I fitted them all with portkey trigger-buttons. If their thumb let up off the button, the portkey would've taken them away. And besides it was a mammoth old fat dragon anyway." Harry paused and saw that his precautions hadn't earned him any sympathy. "Or at least I'd thought it was."

"What was it?" James Jr. asked enthralled by the story.

"Well, I mean it looked like four rolls of belly fat underneath this snoozing overgrown lizard," Harry explained. "Until I actually flew up to it and began to tickle it. My blurry vision got a lot less blurry and it turned out the four rolls of belly fat were actually four little two meter baby dragons. And one large, perfectly fit, very angry mother dragon nursing.

"I flew out of there, dodging her fireblasts until one of the little guys bit down and managed to get a firm hold of my cape."

"Hang on," Sirius interrupted. " Cape?"

Harry nodded. "Well I looked silly with only a codpiece and a helmet on. The cape made all the difference."

Sirius saw everyone else looked as lost as him. "Continue."

"Anyways, it was the little bugger pulling me down off my broom, and angry mama dragon's tail just glanced off my shoulder sending my flailing into the tree. Before I could hit it, I triggered my own portkey, which triggered all three of the boys' portkeys too."

Harry smiled rubbing his shoulder again. "That's how I got a cool scar and that's how those kids won their scavenger hunt."

"Oh yeah?" Tonks smirked, up for a challenge. She showed off her right shin. "That's from a goblin's scimitar."

"You don't want to play this game with me," Harry argued. "You can cheat and make up all the ones you want. My truth is stranger than your fiction." Harry tapped his forehead, subtly indicating his unbeatable trump card in any game of scar one-upmanship.

Tonks didn't think that one should count. "I wouldn't cheat," Tonks said hefting her elbow in the air. " Griffin paw raked me, right here. What do you got?"

Harry jumped up and bent over, revealing a butt cheek. "Muggle shot me three times after a little dark artifact hunting accidentally burned down a thousand acres of cartel owned land."

"Muggles," Tonks mocked.

Harry showed her the back of his right arm and pointed to a centimeter sized ring. "Basilisk fang."

"There's no way that tiny thing is from a basilisk fang," Tonks insisted. "Unless it was about a half meter long and still teething."

Harry rolled his arm over showing the much larger scarred ring. "That side was the exit wound, and it was about twenty meters and several centuries old."

Peter's eyes widened knowing how poisonous the serpents were in addition to their fatal stare. "You should be dead."

Tonks gulped, misinterpreting his meaning.

Harry poked Tonks with an invisible arm and answered, "A phoenix cried several tears, healing it while I was dizzy from the poison."

"That's bloody awesome!" James Jr. cheered.

"Yeah," Harry agreed before pouting. "But I've still never even seen a nundu."

"I saw one," Tonks triumphantly announced. She weakly added, "Course it was in a cage." She deflated further. "And dying."

Harry looked at the others. "Anyone want to go for a nundu hunt?"

Peter saw how excited his great nephew was and wisely decided, "I think perhaps we've taken up enough of your time, Sirius, Harry."

"That's probably a good idea," Sirius said shaking Peter's hand again. "I may need to put Harry down for his nap."

"Sorry, Lord Potter," Harry formally apologized. "I can only stomach so many reminders of our nation's corrupt wizarding history before I want to go… well, tickle a sleeping dragon. It gives me fresh memories of how exciting and fun the magical world really is."

"No apology necessary, Lord Black," Peter assured him. "I may have had a few flings with a vampire princess in my youth as well."

"Uncle PJ!" James Jr. exclaimed in shock. He started to smile, "Got any pictures?"

Peter steered his great nephew away. "Good day, Lords Black, Miss Tonks-Lupin. We should do this again some time."

They had spent two long days scouting, planning, and settling on a course of action for their next job. The decision had been made and they'd already started the ball rolling with a hidden slow-acting ward-eater. Lord Simmons lived alone and was going to be out of the country for eight days. In Harry's estimation, the primary outer wards would be weak enough by the day after tomorrow to crumble without incident.

With all of their preliminary work done, the two Lord Blacks were wandering Diagon Alley, when they encountered a small but familiar establishment entitled Weasleys' Wizarding Wheezes.

Sirius smiled at the window display and walked in first. "How could you not want a custom charmed shirt to say Fuck you all very much? It's my new catchphrase!"

"I'm sorry, Sirius," Harry assured him while looking at the magic interwoven into the expensive t-shirt. He smiled to see 'and your mother twice' on the back of the shirt. "But you're far too old for a catchphrase."

"I am not," Sirius pouted. "You're just jealous my catchphrase is better than yours."

"I consider it my civic duty to piss you off is much too long for a catchphrase, but let's find out which one has been selling better." Harry took Sirius' shirt from him and they walked up to the counter where a Weasley twin was cashing out a customer and wearing a nametag that helpfully said, 'Weasley.'

After the customer finished, Harry and Sirius stepped up. Harry greeted, "Weasley?"

The man looked up as his twin came out from the back room with a sandwich in his hand. Recognition flashed in his eyes as he retorted, "Lord Black?"

"Weasley," Sirius greeted the other twin.

"Lord Black!"

"Weasley."

"Lord Black?"

"As much fun as it might be to continue, Fred, George, this is Sirius, and I'm Harry."

"It is indeed very serious," one of the twins agreed.

The other continued, "And I can recommend a good barber if you like." He closed an eye to examine Harry's unruly black hair. "Maybe some landscapers too."

"We have a question for you, Fred," Harry said looking at the twin manning the register.

"How'd you know I'm Fred?" He said with a frown.

Harry grinned. "I didn't because you're not. You're George, and I know that because you would never give up the opportunity to switch places so quickly as to admit to being Fred."

George turned towards Fred who was still eating his sandwich. "He's a slippery one alright."

Fred shrugged and swallowed the bite in his mouth. "Well we are selling shirts off of their quotes."

"And that's what we wanted to ask you about," Sirius jumped in. "Just how much better is Fuck you all very much selling versus that other one that's not really a catchphrase?"

"They're about even as most people buy both. Ten galleons for the pair, six galleons for just one," George answered. "You Lords here to demand a piece of the action?"

Sirius and Harry exchanged a glance and both shook their heads.

"I was wondering," Harry inquired. "Just what sort of magic is on them to justify the cost of six galleons at your limited time only sale price?"

"They're expensive because we had to create our own spell and security on them," Fred answered. "It's based off of muggle charms, where muggles look at magic buildings and see ruins. The spell makes it so people who'd get really offended by the words see only what they'd expect to see."

"Which is usually just a plain t-shirt," George added.

Sirius let out a low whistle. "That's a tasty piece of magic."

"They're not quite foolproof though," George answered pointing towards the front of the store.

A small girl was tugging on her mother's sleeve and asked, "Mummy? Why does that say…" The little girl pulled her mother closer and whispered in her ear.

"Well I never!" the mother huffed and grabbed her daughter leaving the store quickly.

Harry and Sirius turned back around to face the brightly smiling Weasley twins.

"You're obviously doing something right," Sirius grinned. "But with the ability to manufacture clothes like that in addition to all your other wheezes, I'd have thought you'd need a bigger store."

Fred smiled sadly. "Unfortunately we don't have the capital to expand and Gringotts' unsecured loan rates hover right around…"

"Your firstborn and your soul," George finished. "Why? Do the Lords Black have ten thousand galleons they want to loan us?"

Sirius and Harry looked at each other for a moment intermittently smiling and shrugging. Harry turned back, "Maybe."

Fred and George both stiffened and stood a little straighter. "Are you serious?"

Harry slapped a hand over Sirius' widely smiling mouth. "First thing is you never ask that question around this guy. And second…" Harry let go of Sirius' mouth and turned to him. "What's second?"

"Second," Sirius grinned. "I can assure you that we are at a minimum, half-serious."

Fred and George were smiling brightly at Sirius.

"Ah crap," Harry realized and grumbled. "I'm about to be outnumbered and he's got a new catchphrase."

"Give us a few days," George said. "We'll work up a proper business presentation and proposal for you."

"You don't have to do that," Harry said waving them off. "We wouldn't even appreciate a proper business presentation. Tell you what. Give him his t-shirt free, set me up with a few pairs of extendable ears, and we'll buy you guys drinks tonight. We can talk about it then."

"I'll warn you right now," Sirius jumped in. "I'm thinking more along the lines of an investment or partnership than a simple loan. We don't want to buy you out or force our opinions on you, but I think giving us a stake in helping your business to improve will benefit us both."

"The shirt's yours," George quickly agreed.

Fred added, "And I know where we can go and get the drinks for free."

The twins looked at each other and said in unison, "But what are extendable ears?"

Harry blinked having not even considered that they might not have been invented here. "Oops."

Sirius came to Harry's rescue and added, "We'll probably give you some invention ideas even if we don't reach an accord. Now where's this place with free drinks?"

Fred corrected, "They're not free for everybody, but if you're with us, you should be fine. We'll close up a little early and meet you at the Hog's Head in an hour?"

"It's in Hogsmeade," George clarified. "Near the edge of town."

"We know it. See you soon, gentlemen," Sirius agreed and steered Harry on out of the store.

The two men hadn't even gone thirty paces when they were interrupted by one of the slimiest sounding voices around.

"Well, well, well. If it isn't both the Lords Black," Lucius Malfoy drawled, while his wife just stood next to him with a stoic expression. "Two people claiming the same Lordship. That's a bastardization of magic and nobility not seen since the blood traitor to the Black name was… purified twenty-five years ago."

Sirius knew Lucius was just trying to get a rise out of them. "I'm sorry. Am I supposed to know you?"

"Hang on," Harry happily interrupted when Lucius was about to respond. "The over-compensating cane, the hair that has to look more feminine than his wife's, you know this guy. This is that registered sex offender the other Lords kept joking about, Shoeless Towel-boy or something like that."

Lucius was seething but kept up his mask of indifference. "You poor misguided plebeians. You don't have to hide behind such a faux rebellious attitude just to get your names in the paper. After all, the Blacks and Malfoys have been allies for centuries."

Harry got the feeling he detected amusement in Narcissa's eyes. "Allies? Don't you Malfoys consider the word allies a synonym for the people you haven't gotten around to stabbing in the back yet?"

Sirius jumped in and explained to Harry. "He's referring to the part of the Black legacy where you devote yourselves blindly to terrorist organizations. There's nothing like propagating intolerance and bigotry to bring glory and honor to a proud family."

Lucius narrowed his eyes but wasn't going to lose his cool. "If you have no interest in improving the state of affairs and restoring our nation to greatness, perhaps you should go back to whatever hole you two crawled out of," Lucius warned.

"Restoring our nation to greatness?" Sirius retorted. He turned to Harry and asked, "Does he actually mean ideals as dated as that hideous outfit he's wearing?"

"Be nice, Sirius," Harry sarcastically scolded. "You can see the wrinkles on his face, the grey coming in to his hair. At least he can still fit into an old costume like that."

Lucius' eyes flared at the mention of grey hair but held his tongue. "I see tradition and loyalty has truly become lost to the Black family."

"On the contrary, Lord Towel-boy," Sirius retorted happily. "The Blacks will protect their own. It saddens us to think of the horrors Narcissa Black has endured over the years, though it is a comfort to know that you can't teach ignorance."

"No matter how hard your daddy and his wand probably tried," Harry added with a grin while fighting the impulse to smack the smug look off Lucius' face.

Lucius just smiled dangerously. "I was asked some very interesting questions about you, Sirius Black," Lucius said with a knowing grin. "And I suspect you were asked similar questions about me."

"You suspect?" Harry interjected. "He suspects, Sirius. Do you suspect anything?"

"I suspect his crotch is so rotten that even the crabs committed suicide," Sirius answered.

Lucius shook his head. "Boys, boys. Tsk, tsk. Always so quick to hide behind sarcasm. Quite a bit like a Sirius Black I used to know. He died on Halloween begging for mercy from what I hear. It'd be a crying shame for history to repeat itself."

"Says the man who brought up that point once already," Sirius retorted.

"I noticed you sent a representative to the Wizengamot," Harry commented. "You should come yourself. I'd love to see if we couldn't try and resolve our differences with an audience."

Lucius sighed. "I suppose it was a vain hope that either of you could engage in any intelligent conversation." He grabbed Narcissa's hand. "Let us take our leave from the travesty your former family has become."

"We mean it, Narcissa," Sirius called out as they walked away. "We will protect a Black. It requires renouncing any other name or Master, and declaring loyalty to the family. Think about it the next time he curses you."

Harry sighed once the Malfoys were out of earshot. "God I hate that fucker."

Sirius shook his head. "You know growing up, she was only mean to me when she was forced to. Not exactly a bucket of compassion, but her heart wasn't in it. Not sure her heart has ever been in anything."

Harry smirked. "She's as bad as Molly Weasley at being a doting mother."

"I could see that." Sirius agreed and turned to Harry. He made sure he was looking him in the eye, pleading, "After this job, I want to rob that fucker blind."

Harry nodded and sighed. "Me too, but don't set your heart on it just yet. If it's anything like our old world, the wards are tighter than everything this side of Gringotts and Hogwarts."

"I figured," Sirius admitted. "Let's go get drunk now. Get a head start on those Weasley twins."

The pair apparated to Hogsmeade and walked right into the dingy pub, the Hog's Head. A quick glance showed a woman behind the bar and not the Headmaster's brother that Harry had been expecting. His attention was drawn to a smiling blonde woman waving him over to her table. Sirius walked up to the bar while Harry approached the attractive familiar face.

"I've been expecting you," Luna Lovegood greeted Harry.

Harry looked around briefly and saw Sirius was still trying to get the attention of the bartender. "Are you sure it's me you've been expecting?"

Luna shook her head. "No, but I think it is."

"Why were you expecting me?"

Luna tilted her head in the exact same way the Luna of Harry's old dimension did. "You know me, but I don't know you."

"Interesting," Harry commented, unsure how he felt about an alternate Luna but having never doubted the loyalty of the first one.

Luna tilted her back up and earnestly asked, "Perhaps we could discuss it over libations as we collectively contemplate the possibility of intercourse?"

Harry blinked. Then he took a moment to process her meaning and smiled at her. "Okay."

"Harry!" Sirius wheezed out. "Harry help! Man down!"

Harry whipped around and saw Sirius on the floor, with his hands over his crotch. He didn't see any threats but a few that looked like regulars around the bar were chuckling. He ran up to his godfather and asked, "What happened?"

Sirius took one of his hands off his private bits and pointed straight towards the bar and bartender.

Harry jerked up and immediately began to assess the threat. The bartender was a bit short, had a rag tied up covering her black cropped pixie-like hair. A decent chest accentuated by a halter-top and half-folded down apron showed a toned stomach. The most fetching aspect was the pair of thong straps riding up her bare hips. She had more piercings than just about any witch Harry had ever seen, but the twinkle in her eye was way too familiar.

"Holy crap!" Harry blurted out, leaning forward to look closer at her face. "Ginny?"

The bartender's smirk turned into a frown and she slapped her hand down on the bar directly in front of Harry.

Harry wondered what the hell happened to Ginny Weasley and why she was slapping the bar when he felt a steel-toed boot fly up between his legs and slam into his soft tissue.

Harry crumpled to the floor, grabbing his livelihood, and assuming a nearly identical position as Sirius.

Sirius was now laughing in pain but making no move to get up off the floor yet. "That kick lifted you off the ground. That was great."

Harry could only groan, as the bartender walked around the bar and right up to the two men on the floor.

They both rolled onto their backs to look up at her, catching a nice view of some skintight leather shorts. A small kitten tattoo was partially visible on an inside upper thigh that Harry was confident was completely bare on the original Ginny.

She was perfectly aware where both men were staring as she smirked down on them. "The name is Gin and you'd do well to remember that."

Chapter 14

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"You bad Master!"

Harry winced as he woke up and hissed in pain when wincing aggravated his tender cheek. He groaned in general discomfort.

"Kreacher thought you were just different. Kreacher thought you were quirky. But Kreacher was wrong!"

"What?" Harry blearily asked, realizing there was a house elf standing on his chest.

"You bad Master! Bad, BAD!"

Harry opened his eyes and saw the house elf in question was holding up the Daily Prophet. The entire front page was a giant article entitled, "Lords Black Outduel Lord Voldemort!" with a smaller subheading 'Dark Lord retreats after gruesome broken neck.' The picture showed Harry on his knees and the Dark Lord floating immobile as his head faced the wrong direction. The moving image had Sirius running into frame, then disappearing and running into frame again, in an eternal loop.

"Oh," Harry said watching the picture and remembering why he felt so crappy.

"No-good muggle-loving Master!" Kreacher spat. "Shame on you! Fooling Kreacher into thinking you're a good Master when Master knew Master was a bad Master. Bad!"

"Right," Harry said. "Get off me, Kreacher. That's an order."

Kreacher hopped down and stalked away angrily. "Filthy evil Masters hurting the Dark Lord. Tricking Kreacher into helping muggle-loving blood traitors."

"And leave the paper," Harry added. He was forced to quickly duck as the folded newspaper was thrown at his head and the elf disappeared down the hall.

Harry kicked his legs over the side of the bed and sat up. "Urh…" Harry groaned in pain. He drew his only remaining wand, the ash one with a unicorn hair and used his good hand to scourgify his clothes and sheets.

Harry walked slowly and deliberately towards his bathroom and turned on the tap. He splashed water on his face, gently rinsing the dried blood off his cheek, neck, and arms. He saw scrapes, scratches, and purple bruises all over his body. He exhaled tiredly and looked at himself in the mirror. "You look like crap," he told his reflection.

"And you're talking to a muggle mirror," the mirror snootily replied.

"I'm not stupid, you know," Harry said with a frown, before wincing in pain from frowning.

"Right," the mirror chided before standing up straighter, thrusting his hips forward, and mockingly staring Harry's eyes, "I'm a star. I'm a star. I'm a big bright shining star."

"Hey!" Harry indignantly scolded. "That's not an accurate reflection of me and you know it."

The mirror image rolled his eyes. "You're running late."

"Crap," Harry said glancing at the clock in his bedroom. He tossed on his clothes and grabbed the magical newspaper Kreacher had so kindly left behind.

Harry banged on Sirius' door and stuck his head in. "Time to wake up. We're supposed to be in front of the Wizengamot in three minutes."

"Ugh," Sirius grumbled. "Dammit Harry. You're an idiot."

"What'd I do now?"

"Why didn't you take me to St. Mungo's? I'm in pain here."

Harry pushed the door fully open. "You're a big boy. And you're not that smart."

"Oi!"

"Potions in Bella's room," Harry announced.

"Ugh," Sirius replied.

"I'm taking you with us whether you've had your potions or not."

"I hate you."

Harry shook his head and turned towards Bella's room. He added while leaving, "You made the front page."

"Sweet," Sirius happily called out before adding, "Ugh."

Harry knocked on Bellatrix's door. He waited a few seconds before walking in. "You awake?"

Bellatrix was lying in the exact same spot and just turned her head towards the door. "I wasn't until I heard you say Wizengamot."

"No pain, right?"

Bellatrix sat up looking around in confusion. "No, no pain. What did you do?"

"You haven't looked at your arm, have you?"

Bellatrix made it a habit of pulling her sleeve down to cover the Dark Mark and for the most part pretended the mark wasn't there. She slid her sleeve up and her eyes' widened. "That's impossible."

Harry helped himself to a pain-relieving potion, then a headache potion, and finished with a pepper-up.

"How did… I mean… what did you do?"

Harry tossed her the folded up paper and instructed. "It's an unofficial inquiry from the Wizengamot. The DMLE would have a warrant for your arrest if they could. And don't answer anything we tell you not to. Be ready to go in a minute. We'll get food afterwards."

Bellatrix just listened as the young man ordered her around. She wasn't sure how she felt about Harry's attitude. She unfolded the paper and looked at the front page. Her heart clenched when she looked at the massive headline and photo. She'd feared the Dark Lord's retribution but the photo of him looking so broken, filled her with hope. She felt her body shudder in happiness that she had two Lords willing to help her and stand up for her. She could truly imagine getting another chance, free from the Dark Lord. Her fragile emotional state was beginning to crumble when she was rudely interrupted.

"Hey!" Sirius yelled, pulling the paper away from her. "Keep your tears off my picture, woman."

Bellatrix just turned to see the other Lord Black smiling at the newspaper.

"Where'd I go?" Sirius questioned. "Wait… what the? I'm not even in the picture half the time. What the hell kind of reporting is this? Dammit. Harry!"

Harry came back into the room carrying witch's robes covered in a sunflower pattern. "Don't blame me. They just happened to take a picture from an angle that makes you look fat."

"Makes me look what?"

"Here, put this on," Harry said tossing the robes to Bellatrix.

Bellatrix accepted the robes and looked at Harry doubtfully. "This isn't really my style."

"I'm aiming for innocent," Harry deadpanned. "I think we both know that's not gonna come off as your style."

Bellatrix shamefully got up and faced the wall while she changed into the robes, saying nothing more.

Harry was pleased to notice Sirius hadn't even noticed her brief moment of undress as he was carefully inspecting the newspaper photo.

"I don't look… that fat," Sirius complained. "It's a funny angle."

"We're late," Harry announced. He saw Bellatrix looked uncomfortable in the very feminine robes. "Give me your wand."

Bellatrix looked hesitant but handed it over.

"They won't allow you to have it in the session," Harry explained. "But if I've got it, they can't take it away. And I can give it to you, if we think you need it."

Harry snatched the paper from Sirius and grabbed onto Bellatrix. "You can read the paper when we get there. Might be a nice show of disrespect." Harry apparated to the atrium of the Ministry, pulling Bellatrix with him side-along.

Sirius appeared with a pop moments after. He leaned forward, clutching his side. "Dammit. We've gotta go to St. Mungo's after this."

Harry winced and agreed. The group of three checked in at the front desk and hurried down to courtroom ten.

Harry barged into the sealed courtroom, loudly announcing their presence. "Sorry, we're late. Sirius had pieces of Dark Lord in his hair."

The entire collected Wizengamot looked in surprise as the Lords Black stomped into the room like they owned it, while Bellatrix Black followed them dutifully. Seated in the three seats below Chief Warlock Albus Dumbledore were Director Bones, Assistant Director Potter, and Croaker from the Department of Mysteries.

A simple sturdy table with three chairs was waiting in the middle. A pitcher of ice water and three cups were provided.

Harry made a show of hissing in pain, as he clutched his side. He held up his left hand and called the Sovereign Saber into existence. He twirled it twice as a pleasant reminder to the Wizengamot and then used it as a walking stick for the last few steps to the table.

"Are you Lords alright?" Albus Dumbledore asked, seeing they both looked pretty banged up.

Sirius nodded and took the seat on the far right. "We're headed to a healer after this."

"We could reschedule…" Albus offered ignoring the other members upset murmuring at Albus' suggestion.

"No," Harry insisted taking the seat on the left, gesturing for Bellatrix to take the center chair. "Let's get this over with before my potions wear off and I get grumpy."

"You wouldn't like him when he's grumpy," Sirius warned, gulping down a glass of water and pouring himself a second.

"Come on Chief Warlock," Harry said clapping his hands loudly. "Let's get this inquisition going."

Albus cleared his throat and answered. "Madame Bones will handle Miss Black's questioning, but the events of last night have raised a few questions about both Lord Blacks as well."

"Imagine that," Sirius said, leaning back in his chair.

"Do you have any objections to answering some questions today?" Albus clarified.

Harry waved his hand in annoyance. "Wouldn't you just issue another summons for another unofficial interrogation in a few days if we did?"

"Most likely," Albus cheerfully agreed. He turned to the woman seated below him on the right. "Madame Bones?"

"Thank you," Madame Bones replied at suddenly being thrust to the center of attention. "Bellatrix Black, do you understand that you are not being charged with anything at this time?"

Bellatrix glanced at Harry before nodding at Madame Bones.

"As this is a formal legal body, anything you say will be taken as the oath-sworn truth and inconsistencies could constitute a crime."

Harry heard Sirius whining and handed him back the newspaper so he could read it. When Bellatrix looked at Harry again, he answered for her. "If you want her to answer the questions under veritaserum, she will. But only if we use an inverted bubble and all the questions are relayed through myself and Lord Black."

Amelia glanced at her Assistant Director who was staring thoughtfully at the three Blacks. "That won't be necessary. Miss Black, are you a Death Eater?"

She saw Harry nod and answered, "No."

"Were you a Death Eater?"

Sirius had been holding up the newspaper and reading it in an obvious show of disrespect. He whipped it to the side and leaned around the paper to ask, "Is that a crime?"

"Being a Death Eater?" Madame Bones clarified.

"Or having been one in the past," Harry added.

"No," Amelia answered. "It's not a crime."

"But it subjects you to a more official questioning without witnesses and with veritaserum," Harry stated.

"The laws on interrogating proven Death Eaters permit wartime tactics, yes," Amelia agreed. "Miss Black, were you a Death Eater?"

Harry leaned over, loudly telling Bellatrix, "Don't answer that question."

"The Dark Mark is all the proof we need," Assistant Director James Potter stated in irritation.

Sirius harrumphed and snapped his paper back up, ignoring this world's Prongs.

"Well it's a good thing she doesn't have the Dark Mark then," Harry retorted.

Sirius blew a victorious raspberry from behind his newspaper.

Amelia put her hand up to stop James and asked, "Healer Armstrong informed us she carried the Dark Mark."

Bellatrix looked at Harry who shrugged at her. He replied, "Did you have a question in there?"

"Was he correct in his statement?" Amelia inquired.

Harry stopped Bellatrix again. "I hardly think we'd be capable of interpreting his statement to you when we weren't there."

Amelia paused before rewording, "Did you have the Dark Mark when Healer Armstrong treated you?"

Harry leaned over and whispered into Bellatrix's ear. She looked at Harry curiously who just nodded in encouragement. Bellatrix leaned forward and softly answered, "I'm not here to talk about the past."

A number of Wizengamot members were unsubtle in their annoyance, huffing and grumbling as loudly as Bellatrix had spoken.

Amelia could tell they were quickly going to run out of options. "So you're admitting that you're not a Death Eater now, but are unwilling to say whether you once were."

"I'm not here to talk about the past," Bellatrix said again upon Harry's urging.

"And you don't carry the Dark Mark now, and again, are unwilling to even say whether you ever did."

Bellatrix nodded.

"Say it," Harry whispered and nudged.

"I'm not here to talk about the past," Bellatrix reiterated immediately.

"What are you here to talk about?" An annoyed member of the Wizengamot snapped.

Harry answered, "Bellatrix is here in cooperation with your request. She's openly stated she's not a Death Eater, and she doesn't carry the Dark Mark. Unless you have legal precedent demanding a response, she is free to choose whether to answer any given question or not."

"That is correct, Lord Black," Amelia said knowing they weren't going to get much of anything from this conversation. She had to try though. "Miss Black, without freely offering anything incriminating, could you tell us any details about your former associates? Their names for instance."

Bellatrix glanced at Harry and saw Sirius was still reading the paper. She leaned forward and said, "I'm not here to talk abo-"

"Talk about the past," Amelia interrupted and finished for her. "Yeah. We heard that part. I think we're just wasting each other's time now. So if you wouldn't mind proving that you don't carry the Dark Mark…"

Bella showed off her forearm and the Black family crest tattooed on it.

James Potter walked on down and cast finishing charms, ensuring it wasn't just hidden or disillusioned. "Toujours Pur," He stated loudly. "How quaint."

Sirius flipped his paper back and interjected, "We're contemplating changing it to ite-Bay e-May, itches-Bay. What do you think?"

James looked at Sirius curiously, but without quite as much animosity as usual. He walked back up to sit by his boss, informing her, "It's their family crest, not the Dark Mark."

"Thank you Miss Black," Madame Bones said with a faked smile. "Your cooperation has been… duly noted."

"Great," Sirius called out, loudly folding up his paper. "Are we done now? Because my broken ribs are starting to itch." Sirius sniffed the air a couple times. "And I think I smell roasted almonds."

"I'm sure many people are very curious about the events of last night," Albus stated. "Would you like me to call for a healer while you answer our questions?"

Harry glanced over at Sirius who nodded. "Alright," Harry agreed. "And get us some sandwiches too."

Albus leaned back and whispered something to the woman standing behind him. She left the courtroom presumably to get a healer and some sandwiches.

"First off," Harry addressed. "I want to make one thing clear: last night was a family matter and a family matter only. We're not the Department of Magical Law Enforcement nor do we have any intentions of joining the Aurors. We consider the matter between us and Lord Voldemort closed. End of story."

Albus furrowed his brow. "You do not oppose the Dark Lord Voldemort?"

"Oppose?" Harry repeated and shook his head. "Not really. I think he believes there are wrongs in this society that need to be righted, and I'm certainly agreeable to that. That is not to say I approve of his alleged methods or philosophies. And if he is arrested and found guilty of any crimes, then I would fully support seeing justice prevail. So no, I guess I don't oppose the Dark Lord."

"He's going to come after you," James Potter insisted, "whether you oppose him or not."

"I'd rather he didn't," Harry offhandedly remarked. "We've already had one conflict with him that's been resolved. I hope not to have another."

An older wizard came briskly walking into the room, wearing the robes and carrying the tools of a healer. Harry pointed at Sirius indicating he should go first and the man began to fire diagnostic charms at Sirius.

"Are you saying if you were walking down the street and saw Death Eaters attacking innocents, you would do nothing?" Amelia doubtfully asked.

"Of course not," Harry charmingly replied. "I would do what any decent person would do. I'd contact the authorities."

"You would not step in?" Lord Peter Potter stood up and asked. "You are a powerful wizard."

"A subjective claim but one that's irrelevant. Protecting the magical people of this nation is the work of the Aurors. I'm no more an auror than most everyone else in this room. And while I've met a few with the competency of a whomping willow, I won't belittle the work that they do by implying anyone could step in and do it."

Amelia rolled her eyes at the pile Harry was shoveling.

"I'll take that as a yes," Lord Potter sat down with a smile, shaking his head at Harry's answer.

Most of the Wizengamot were surprised to see no retort from Harry but a look of matching amusement on his face.

"Your turn," Sirius called out as the healer moved over towards Harry. A large plate of sandwiches had been brought in and Bellatrix and Sirius were both scarfing down lunch.

Harry let the healer examine him while the questioning continued.

"The matter of restitution needs to be addressed," Albus stated.

"Prosti-what?" Sirius repeated with a mouthful of sandwich.

"Restitution, Lord Black," Albus repeated somberly. "Your duel last night has left much damage in its wake. Seeing as how you failed to use the Lords' arena for your duel, it falls to the participant Houses of the duel to cover the cost of repairs."

"Fair enough," Harry replied while the healer was focused intently on Harry's damaged right hand. "We're prepared to match every knut Lord Voldemort pays to cover the costs."

A number of disgruntled murmurs filled the air before Sirius swallowed the bite in his mouth and said, "Actually, I was aiming to blast the Dark Lord into that teacup display. So I should probably donate to at least that particular relief effort."

"Dammit," Harry swore loudly after the healer gave him the news.

"What?"

"My bloody wand hand has seven hairline fractures. Any one of them could snap and pop right through the skin. He's gotta vanish the bones and I've gotta regrow them."

"Don't trust him," an old woman called out loudly. "He's a dark wizard. This may all be a charade manufactured by the Dark Lord."

"There's the close-mindedness the Wizengamot is famous for," Harry cheered. "Finally a voice for the voiceless incompetents."

"I'm sorry," Sirius asked with mock sincerity. "But who are you?"

"Hmph," the woman huffed refusing to answer.

Albus interjected, "Madame Edgecombe's family owns one of the buildings in Badgin Alley that sustained damages."

"I make no secret of that," Edgecombe snapped. "But it doesn't change the fact that he's a dark wizard."

"Yeah well…" Sirius shrugged. "You're a werewolf."

Madame Edgecombe stiffened at the accusation. "I most certainly am not."

"So? What does that matter?" Sirius asked in confusion. "I thought we were just making up random shit because we're irritable from all the sores on our crusty old vaginas." Sirius finished while quite obviously scratching himself.

"Lord Black, please," Amelia tiredly answered. "A little decorum while you mock and insult us would be appreciated."

"Well I never…" Madame Edgecombe's complexion was beginning to cycle between shades of anger and embarrassment. "I am making nothing up. He's a parseltongue."

"No, I'm not," Harry said while trying to gesture with his hand. The healer had just finished vanishing the bones so his arm appeared to be flapping like a flesh-filled glove. "Nice work," Harry commented towards the healer while waggling his hand.

"You deny that you're a parseltongue?" she asked with a conniving smile. "That you weren't seen hissing at the Dark Mark before your staged little duel?"

"I'm not a parseltongue," Harry tiredly explained. "I'm a parselmouth. The language I can speak and understand is parseltongue. And if you've ever seen an anaconda you can understand why I sometimes get called a parselcrotch."

"Lord Black!" Amelia snapped, looking more amused than scandalized.

"Too much?" Harry replied with a smile.

"We really don't need to know that."

Harry saw Dumbledore's beard was twitching and hiding a smile. "I'm just floating it out there," Harry said while leaning back in his seat. "You ladies make of it what you will. Well, except for you, Lord Burke."

The man in question flushed in anger but refused to be baited.

The healer finished working on Harry and gave him a topical cream and a carefully measured dose of skele-gro.

"You are a disgrace," Edgecombe harshly announced while calmly sitting back down. "A disgrace to the Wizengamot, a disgrace to wizards everywhere, and a disgrace to your family."

"A disgrace to our family," Sirius repeated skeptically. "You just don't get it, do you?"

"You don't care," Edgecombe snobbishly retorted. "We get it."

"No, you don't," Sirius said. "It's not that we don't care, it's that we don't care about people like you."

"Some of it's that we don't care," Harry corrected. "But it's also fun to point and laugh at the truly retarded aspects of any form of government that includes us."

"I hardly think this is the appropriate time for this discussion," Albus interjected despite being curious what the Lords Black had to say.

"No, I think this is a fine time," Harry said. "Don't you think it's worth noting that had we lost last night's duel, there would be a Voldemort seat here on the Wizengamot? Does it not bother more people that an idiot punk kid could slip on a ring on a whim and suddenly have the ability to inadvertently entrench the Dark Lord into the primary legislative body?"

There were a number of shocked faces glancing around.

"Surprise," Harry mocked.

"You want to talk about a disgrace?" Sirius repeated. "I know more than a few of you flounce about your titles of Lord and Baron simply because you inherited them or your family ring chose you. But how many are concerned about a cousin you've only met a few times? I mean genuinely concerned about their health and well-being, even more than your own inflated sense of self worth?"

Harry was tempted to make fun of Sirius for caring more than he pretended.

"I'm not talking about the rationalization you delude yourself with that you're only trying to make your family name respected." Sirius paused and asked in a calm voice, "But how many of you would be willing to stand up to the Dark Lord for your family?"

Harry saw Bellatrix was slumping lower and lower in her chair. He tried not to enjoy her guilt too much. "Are we about done here?" Harry asked loudly.

"Are you in a hurry, Lord Black?" James answered watching him a bit suspiciously.

Harry gestured wildly letting his boneless hand flap back and forth in the air. "Heck no. It's not like I did anything strenuous last night." Harry's floppy hand smacked himself in the cheek. "Oh wait… there was this one thing."

"Speaking of last night," Albus smoothly segued. "I found it particularly interesting that your wand and the Dark Lord's combined to form the Priori Incantatem effect."

Harry winced. "Noticed that, did you?"

Albus nodded seriously. "I also know you're aware that Mr. Ollivander was obliviated and is missing a wand."

"Before you go pointing that finger," Sirius interjected. "May I remind you that we are the reason he's even aware he was obliviated and lost a wand. We were as surprised as he was."

Madame Bones just nodded, having taken Ollivander's statement. "True, but it's still curious that you were looking for that wand specifically. Seeing as though it appears you found that wand it also raises questions about where you got it from."

"In case you missed it," Sirius answered. "Harry's wand went snap, crackle, and pop. And I don't think Voldemort's going to drop by and let you all check out his wand. For all your assumptions, they could be brother wands sharing a core of Veela ovaries."

" Phoenix song was heard," Amelia stated.

Sirius was about to retort before deflating rapidly. "Oh."

"Thanks for the help, Sirius," Harry said with a fake smile.

Sirius shrugged. "Well that's what you get for making fun of my disgrace observation."

"I didn't say anything," Harry argued.

Sirius shook his head in disagreement. "Your look said it all."

Harry resisted the urge to poke his pouting godfather in the eye. He turned towards the front of the Wizengamot. "I'm under too many other potions to take veritaserum, but I'll explain this under a truth spell."

Albus swiftly drew his wand. "Do you mind if someone other than Lord Black casts the spell on you?"

Harry glanced at Sirius and Bellatrix. "As long as you don't mind these two keeping their wands drawn."

Albus agreed and cast the intended spell on Harry. One lesser known advantage to casting the spell was the ability of the caster to feel when the spell is being resisted. That would give Albus a little more information on misleading truths or half-truths.

"Is it working?" Amelia asked turning towards Albus.

Albus nodded. "I believe so."

"Let's find out," Sirius grinned deviously. "Hey Harry, I know you saw Amy's knockers the other day. What did you think of them?"

Harry answered without pause. "They've held up better than I would've guessed. Which bodes well for the sake of Susan's breasts too."

Sirius turned towards Amelia who was keeping her head down. "Yeah, I'd say the truth spell is working."

"I would have to concur," Albus agreed. He saw a few people turn to him and quickly clarified, "That the spell is working."

"Lovely," Harry stated feeling the spell twinge at his sarcasm. "Okay, the thing with the wand is that I purchased it completely legally from… someone who I believe was the wandmaker. And I certainly never memory charmed Mr. Ollivander."

"Where did you get that wand?" Albus asked.

"I bought it from a wandmaker, and no, I'm not going to reveal the wandmaker's name."

Amelia inquired, "Do you not suspect the wandmaker may have acquired illegally? Or be guilty of attacking Mr. Ollivander?"

"For reasons I'm not going to share," Harry happily answered. "I can say that I am nearly certain the wandmaker who sold me that wand, was freely given the core and crafted it personally."

Harry didn't want to paint himself into a corner but got an idea. "I will add that I purchased my wand over a decade ago. Supposedly, there was a similar one at Ollivander's and that was why I asked Mr. Ollivander specifically for it."

Albus felt a twinge in the spell but knew everything Harry had said was the truth. He cancelled the spell and inclined his head. "Thank you for your cooperation, Lord Black."

"We done?" Sirius said, pushing himself to his feet.

"Not just yet," Albus said with an apologetic smile. "We were wondering what spell you used to finish the Dark Lord, and whether it was related to your unique form of defense in the duel."

"You don't need to know that," Sirius whined.

"I told you," Madame Edgecombe could be heard murmuring while shaking her head. "Dark. The whole family."

Harry offered, "It wasn't a spell I think anyone else could easily reproduce. But of course it was very evil, dark magic."

Sirius snorted at the deafening silence.

"Egads," Harry chided. "I've seen livelier crowds at death-day parties."

"Lord Black," Albus slowly began.

Harry put his hand up stopping Dumbledore. He looked at the Unspeakable. "Croaker, isn't it?"

Croaker nodded silently.

"You got some curse-breaking glasses?"

"I can get some," Croaker said, reaching into his inside pocket. There was a flash of magic and he pulled out a pair of rose-tinted glasses.

Harry waved him down. "I thought you might be willing to break down all of my evil, dark magic."

The pitcher of water lifted up off the table and refilled the three glasses in front of them.

"You see it?"

Croaker nodded, looking through the glasses. "Is there more to it than the two charms I see?"

Harry shook his head.

Croaker waved his hand through the glowing magical appendage, passing it through without resistance. He stuck his wand tip right into and whispered a spell that drained just a little magic from Harry's arm.

He whispered another spell analyzing the magic. "Remarkable."

"That's what the ladies tell me," Harry agreed.

Croaker ignored the sarcasm and asked, "So do you just exert more or less magic into either spell? This is an amazing amount of control."

Harry nodded and explained, "That's kind of the way it started, but at this point it's just second nature."

Croaker nodded looking at Harry's glowing appendage and saw several others emerge from his body as the pitcher and three glasses began to orbit them all. "I'm not surprised considering how the two have practically fused into one spell," Croaker added while looking only at the magic.

Dumbledore had been watching intently through his own charmed glasses as well.

"An explanation, please?" Amelia kindly ordered.

Harry set everything down and sucked his arms inward disappearing inside himself. He waved at Croaker to answer.

"It's nothing more than two sustained spells held in conjunction: one a banishing charm, the other a summoning charm," Croaker answered. "So you basically summoned the back of Voldemort's head while banishing the front, resulting in the violent twisting we all observed. How long have you been practicing those two spells?"

"Longer than anyone else I've heard of. But I think I'm predisposed to those two spells more than others. That's why I doubt anyone could easily reproduce the effect," Harry turned towards Albus. "And I think we've been patient enough. I'm exhausted and have the pain of skele-gro to look forward to instead of a nap. Was there anything else you wanted to know that can't wait?"

Albus glanced at Amelia who shook her head and nodded. "No, nothing else at this time. We thank you for your patience and cooperation, Lords Black, Miss Black."

Sirius jumped right up out of his seat, happy to go. Harry and Bellatrix followed him at a more sedate pace. By the time they caught up with Sirius, he was surrounded by a half dozen reporters and photographers.

"Did the Dark Lord-"

"It was purely a family matter," Sirius interrupted as quills were whisking in notebooks. "Let me make this clear. We're not opposed to the Dark Lord. We're certainly not supporting him either. If he's guilty of the crimes he's accused of then I hope the Aurors can arrest him and put him on trial. But we're not interested in doing the job of the DMLE."

"He's going to want you dead," one man in a brown hat stated.

Sirius shrugged indifferent. "I suppose it's possible he could be the type to hold a grudge, but as far as I'm concerned the matter between him and the Blacks is closed."

"Don't you feel you have a responsibility-"

"Yes," Sirius interrupted. "As a Lord, I have a responsibility to my family. Of course ask anyone who knows me, and they'll tell you I'm not a very responsible person."

Harry caught Sirius' eye and jerked his head towards the atrium.

Sirius nodded and gave them a chance to escape unnoticed. He addressed the reporters and said, "You know I've been called a muggle-lover, simply because I dislike muggles just as much as I dislike wizards. But when it comes to the measure of a wizard, I wonder how many would be willing to stand up to the Dark Lord, or the Minsitry. Or even Albus Dumbledore for that matter. The only thing I knew about Bellatrix was that she was a Black. And as her Lord, that's enough. Anything else is a private family matter. Thank you."

Sirius hurried after Harry and Bellatrix, quickly apparating back to Grimmauld Place.

"Dammit," Sirius called out wondering where Harry and Bellatrix were. "You know what I just realized?"

"I'm in the muggle room," Harry's voice called back. "What did you realize?"

"I realized," Sirius ruefully admitted, "that 'Parselcrotch' is going to sell more shirts than any of my lines. Hell, I want a shirt that says 'Parselcrotch' on it. Maybe with a picture of a giant spitting hooded cobra."

"I'm sure Fred and George will have them on the shelves by the end of the day," Harry winced and clenched his eyes shut. "Let me start the sappy movie."

Sirius glanced at the screen as it came to life and turned back to Harry. "Why a sappy movie?"

Harry took a deep breath, patting himself on the arm with his good hand. "I can't sleep when I'm regrowing bones. And if my eyes water in irritation it won't be the work of some random bug I made up that flew in my eye."

"It was real," Sirius said for what felt like the hundredth time.

Harry ignored and continued. "It will be because I'm emotionally moved by this rich and dramatic tale. No other reason."

"You're gonna cry," Sirius laughed and pointed. He stopped and looked around, "Where's our resident psycho-bitch at?"

Harry pointed down the hall. "She's in her room. Kreacher was going to get her some food. I think he likes her more than us."

"We're going to need to figure something out for those two."

"I don't really trust either of them on their own, let alone together," Harry said. "But it's not like this side of Kreacher is terribly surprising."

Sirius nodded and silently watched some of the movie while fighting a smirk every time he heard Harry hissing softly in pain.

"Hey Harry?" Sirius said waiting for Harry to look over. "Why did you tell them so much about your wand and your freaky arm thing? We didn't have to answer."

"Why'd you care so much when I was called a disgrace?"

"I didn't care," Sirius explained. "I just wanted…"

"Stop looking for an answer," Harry said noticing Sirius was searching for an excuse. "I just was pointing out that you cared first."

"You answered their questions because you cared? And I didn't care by the way."

Harry paused the movie and explained. "I've had to deal with being looked at as both the poncy hero and as the next coming of the Dark Lord. And if I'm picking the lesser of two evils here, I don't want the headaches that come with them thinking of me as the next Dark Lord."

Sirius shook his head. "You cared."

"Besides," Harry added. "The best way to keep big secrets is to freely tell all the little ones and act like you have nothing to hide."

"Huh?"

"If you got ten questions about someone, and they eagerly and freely answer the first eight, then you're less likely to doubt or demand the answers to the last two."

"Oh, I get it," Sirius smiled. "You cared."

Harry ignored Sirius, turning back towards the movie and starting it up again.

Sirius stayed quiet for about a minute before asking "Hey Harry? Was your Voldemort a lot stronger?"

Harry paused the movie again and turned to his godfather curiously. "My Voldemort? Like he was a possession or a husband?"

"You know what I mean. Was he harder to defeat?"

Harry sighed, scratching his chin in thought. "Harder? Well… this Voldemort was a lot more composed and analytical. I guess this one wasn't quite so psychotic really. But stronger?" Harry sighed, deep in thought. "I think this one could've outlasted our old one."

"Really?" Sirius asked.

Harry nodded. "Did you see how many spells he cast? That kind of volume's ridiculous. And he still had more in him."

"We won," Sirius weakly added. "Stop trying to scare me."

"You asked."

Sirius kicked his feet up and laid back on the couch. "I hope he's hurting." He glanced over at Harry. "Or at least crying as much as you are, you big baby."

"I'm not above vanishing your pelvic bone."

Sirius frowned in confusion. "I don't think there's any real bone in that."

Harry sighed and started the movie again.

An ear-piercing shriek echoed around the stone chamber, sustained for ten agonizing seconds.

Voldemort stopped and panted as he caught his breath. He lay flat on his back on the altar in the middle of an old ritual room. He didn't care how immature and undignified he may have appeared. There were moments when his anger was better served yelling at the top of his magically enhanced lungs.

He had undergone enough rituals that his body was in the process of healing itself from injuries that would have easily killed lesser men. Already his mouth and jaw were working, though he still could not turn his head, nor could he feel anything below his neck.

Unfortunately for the Dark Lord, the healing was moving at a glacial pace. Fully healing his spine could take years, and there was no way to know when he might regain control of his limbs. But he knew of another way. Only the alternative ensured his magic would be drained and chaotic for weeks. After conceding that weeks would be preferable to relying on his limited ritual-created ability, he'd called for Rabastan Lestrange. And ordered him to go out and find a muggle as close to exactly the Dark Lord's size as possible.

Now he was just waiting here for Rabastan to return, with all the time in the world to think over how things had gone so wrong.

Just two days ago the Dark Lord had been torturing a new recruit, satisfied in the knowledge that it was being felt by the deserter, Bellatrix Black, when he was crudely interrupted by one of his faithful with an urgent message.

He'd heard many such tales of the Lords Black already and he hoped to gain their allegiance. When he arrived and saw his downed Death Eaters, he hoped they were putting on a show of their talents. When the one named Harry conversed with the Dark Mark in parseltongue, he hoped he had found a loyal kindred spirit.

But the Dark Lord had been foolish to hold onto hope.

He would humbly admit that they played him masterfully. First through capturing his attention long enough to humor them, then by tempting him with something useful to offer, and finally by inciting his anger until he had acted irrationally.

Voldemort at first wanted to claim their dueling skills were no match for him. Sirius would have fit right in with the inner circle, and Harry seemed too concerned with defense, showing only modest skills in offense. But the Dark Lord also realized it was that assessment of Harry that had permitted the young man's close approach. And he wasn't going to forget the smile that flashed on Harry's face just before the Dark Lord got turned into a captive of his own body.

Harry had been playing nice, waiting until he was close enough to strike.

Voldemort was confident they couldn't have killed him. He had too many protections against that. But when his neck broke, and he couldn't move his body, he had felt helpless. And that scared him. How easily he could have been captured then, and even now he was still susceptible.

The Dark Lord had been pleased to discover his magic was getting restless trapped inside his body and could now be focused in ways it never had before. It had only taken a burst of anger to explode the door to this room when he'd first portkeyed back here.

He had possessed one of the recruits when he had to address his faithful, but even that healthy young body couldn't sustain him and he was back here in his own flesh prison within a matter of hours.

The Dark Lord shrieked once more at the top of his lungs. He was angry. But he was disappointed in himself even more.

"You okay, Master?" the younger Goyle asked, sticking his head into the ritual room.

Voldemort closed his eyes and concentrated. He was rewarded by the sound of a fleshy pop and a kneecap came spinning across the floor, clacking against the altar the Dark Lord rested on. He happily chuckled to himself at the sound of Goyle screaming in pain, unable to even touch his bloodied leg.

He heard an obviously more intelligent recruit stun young Goyle and drag his body out from the doorway. The Dark Lord sighed again wondering how hard finding a muggle his size would be.

Returning to his musings he briefly wondered if the Lords Black were a manipulation of his unknown nemesis. Most often the Dark Lord referred to him as 'that fucker' considering how little was known of him. Numerous plans over the years had been foiled by that fucker, many of them in the early stages. He had first suspected there was a spy amongst his inner circle, but Voldemort had re-established each of their loyalties personally.

All Voldemort knew was that fucker seemed to be a complete enigma. He was operating from the shadows exclusively for almost two decades, as no one seemed to know anything about that fucker. The rumor that it was Neville Longbottom the Dark Lord found laughable. The mere idea that a child could match up to the Heir of Slytherin was so unfathomable that it didn't even anger the Dark Lord. It amused him.

He knew that fucker wasn't a kid. He'd dueled with him on dozens of occasions. Never for more than a minute or two before one or the other fled the scene. And that fucker wasn't shy about blowing shit up. The Dark Lord knew that fucker had an elegance and style similar to his own. And a ruthlessness that scared every one of his Death Eaters.

The two Lord Blacks possessed little style and more blunt force trauma in their execution. That was one part of Harry that not even that fucker could have faked. A tired clumsiness to his actions, that neither the Dark Lord nor that fucker would ever willingly show.

Voldemort sighed thinking about the myriad of fronts he was forced to constantly fend off, whether it was that fucker, Dumbledore and his flaming little Order, the increasingly competent Aurors, or now the Lords Black.

He had read the Prophet and heard reports from other sources that the article was completely accurate. The Lords Black wanted nothing to do with him and really were only interested in protecting Bellatrix Black's soul. They weren't going to assist the Ministry, and given their attitudes in the Wizengamot sessions weren't going to fall in line with Dumbledore any time soon. They weren't even gloating over their very public victory.

The Dark Lord honestly found it a bit disturbing. Because he really had no idea what to make of it. Could they genuinely believe he'd just let it go and consider the matter closed as they pretended to? Were they really deluding themselves into thinking they might not get any retribution from him? Voldemort was truly lost on what to deduce from their behavior.

If anything, the Dark Lord figured, their unpredictability was about all you could count on. And from what Voldemort could tell, it seemed to focus on Harry more than it did Sirius. His behavior and skills were just one revelation after the next, from his gift for the serpent tongue to the scar on his forehead to his magical arms. And to willingly and publicly divulge the secret of his arms? That's what puzzled Voldemort the most.

He was trying to gain an understanding of the two Lord Blacks. His musings led him back to his brief attempt at Legilimency. Neither had any noticeable protection though Harry had immediately located him and ejected him forcefully enough to snap his hold on both of them. But it was not before he had gleaned a single thought from each of their heads. Two more pieces of the puzzle that formed this unique pair of Lord Blacks.

From Harry's mind he had discovered that Sirius was Harry's godfather. A relationship that was even more important when combined with what he had extracted from Sirius' head: Harry was the son of Sirius' best friend.

That pointed strongly to the conclusion that they weren't both born Blacks. When he considered that at the time Sirius Black was healing in St. Mungo's he was not yet Lord Black, it appeared that Harry had received the title first and yet Harry was the one less likely to have been born a Black.

For Harry to receive the Lordship, he would likely have inherited it from his godfather, indicating… that Sirius had died? The Dark Lord could tell he was getting somewhere and continued to brainstorm. He began to think that Harry may have traveled back in time after having become Lord Black, and then altered the timeline and saved his godfather's life.

Therefore he was already Lord Black, and he could assist Sirius in gaining the same title. The Dark Lord was trying to imagine just how powerful the magic to accomplish something like that would be when he froze in recognition.

He couldn't believe he had been so oblivious. It had been twenty-five years since he'd last encountered a Sirius Black with a godson named Harry. He knew without a doubt that he had killed those two, but the situations were damning in the similarities.

He started to try and imagine how Harry could have splintered the timeline that far into the past when he suddenly caught on to the fact that he didn't have to go back at all. These weren't the Sirius and Harry of this timeline. These two came from another one entirely. Sirius came first, and that's how Harry received the Lordship in their world. Then Harry came after Sirius and helped Sirius gain the Lordship in this one. They really did just arrive in the last few months.

Voldemort then connected that Lord Harry Black was a different Harry Potter, and a viable subject of his prophecy. That made things far more complicated.

Yet again, the Dark Lord screamed in frustration.

"I've got one, Master!" Rabastan Lestrange announced levitating an awake and frightened muggle into the chamber.

"It's about bloody time," Voldemort snarled. "Show him to me."

Rabastan directed the man to hover over the Dark Lord so that he could get a look at him. "He may look a little taller, but that's just the hair."

Voldemort looked up at the man blocking his light. "He'll have to do. Strip him. And lay him on top of me. Face up."

Voldemort's robes fell open revealing his own nude body, and the petrified man was set down right on top of the Dark Lord.

"I've got him," Voldemort ordered, seizing control of the spell with only his mind. "Leave us. And seal the door behind you."

"Yes Master," Rabastan happily agreed, eager to get out of there. He felt the locks on the door latch before he could turn them himself.

"First things first," Voldemort said, extending his tongue to lick the back of the man's head. "Let's break that silencing spell."

The man's frightened gasps and yelps were made audible and he shouted at simply having the ability to do so.

"Go ahead and scream," Voldemort hissed at him, pooling his magic at the surfaces where their bodies met. "It inspires me."

The screams echoed throughout the room and all the halls in the building. Many Death Eaters were relishing in the haunting sounds, while their weaker-willed brethren were intimidated by them.

About twelve hours later the inner circle was assembled waiting outside the ritual room door.

The Dark Lord opened the door with his hand and stood there leaning against the door frame. His skin was white but looked shiny and new. Behind him on the altar was what appeared to be a skin sack filled with fluid and tissue that only vaguely resembled the muggle.

Voldemort was panting from the effort but was very pleased to be mobile once again. "I want to know everything there is to know about the Lord Blacks. No one is to touch them, understood?"

The inner circle all nodded their heads obediently, completely masking their own opinions.

While trying to block out the pain, Voldemort had been doing a lot more thinking on the presence of this Harry Potter, if he was in fact Harry Potter. The more he considered it, the more sense it made to the Dark Lord. But he wasn't going to rule out that fucker either. He briefly entertained thoughts of how revealing their secret could be used against them, or to blackmail them, before remembering the prophecy. Which would mean their secret getting out would probably hurt him more than either of them.

"The Lord Blacks are off limits until I say so. But if you find the deserter," Voldemort clenched his teeth demanding, "Make an example of her."

He dismissed his inner circle and began to calmly walk back to his own chambers, hiding the pain he was still in. He realized that if Harry and Sirius really did just arrive in this timeline, then their ignorance of the differences between worlds could be used against them.

And then, when the time is right and they had run out of surprises to hide behind, he would savor killing Harry Potter again.

Sirius Black though would be denied the mercy of joining his godson in death. No, the Dark Lord thought with a grim smile, Sirius' pain would come from living.

Chapter 15

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"Son of a bitch!" Sirius yelled after stubbing his toe. He looked down and saw an empty dirty cauldron had been set down in front of his bedroom door. "Harry? Did you put this here?"

Kreacher's not so quiet cackling was heard coming from the down the hall.

"You wretched little hatemonger," Sirius swore shaking his leg, trying to ignore the pain in his toe. "Get back here."

"Stupid bad Master wasn't looking where he was going," Kreacher mumbled to himself ignoring the fact that he was walking towards Sirius. "Stupid stupid Master."

"Listen up, you little ingrate," Sirius ordered. "We were protecting a pureblood, Bellatrix, from a mudblood, Tom Riddle. That's right! The Dark Lord's pappy was a muggle."

"Kreacher knows about the Dark Lord," Kreacher mumbled in irritation. "Everyone knows about the Dark Lord. But not everyone knows about Kreacher's stupid Masters. Oh no. Stupid masters have lots of secrets to keep."

"Sirius," Harry yawned as he walked out of his bedroom. "Do you have to pick a fight with a house elf every morning?"

"He tried to break my foot," Sirius defended, pointing down at Kreacher.

"Kreacher forgot where Kreacher put one of the cauldrons to clean. Accidents happen. Even to stupid Masters the Dark Lord is going to eviscerate. Accidents happen." Kreacher muttered, not looking up at either of them.

"Are you sure we can't kill him?" Sirius questioned. "Are you really, really sure?"

"You're not that guy," Harry chided.

"I don't know," Sirius argued, shaking off the pain in his big toe. "I think I can change. I hear good things about evil."

"Stupid Masters getting stupider," Kreacher muttered and lazily stomping away disrespectfully. "Bringing muggle filth into the noble and most ancient House of Black."

Harry narrowed his eyes as Kreacher began to walk away. He turned to Sirius, "But I think it might be time we started punishing the racist little wanker."

"Kreacher, come here!" Sirius happily called out. He asked Harry, "Want see who kick him further? We can start from the top of the stairs. You get a bonus kick if he hits the umbrella stand."

"No, no," Harry said motioning with his hand. "That's not the sort of punishment I had in mind."

Kreacher had reluctantly walked back up to Harry and Sirius, mumbling, "Blood traitors don't even know how to punish right."

"Kreacher," Harry ordered. "That sort of language will no longer be tolerated."

Kreacher gnashed his teeth before smirking cheekily and explaining, "Sorry Master. Kreacher only speaks English."

Sirius looked at Harry and offered, "I'll let you kick first."

Harry shook his head. "That's the kind of negative treatment he expects. No, Kreacher, you are going to gently massage my feet while I read to you notable facts about muggle history."

"What?" Kreacher said looking at Harry in confusion.

"Oh," Sirius said thinking deviously. "You know, I've got some underwear that needs to be cleaned…"

"Perhaps by hand?" Harry suggested. "Of course no magic should be used at all with delicates."

Sirius rubbed his chin in thought. "I was thinking tongue-washing actually."

Kreacher was looking at them fearfully. "But… but… not even mudbloods-"

"That's another thing," Harry interjected. "We're not going stand for those slurs anymore. Every time you use words like mudblood, muggle filth, blood traitor, anything like that…" Harry paused, thinking up something appropriate. "For every derogatory implication, you have to make a child smile."

Kreacher paled while Sirius was clearly impressed.

Harry continued. "We'll transfigure you into a midget and take you to a muggle park. If we hear you say mudblood three times, that's three kids you're going to make smile and laugh."

Kreacher whispered in horror. "You wouldn't…"

"You think I'm bluffing?" Harry said staring the elf down.

"But…" Kreacher argued. "The young ones… they have all the diseases."

"That's one," Harry said raising a finger. "Looks like we're going to the park tomorrow. You want to go for two?"

"No!" Kreacher shrieked. "Kreacher will be good."

Sirius smiled at Harry. "Well that was a quick improvement in attitude. I figured you'd have to obliviate him."

Kreacher turned to Harry in surprise. "You know how to memory charm house elves?"

"Obliviate," Harry quickly cast on the elf. "Sirius, don't even mention that around him."

Kreacher was just standing there with a glassy eyed stare.

Sirius gently nudged the elf to make sure he was okay.

Kreacher jerked into awareness and said, "Please don't make Kreacher be nice to mud-…ggles."

Sirius shrugged happily. "I guess the memory charm works."

"Obliviate," Harry immediate recast on Kreacher. He pointed his finger at Sirius, "That's one for you, buddy!"

"Me?" Sirius argued. "Why do I… Actually, I don't mind making a kid or two smile."

"Good," Harry said. "Because you're still going to be transfigured into a midget. And Remus and Tonks are invited and encouraged to bring cameras."

Sirius paled and insisted. "Hey now, that's not fair."

"Hello?" A loud call came from down the hall. "Anyone there?"

"Mistress," Kreacher said just as he popped away.

Harry and Sirius had both turned in the direction of the call, having recognized Bellatrix's voice. Harry looked at his godfather, "You ready to get her story?"

Sirius nodded. "Yeah. I'm sick of worrying about whose on bitch-sitting duty."

"It feels wrong keeping her locked in a room," Harry agreed.

"I know what you mean," Sirius said with a nod. "It's just not right to keep a grown woman locked in a room, unless you're using her for sex."

"No Sirius," Harry said with a roll of his eyes. "That would feel wrong too."

The two of them went to Bellatrix's door and knocked.

"Come in," she replied as the two Lord Blacks walked into her room. "Am I going to be a prisoner here forever?"

Sirius grabbed the chair by her desk while Harry pulled out the recliner he kept in his shrunken trunk. "Nope," Harry answered plopping down, ignoring the strange look from Bellatrix. "It's time we figured out what to do with you."

Bellatrix sat on the edge of her bed. "I know you both don't like me, and I can never repay what you've done for me-"

"You don't owe us anything other than loyalty to the family," Sirius interjected.

"And before we decide anything," Harry said. "You need to give us some answers."

Bellatrix swallowed but earnestly offered, "What do you want to know?"

Sirius looked at Harry, allowing him to take the lead.

"Well," Harry said. "You could start with why you joined the Death Eaters and why you wanted out."

Bellatrix looked at Harry in confusion. "Why I joined? I don't know where you two fit into the Black family considering you certainly weren't on any family tapestry I've ever seen, but we were all raised to be servants of the Dark Lord. Asking why I joined is like asking why I'm a witch."

"Does that mean you toe the party line on blood status?" Harry inquired. "Kill the unworthy, enslave the unpure, yada, yada, yada."

"I honestly don't care," Bellatrix shrugged indifferently. "If you want me to start wearing muggle clothes that say 'Hug a Muggle,' I will. If you want me to start hunting down the half-bloods dirtying proper wizarding society, I know some pretty good curses. But I've never been a dedicated true believer like my brother-in-law."

"Malfoy will believe anything that says he's better than everyone else," Sirius retorted. "It's probably why he'll be wrong his entire life."

Bellatrix smiled lightly. "You won't be hearing me defend Lucius anytime soon."

"Yes well," Harry chided. "As useless tools go, Lucius Malfoy is a half-inch strap-on."

Sirius shook his head. "You're probably giving him a quarter-inch too much credit."

"Alright then," Harry said attempting to get back on topic. "So your heart wasn't really in the Death Eating business. That's not exactly enough reason to openly and actively defy them. You know they're going to want you dead. So why'd you want out?"

Bellatrix took a moment to look at her Lords before uncertainly replying, "I don't know what you want me to say."

"Did something happen?" Harry asked. "Was there some life-changing event that opened your eyes to the atrocities of the world and jaded you on everything you previously held up as unwavering truth?"

"Did they rape you, beat you, kill your favorite pet muggle?" Sirius asked. "Anything?"

"Nah," Bellatrix shook her head. "Sorry. Nothing like that. I wasn't punished anymore than any other Death Eater. I never tried to draw attention to myself or work my way up the chain of command. I killed when I supposed to kill, I tortured when I was supposed to torture. Though I suppose I did try to hide how much fun those parts can be."

Harry wasn't sure but he thought he saw her eyes twinkling.

"No one tried to force you into marriage?" Sirius asked curiously.

Bellatrix smirked. "There aren't many witches of my pedigree still single at my age, but I never let anyone touch me that I didn't want to."

"And if you did want them to touch you?" Sirius flirtatiously retorted.

Bellatrix sat up prouder, straightening her shoulders and thrusting her chest out. "I am a Black and can be very alluring when I want to be."

Harry glanced over at Sirius and sighed.

"Oww!" Sirius shrieked slapping a hand over each eye. "Both eyes, Harry! Really? Was that necessary?"

Harry ignored his godfather and turned back to Bellatrix. "I still don't get why you'd want to go from laying low avoiding attention to Dark Lord enemy number… four or five maybe."

Bellatrix took a deep breath and shyly admitted, "I guess it was seeing my nephew, Draco."

"Ahh," Harry nodded. "I'd want to get the hell away too."

Sirius snickered in approval.

"Umm, actually," Bellatrix corrected, "he was more a reminder that I can't put off having a child forever."

"See? Nothing wrong with family," Sirius jumped in before thinking of Draco. "Well, usually."

Harry ignored Sirius while looking at Bellatrix as if she were crazy, which was entirely possible. "Seeing Draco made you want kids?"

Bellatrix nodded.

"What the hell kind of kid do you want? A transsexual quintaped?"

"No!" Bellatrix quickly corrected. "I don't want a kid like Draco. Good god, no. Draco's wife Pansy is expecting, which means my sister is about to be a grandmother."

Harry whistled in relief. "Okay, that makes a lot more sense."

"But I don't want my kid to grow up a Death Eater the way I did," Bellatrix explained. "I've been waiting for the Dark Lord to conquer Britain or be destroyed. Two things I'm not so sure will ever happen. And then you guys came along…"

Harry nodded and finished for her, "offering you a way out from the Death Eaters."

"Well, yeah, that too," Bellatrix said looking up in surprise. "But I was also hoping one of you would let me carry and raise your heir."

Harry froze in place and now knew for sure she was completely insane in this world too.

Sirius who had been in the process of checking her out once again, stopped suddenly. He got to his feet saying, "I'm out of here," and calmly left the room.

"You could be as active or absent in our child's life as you like," Bellatrix pleaded as Sirius walked away. "I just want to be a mother. I don't even care if it's a squib!"

"You," Harry began but couldn't say anything further. "You…" he tried and failed again.

"I can be your consort, your mistress, or just the mother to your child," Bellatrix begged. "I'm not picky."

"Stop," Harry said unable to look up. "Just… stop."

"I realize you both hate me for some reason," Bellatrix tried. "So I don't mind if you want to get rough with me. Just don't hurt the womb."

Harry got up and left the room sighing. "Fucking nutty purebloods."

Bellatrix was again alone, still locked in her room. "That could have gone better," she said to no one in particular.

She fell backwards onto her bed and stared up at the ceiling. After about five minutes of quiet contemplation, she called out, "Hey guys?"

When there was no response, she tried again, "My Lords?"

"Harry?" She yelled. "Sirius?" She forlornly continued, "Anyone?"

Harry opened her door and asked, "What?"

"I won't bring up the subject you obviously don't want to talk about," Bellatrix assured him. "But can I at least leave this room? I promise not to go anywhere without permission or an escort, I'm just sick of-"

"Yeah," Harry interrupted her. He grabbed a hold of the anchor stones on her doorway and brought the warding magic crashing down. "Come on. We still need to talk and we can do that in the kitchen."

Bellatrix followed Harry out of her room. They walked past the muggle room, where Sirius was focused intently on the large television screen in front of him.

"You take your reproductive organs and just keep moving," Sirius harshly ordered while hitting buttons on the remote, not even glancing towards her.

Bellatrix hurried after Harry down the stairs, quietly commenting, "I can't do anything right by you guys, can I?"

Harry briefly looked back at her before continuing to the kitchen. "You want something to drink?"

"Whatever you're drinking is fine," Bellatrix replied. She walked over towards the window and saw it was a sunny day. "You mind talking outside?"

Harry only then realized she'd gone from cursed, to the hospital, to tortured, to locked in a room, to the courtroom, and back to locked in her room. "Yeah," Harry said pouring her a large glass of firewhiskey and one for himself. "Outside works for me."

Harry scourgified a bench in the enclosed back yard and sat down while Bellatrix just meandered through the dried leaves and tall grass. Harry began, "Let me just make this part clear first. Neither I nor Sirius will be providing you an heir so don't ask. But as you said, you are a Black and I suspect there will be no shortage of volunteers to helping you out with that."

"I'd like it to be someone you approve of," Bellatrix responded while staring up into the sky. She turned to look at Harry. "Because my child will be a Black and it'd be nice if you liked him or her."

"Nothing like a clinical screening process of potential sperm donors to start the day," Harry said sipping his firewhiskey. "Okay. We can talk about baby batter later. But I need some background information from you."

Bellatrix sighed. "You want to know all the people I've killed?"

Harry winced. "No. Well, maybe I'm a little curious but… no. Yeah… no. No. I don't want to know."

"What then?"

"In case you've not caught on," Harry explained. "Sirius and I aren't originally from around here. And I need to know what sort of Death Eaters are going to be out for your blood, what resources your former Master has at his command, pretty much everything the Wizengamot and DMLE wanted to know."

Bellatrix nodded, expecting as much. "Should I start anywhere in particular?"

Harry sat his glass of firewhiskey down. "Why hasn't Voldemort been more successful? Is the Ministry that on top of things? Or the Order of the Phoenix?"

"The Ministry's clueless," Bellatrix explained. "And Dumbledore's group gets more credit than they deserve. No, the Dark Lord's nemesis is a wizard working from the shadows."

"Neville Longbottom?" Harry suggested.

Bellatrix shrugged. "No one knows. We always referred to him as that fucker."

"That fucker?" Harry repeated with a chuckle. "I suppose that's catchier than You-Know-Who."

"Who?"

"Never mind," Harry said. "So who is that fucker? Or what do you know about him?"

"That's just it," Bellatrix said. "Hardly anything is known about that fucker. He just appears when he wants to and then takes down just about everyone."

"Everyone?"

"Not all at once or anything. He doesn't take on twenty wizards but when he shows up, he usually quickly asserts control of the situation. Stunning, disabling, and sometimes crippling some very good duelers."

"He doesn't kill?"

"Not often," Bellatrix replied. "Everyone knows he could, and he has killed a few that have irked him, but I'd guess most of the time it's just not worth killing to him."

"Do the Death Eaters fear him?"

Bellatrix nodded seriously. "The Dark Lord fears him, though he'd never admit it. I only saw him really go all out once. The Dark Lord, along Sidney Nott, Andreas Rollins, and the Gibson twins, summoned a demon. The summoning circle drained them all, and there were several of us on hand to protect them after the calling ritual.

"The demon split both Gibsons in two before anyone realized what was happening. Then that fucker appeared and just happened to have a lasso capable of holding a demon long enough for him to behead it."

Harry whistled, thankful he never had to do that. "And that required him going all out?"

"Beheading a demon will kill it," Bellatrix said, "but not right away. And they never go quietly. The Dark Lord was injured. Nott and Rollins were killed, but that fucker was the only one keeping up with the headless demon."

"So he was helping out?" Harry asked curiously.

Bellatrix shook her head. "The Dark Lord knew what he was doing when he summoned that thing. But see that's just it. That fucker seems better informed than any Death Eater of what the Dark Lord's plans are."

Harry resisted the urge to rub his curse scar thinking about how he had picked up on some of his Voldemort's plans. "And Voldemort doesn't know why or how?"

Bellatrix shrugged. "The first few years after that fucker started appearing, the Dark Lord was furious. Then he started acting more carefully and obsessed over figuring out the unknown wizard. He tried to contact him, even put some hidden messages into the Daily Prophet. Now that fucker is just the albatross he can't shake."

"Twenty years and he knows nothing about this guy?"

"It hasn't been quite that long," Bellatrix corrected. "And it's not like the Dark Lord would tell me what he knows about that fucker."

Harry was sitting there wondering if the mystery wizard could have been hit by a Killing Curse and gained a link to the Dark Lord. "Is there anything you can tell me about him?"

"Well, I don't know if he still suspects this, but for a while the Dark Lord was convinced that fucker was hoping to take his place and become a new Dark Lord."

Harry didn't even try to hide his sigh. "You think that fucker will care about your shift in loyalties?"

Bellatrix shook her head. "I doubt it. He's only ever seemed to care about the Dark Lord, but as far as I know they've never really gotten into a serious duel. Not like you two did with him."

Harry started nursing his firewhiskey again in an effort to hide the smile on his face. Harry gave up trying to devise a clever way to inquire and just outright asked, "Do you know if the Dark Lord has ever hit that fucker with a Killing Curse?"

Bellatrix looked at Harry oddly. "I hardly think that's something he'd keep to himself. Why? Do you have reason to believe he's dead?"

"Forget it," Harry said quickly changing the subject. "Is the Dark Lord based out of Little Hangleton?"

Bellatrix jerked her head up and nodded. "That's where one of the most heavily warded safe houses is. How did you know that?"

"Lucky guess," Harry retorted. "And he probably keeps Nagini close by when he's there?"

Bellatrix furrowed her brow. "Who's Nagini?"

"The Dark Lord's familiar?" Harry offered. "Large venomous snake?"

She slowly shook her head. "As far as I know, he doesn't have a familiar. I've seen him talk to snakes, but not kept as pets."

"Huh," Harry said, having not expected that.

"Although," Bellatrix said. "There are rumors that he's got a monster at his command in the forest behind the Riddle house."

"A monster?"

Bellatrix shrugged. "He expressly forbade everyone from going into that forest. A couple Death Eaters supposedly have, but they might have just disappeared or been quietly killed. I've heard sounds in there, sounds of something big, but it is a forest so…"

"You don't think," Harry was musing out loud and stopped himself from saying too much.

"I don't think what?" Bellatrix asked.

Harry was saved from answering as a crack announced the arrival of Remus Lupin.

"Harry!" Remus greeted. "You're okay." He turned and saw the woman standing near the large gnarled tree. "And you're not alone."

"It hasn't been that long since I last saw you, Moony," Harry greeted.

"Yes, well," Remus held his tongue in front of the former Death Eater. "You've caused quite a stir since then."

"Remus," Harry stood up to give a proper introduction. "This is Bellatrix Black. Bellatrix, this is Remus Lupin."

"We've met," Remus guardedly stated. "Though last time I saw you, I believe you were wearing a mask."

Bellatrix resisted the urge to snap back. She snootily retorted, "Do not presume that every Death Eater you've crossed has been me, werewolf."

"Bellatrix," Harry said softly as one of his magical arms reached out and grabbed her chin, turning her head to look straight at him. "You should know I grew up with a pretty crappy excuse for a family. So just be aware, that the lengths I'll go to, to protect family, are nothing compared to what I'll do to defend my friends. Are we clear?"

Bellatrix swallowed the lump her in throat as the photo of the broken Dark Lord flashed in her head. "Yes, my Lord. Forgive me. I'm still… relearning my place in the family."

She felt Harry's hand release her and she turned towards Remus. "I don't think an apology for my past will mean anything to you, Remus. But my loyalty is to the family now. And you raised a Black, so you have my respect."

"Hmm," Remus murmured while glancing at Harry. "There may be hope for you yet, Bellatrix. I still remember a witch at Hogwarts who was one of the few Slytherins who could take a joke."

"That's right," Harry realized. "You two went to school together."

Remus nodded and asked, "Is Sirius around?"

"He was pouting in the muggle room last I saw," Harry waved towards the back door. "The wards are back to normal, so you can go on in."

Remus nodded curtly towards Bellatrix and walked into the back entrance.

"The half-breed!" Kreacher shouted as Remus walked in.

"That's two!" Harry yelled loudly, staring at the elf.

Kreacher let out a frightened 'eep' and popped away.

Harry turned back and saw Bellatrix looked meek and subservient again.

"It's weird to hear him ask about Sirius," Bellatrix quietly explained, "when it's a different Sirius entirely."

Harry was again able to avoid a risky topic of conversation, this time by the arrival of an owl. It flew down and perched on the edge of the bench, sticking out its leg towards Harry.

He cast the usual oculamagi spell over his eyes and saw there was nothing magical about the letter at all. He untied it from the owl, who settled in to wait patiently for a reply. He saw the letter was addressed to Lord Harry Black and Lord Sirius Black. When he opened it, he didn't recognize the feminine hand-writing and skipped down to the bottom to see who it was from.

Harry's eyes widened and he couldn't avoid the emotional response at seeing so casual a signature of Lily Potter. "Fuck."

"Who's it from?" Bellatrix asked curiously, keeping her distance so as not to intrude.

Harry looked up at Bellatrix and back down at the letter, feeling as though his life was a surreal experiment. He quickly read through the missive and answered, "It's an invitation to dinner from the Potters."

Bellatrix weakly laughed. "Speak of the devil."

"What's that supposed to mean?" Harry said looking at Bellatrix accusingly.

Bellatrix held up her hands indicating she was implying nothing derogatory. "First Lupin, then I was thinking about Sirius Black, and now Potter too?" she explained. She looked off into space as old memories surfaced. "You know I was there that night."

Harry looked up curiously. "What?"

"The Potter house on Halloween, '81," Bellatrix explained. She saw Harry's look and quickly added, "I didn't attack my cousin or anything. There were a couple dozen of us waiting in the wings, but the Dark Lord wanted to do the job personally. I saw him kill Sirius and retrieve the baby Potter. He severed Sirius' skull from his spine and cleaned it off while the baby just kept crying."

Harry was just gaped at her, unable to believe what he was hearing.

"I'm sorry," Bellatrix said noticing Harry's expression. "You don't want to hear this."

"No," Harry immediately answered. "I do. I just… so what did he do with… the baby? He's not still alive, is he?" Harry was momentarily wondering about that fucker.

"No," Bellatrix blurted out before hesitating. She sighed and continued. "I left before it was done, but he held Sirius' skull in one hand, while he cradled the baby in his arm. He used his free hand then to… well, it was some sort of ritual. Whatever it was, it was ancient dark magic. Nothing I recognized. Just before I left the Potter kid finally stopped screaming."

"I later heard that he'd drained the life from the area, turning the nearest tree into a skeleton and staining the ground permanently," Bellatrix admitted with an unconcerned shrug. "I reckon he wanted to make an example of a potential subject of his prophecy. Of course, I didn't know about the prophecy then. Hmm," Bellatrix mused. "You know, that might have been when my disinterest in the lifestyle really started."

Harry was sitting there clenching the letter in one hand and listening to her in horror. He didn't need to know this. He really didn't need to know that Sirius' skull was a Horcrux. And he really didn't need to know it was made from the cold-blooded murder of his infant alter ego.

Bellatrix saw Harry looked a bit rattled by her tale and added, "Yeah, you may just want to take a pass on that dinner. The Dark Lord's ritual effects are probably still there, whatever it was he did."

Harry just listened to her calm tone and was clueless how to respond to this. He stared at her without blinking for the better part of a minute before agreeing, "Yeah. No dinner." He knocked back the rest of his firewhiskey and stood up banishing all the negative thoughts from his mind. He looked at his watch and saw it was still well before midday. "I'm going to go get drunk." He stopped and turned back, "Do me a favor, and never mention this to Sirius."

Bellatrix nodded in acceptance and watched the typically more composed of her two Lords walk away. She looked over at the owl still perched on the bench. "It may take him a little while to reply to that letter."

The owl turned to look at her and hooted softly having figured that out on its own.

"Know any good jokes?"

The owl tilted its head, wondering if it was safe around the strange woman.

"Or perhaps a powerful wizard willing to impregnate me?"

The owl had made its decision and flew off to wait in the tree where it would be safer.

Bellatrix sighed. "Yeah, I get that a lot."

Remus sat his beer down, looking at Harry incredulously. "How could you not have known? You saw Sirius leave with her identical twin sister just ten minutes earlier."

Sirius was laughing heartily while his godson embarrassingly picked at the label on his beer bottle.

"It's not like I hadn't been drinking or anything," Harry explained. "And in my defense, Sirius' girl was wearing a lot of whorish makeup."

"Hey," Sirius snapped. He paused and scratched his chin in thought. "I do like the whorish makeup, don't I?"

"Padfoot," Remus reminded. "You've always had a clown fetish."

Sirius choked on his beer. "You swore to never tell!"

"Different Remus, different Sirius," Remus said with a smirk, finishing off his beer. He stood up and announced, "This time it is my turn."

"No, last round was your turn," Sirius grumbled.

Remus ignored him, asking, "You guys want the same?"

Harry and Sirius both nodded and took a look around the muggle bar, taking notice of the single women.

"You're not worried about leaving her alone?" Sirius asked, knowing Harry knew exactly who he was talking about.

Harry shook his head. "She was going in disguise to her storage space. She packed up and stashed everything important before she showed up at Grimmauld Place. And besides, I gave her some homework to do."

Sirius finished off the last of his beer and set the empty bottle down. "Homework?"

Harry smiled. "She's making a list of every Death Eater, including all known homes, maps, protections, wards, house elves, the works."

Sirius scoffed. "Won't she find that a bit suspicious?"

"Maybe," Harry admitted. "But I was very insistent that if she gets captured and kidnapped, we're going to need to know the layouts of Death Eaters' homes. Keeping that information to herself is just an unnecessary risk."

"Right," Sirius chuckled.

"And of course we also need to know the locations of valuables for leverage or ransom," Harry added. He thought it over in his head and realized that even Goyle would have been suspicious. "Besides it saves us a lot of ground work and she's sworn loyalty."

"Malfoy?"

Harry shook his head. "She's not keyed in."

"Damn," Sirius swore as Remus returned with three more beers.

"Are we discussing your new houseguest?" Remus asked.

"We were," Harry said accepting the beer from Remus. "But let's not anymore. How's work going, Moony?"

"Same old, same old," Remus said. "Another upgrade was forced on our customers so we've been swamped with calls. I guess the head office was worried that some people were beginning to like our products."

"Tsk, tsk," Sirius chided. "Your talents are wasted at that place. Don't you think it's time you looked into getting a more productive job?"

"Sirius?" Remus said in between sips of his beer. "You're going to lecture me on my vocation? You?"

"Someone has to," Sirius retorted.

"My job doesn't come with a significant risk of a prison sentence," Remus argued. "I think career-wise I'm in a little better place than you right now."

Harry jumped in. "I hate to say it, but I agree with Padfoot."

"Thank you," Sirius cheered. "Face it, Moony. You don't have to financially support Tonks, your home is paid for, any emergencies come up and we've got your back. And you tell me, which does more good for the world: annoying muggles on the phone or re-appropriating a certain group's resources?"

Remus raised a curious eyebrow. "You want me to join you two in your illicit affairs?"

Sirius' eyes widened and Harry snapped, "He didn't mean it like that, Sirius. I know, the moustache confuses me too sometimes."

"Hey," Remus frowned. "Cheap shot."

"And no," Harry continued. "That's not what we're saying."

"Yeah," Sirius agreed. "We thought of it first. We got dibs."

"Actually," Harry corrected. "I was more thinking that we're nobility and can weasel our way out of most things, but with your affliction you'd get raked across the coals if we were ever caught in any sort of compromising situation."

"Not to mention it's fundamentally immoral and wrong," Remus added.

"Details," Harry said waving off Remus' argument. "What Sirius and I are saying though is that you have more options and freedom now to find something a bit more fulfilling."

Remus tipped back his beer, mulling their words over. He admitted, "Tonks has been getting on my case about this too."

"Smart girl, that one," Harry agreed.

"And a wildcat in the," Sirius paused at Remus' warning growl, "…battlefield."

"Don't even go there," Remus said staring at Sirius. "Pack instincts got nothing on parental ones."

"Ugh," Harry said slouching in his seat. "That reminds me."

Sirius quickly asked, "Of the time you and Tonks-OWW!" Sirius grabbed his eye.

"Don't go there, Sirius," Harry said earning an approving nod from Remus. "You know the rules. If Tonks is around then you can joke about the number of times my dipstick has checked her oil, but not with only Daddy here."

"I don't even get that muggle reference and I'm disgusted," Remus said rubbing his temples.

"Well on my motorcycle," Sirius began to explain using his hands to demonstrate. "The dipstick goes in the-"

"Stop," Remus said and pleading with Harry. "What were you reminded of?"

Harry frowned. "Your mention of parental instincts reminded me that we received a letter."

"Oh you got that?" Remus said happily.

"What letter?" Sirius asked.

"It was from… Lily Potter," Harry said. "Inviting us to dinner at Godric's Hollow."

"School's in session so it'll have to be a weekend," Remus explained. "And as long as it's not a full moon I'll be there, and of course, Tonks, and Lord Potter."

"We're not going," Harry firmly said.

"Oh thank Merlin," Sirius exclaimed in relief.

"What? No," Remus frowned. "You have to."

Harry shook his head. "I really should just keep my distance from her as much as possible."

"But it'll be so much fun," Remus pleaded. "And you know James will be uncomfortable."

"That is true," Sirius realized beginning to agree.

Harry looked at his godfather. "If you want, you can go."

"If I'm going, you're going," Sirius insisted.

"I'm not going," Harry repeated. "You saw what happened at St. Mungo's. That'd just raise way too many questions I'd rather never answer."

"Never?" Remus asked worriedly. "You're never going to tell them who you really are?"

Harry shrugged. "Maybe eventually but there are… more issues than you realize."

"There always are with you," Sirius agreed. "Wait, what issues?"

"Ones I'd prefer never to think about," Harry quietly admitted. "And are unavoidable every time I'm near her."

"You're really not going to dinner?" Remus asked.

"Really," Harry assured him, "No."

"Guess we're not going," Sirius echoed. "Now if you gentlemen will excuse me, I see a delightfully delectable derriere in dire and desperate need of deep… care and affection."

Harry followed Sirius' line of sight and saw a pair of attractive women at the bar, one of whom was caught looking right at his godfather before turning away.

Remus and Harry were left alone at the table while Sirius went and turned on the charm. Remus smiled. "Once a scamp, always a scamp, huh?"

"Yup," Harry agreed, while keeping an eye on Sirius.

"So what sort of career change would you suggest?" Remus asked.

"No idea," Harry asked. "What do you want to do?"

"My options are limited by my condition," Remus explained. "It's not the sort of thing you can hide, needing every full moon off. And not too many people would hire me for that reason."

Harry suddenly had a bright idea and wondered why he'd not considered it. "You like pranks, right?"

"Professional pranking is not a job," Remus answered. "As Sirius was heartbroken to discover in his fifth year meeting with Professor McGonagall."

"Naw," Harry said. "I meant because I have it on good authority that Weasleys' Wizarding Wheezes is going to be expanding significantly. Bigger store in Diagon Alley and a second branch in Hogsmeade."

Remus perked up. "Weasleys are good people. Fred and George help out the Order. You think they'd be willing to work around full moons?"

Harry nodded. "I suspect when you tell them your nickname they'll be more than happy to."

"My nickname?"

Harry smiled. "If they grew up anything like the twins I used to know, their livelihood during school was in large part thanks to a certain map they nicked from Filch's office."

"Really?" Remus said thinking it over.

"It doesn't hurt that me and Sirius are their new financial backers," Harry added. "Tell you what, you're not working tomorrow, right?"

Remus shook his head.

"I need to go to Diagon Alley and buy an animagus potion." Harry suggested, "We'll drop by, visit the twins, see if you have any interest in working with them, or they have any positions for you and go from there. If you want, you can crash at our place and we'll go in the morning."

"Yeah," Remus agreed. "Sounds like a plan."

"Hang on," Harry said looking towards Sirius. "Come with me, Remus. Sirius needs backup."

"What?" Remus said jumping to his feet. "Is it Death Eaters?"

"Settle down!" Harry harshly whispered. "And no, it's not Death Eaters. It's a Betty with an overprotective friend."

Remus looked at Harry incredulously.

"You need to get laid, Moony," Harry said as he began to walk over towards the bar. Sirius was on a stool talking to a pretty girl on his left. To the girl's left was the overprotective friend, and to that friend's left was a guy sitting alone, seemingly there just to drink. The seat next to the man was empty, and Harry went straight for it.

Remus sighed at Harry's statement and followed after him. "Tonks has been on my case about that too."

"Like I said," Harry repeated. "Smart girl." Harry took the only empty stool while Remus was left standing awkwardly.

"Maybe I should-"

"Don't go anywhere," Harry ordered him. "This will take just a second."

"There aren't any more stools," Remus was whispering to Harry. Harry was just smirking up at Remus while sending an invisible magical arm out.

The overprotective female friend yelped and turned to the unknown man in between her and Harry. She slapped him soundly across the face. "You keep your hands off me, you bastard!"

The confused man was rubbing his rapidly reddening cheek. "But… I didn't-"

Harry had stood up and placed a warning hand on the man's shoulder. "I think you've had enough."

"Seriously," the man pleaded. "I didn't do-"

"If you want," Harry said while keeping a tight grip on the man. "There's an empty table right over there where you won't bother this young lady."

The man knocked back the rest of his drink and got up. "Forget it. I'm out of here." He stumbled his way out the door.

Harry sat back on his own stool and waved towards the empty spot. "Take a seat, Remus, before another drunken lout starts groping this fine damsel."

Remus was biting his tongue, knowing full well what had happened and sat down. He saw the other girl by Sirius was looking their way and Sirius was behind her flashing a bright grin and a thumbs up. Remus felt Harry poking him repeatedly in the side and finally turned to the woman next to him, asking, "Can I buy you a drink?"

"Sure," she agreed, leaving her friend alone to deal with Sirius' undoubtedly classless advances.

Harry kept one eye on Sirius and Remus, while looking around the bar. He heard the two older Marauders and the two women getting on splendidly when he spotted an attractive brunette standing near the door. "If you'll excuse me a moment," Harry said getting up and going over to talk to her.

Remus and Sirius nodded at Harry, while the two women obliviously continued on their conversations. Remus had barely time to order a drink before Harry was back again.

"Gentlemen," Harry said to Sirius and Remus. "I'm going to head on home. Don't do anything I wouldn't do."

The two women giggled ferociously, leaving Harry to think Sirius and Remus might be making a break for it pretty soon.

"Night, Harry," Sirius said wincing at the sound of the women's laughter.

Remus saw Harry throw his arm over the brunette and leave the bar, amazed at how quickly the young man worked.

Sirius and Remus continued to chat up the two women who it seemed loved the sound of their own voices. Remus had taken Sirius' advice and was hoping more alcohol would make them sound better.

It wasn't working.

Another twenty minutes and two drinks later the women said they had to leave. Given the option both Sirius and Remus declined the offers of walking them home choosing to stay for another drink instead.

Remus could tell he was quite drunk, and given the volume of Sirius' voice when he talked, he was too. But neither could believe their luck when a gorgeous pair of twins sat down and joined them in drinking. They were having a far better time, or perhaps, Remus mused, they were just drunk enough to not know any better. Approximately an hour later, the twins, Sirius, and Remus were all totally inebriated and began walking back to Grimmauld Place.

Remus was in slightly better shape than Sirius, or at least than Sirius was acting, because the elder Lord Black had a twin under each arm, helping him up the stairs. It was only after they both helped Sirius back towards his master bedroom that Remus realized the twins were a package deal and they were going with Sirius.

Sirius came back out into the hallway where Remus was standing in disappointed surprise. "Sorry Moony, but… twins!"

"It's fine," Remus said.

"It's better than fine," Sirius cheered, glancing back and noticing they were both making themselves at home in his bed.

"I'm just gonna crash in one of the guest rooms," Remus assured him, noticing he was slurring his words and feeling exhaustion replace his nervous excitement.

"Yeah, of course," Sirius said. "Just don't…" Sirius stopped when his drunken mind came to a truly brilliant conclusion, realizing he could have his twins and maybe get Remus laid after all. "Third door on the right. That's the cleanest guest room in the whole house."

"Thanks Padfoot. Have fun," Remus tiredly agreed and walked down the hall. He opened the door and didn't even feel like turning on the light. He closed the door behind him, stripped out of his clothes, and crawled into the large inviting bed. He idly noticed that it did smell quite nice and was surprisingly warm and soft.

Chapter 16

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"Again?" Remus mumbled in his half-conscious and half-drunken state. "You're insatiable."

"Well," Bellatrix said mounting the werewolf for the third time that early morning. "I figure the more shots fired, the better the odds at least one will hit the bullseye."

"I could've sworn I heard you hitting the bullseye a couple times there," Remus mumbled in peaceful enjoyment as his body fell into familiar rhythmic gyrations.

"I don't know if it's true or not," Bellatrix explained as she got comfortable and arched her back, keeping a steady determined pace. "But I heard that orgasms increase the chances of conception. So don't mind my diddling."

Remus' eyes snapped wide open. He looked up and saw Bellatrix's attractive nude form bouncing above him. "Oh god."

He looked down and saw where their hips were joined, creating regular fleshy thwacking sounds. "Oh god."

"Already?" Bellatrix asked, increasing her pace.

Remus slapped his hands over his face. "This is a nightmare. It can't hurt me. It's not real. I just need to focus on waking up. Wake up... Wake up now... Wake up now..."

Bellatrix sighed, but hadn't stopped bouncing up and down on Remus. "I don't know why everybody hates me so much around here."

"You're raping me, right now," Remus snapped, resting his hands on her thighs.

"Don't be so dramatic," Bellatrix chided, shifting her weight forward so she could look him in the eye. All the while her rhythmic bouncing continued. "Besides, do you even want me to stop 'raping' you?"

Remus was meeting her bounces with thrusts of his own. He frowned uncertainly. "I'm a little conflicted on that point."

Bellatrix was grateful she could count on most men to act like the idiots they really were. "You don't feel very conflicted."

"I'm a complex man."

"You feel thick. And meaty."

Remus kept bouncing her in place. "Well… thank you."

Bellatrix nodded civilly. "You're welco-"

"No!" Remus yelled, beginning to come to his senses. "No, no!"

"Dammit," Bellatrix cursed, trying to keep going. "I thought your brain might've been catching up in the race for blood flow."

"Get off of me," Remus said lifting Bellatrix bodily as he hurriedly wiggled away from her and out of the bed. He looked around and realized he was naked, not to mention visibly saluting a superior officer. He grabbed a pillow to temporarily cover himself. "What the hell is going on?"

Bellatrix sensed his confusion. "Were you bewitched?"

"Ohh," Remus said slapping one hand to his forehead while the other held his pillow in place. "Headache. Hangover headache."

"I can think of one good way to lessen the pressure in your head by easing the blood flow."

"No!" Remus snapped back at her. He once again was distracted by the slight sheen of sweat covering her very firm and nude body. "Well, maybe…" Remus shook his head and banged on the side of it. "No! Tell me what's going on."

Bellatrix looked at him curiously. "You really don't-"

Remus eyes' widened in remembrance. "And what the fudge were you saying about conception?"

Bellatrix was about to scold him for interrupting but was distracted. "Fudge? Did you just say fu-"

"You're after my sperm!" Remus gasped and pointed.

Bellatrix gestured airily. "Well, that's kind of the-"

"Hang on," Remus interrupted again. "That doesn't make any sense."

Bellatrix was getting irritated. "Will you stop interrupt-"

"I remember before the first time, you cast charms on your happy place. I assumed they were contraceptive charms," Remus said scratching his head as he was beginning to piece together the reality of this morning.

"Oh so now you rememb-"

"But why would you cast contraceptive charms?" Remus repeated and stopped. He seemed almost hesitant to muse aloud, "Unless you were harvesting my sperm for… later?"

Bellatrix didn't say a word, denying him the opportunity of interrupting her again.

"Don't you have anything to say?"

Bellatrix huffed. "I was under the impression my Lords had selected a father for my child and you were here to fulfill that obligation."

Remus was still feeling the effects of the previous evening's alcohol and when he processed what Bellatrix said, he assumed he was having some sort of hallucination. He stumbled and stuttered his way through a few unfinished thoughts. He decided to disregard her last statement and got back to the simpler matter at hand. "Why are you even in my room?"

Bellatrix looked around the room. "This is my room. You crawled into my bed while I was asleep. When I awoke, you were poking me in the back with that thing."

Remus' breathing was labored, processing his last conscious thoughts before waking up in a sex dream, which turned out to be a lot of sex and not much dream. "But Sirius said," Remus stopped and he jumped back shouting, "SIRIUS! I'm going to kill him."

Bellatrix was leaning against the headboard and had pulled her knees up. "So we're really not going to give it another shot?"

"No!" Remus yelled at her. "I…" He trailed off as he watched Bellatrix slide down the bed, lay on her back and pull her legs up.

Bellatrix was rocking back and forth on her back. She remembered something about utilizing gravity and relaxed muscles to improve the odds when she saw Remus staring at her. "Just trying to help the process along." She saw he wasn't moving but was staring at her naked body. She pointed towards her crotch, "Feel free to jump in, if you want."

Remus could feel a twinge of desire igniting in his stomach. He turned, bending over quickly and vomited all over the floor.

"Now that's just rude," Bellatrix said, still doing her unusual rocking in hopes it would help with conception.

Remus was panting, not even caring that he was spitting on the floor, in an effort to get the taste of bile out of his mouth.

"If you want me to wear a glamour, just say so," Bellatrix offered. "Until I'm pregnant, consider me your penis sheath. Penis glove? Penis holster? Penis pincushion? I think I like sound of sheath best."

Remus was wiping the mess from his mouth and asked, "What did you cast then, if not contraceptive charms?"

"I assumed you'd recognize it," Bellatrix explained from her odd position. "I don't care if it's a boy or a girl, but I'd rather not a werewolf if it can be helped, so that was just a bit of magic ensuring it'd be a daughter."

Remus just stared at her in shock.

"You know," Bellatrix tried to fill the uncomfortable silence, "because your curse is only ever passed on to sons."

"I know that," Remus snapped and exasperatedly scolded, "But that's a dark spell."

Bellatrix resumed her rocking motion. "That I only needed because you're a dark creature."

Remus started to get dressed unable to maintain a conversation with a nude Bellatrix rolling around like a turtle flipped over.

He glanced at her after pulling his shirt over his head. Bellatrix paused a moment and hopefully pointed towards her exposed nether regions, silently inviting him again.

Remus shook his head and left the room as quick as he could. He walked down to Sirius' bedroom and banged hard on the door. "Get out here, Padfoot!"

His sensitive werewolf hearing picked up on movement muffled by a weakened silencing charm, before the door was pulled open, by a half-asleep Sirius Black. "Moony?"

Remus didn't hesitate for a moment or hold back any of his enhanced strength as he landed a sharp right cross to Sirius' temple.

The punch connected with a loud crack and Sirius crumpled to the floor. His mouth was open in silent scream that slowly trickled into a whining, "…aaaAAAHHH!"

Sirius was clutching his head and looked up at Remus.

Remus waited a beat and then started kicking Sirius in the leg. "What," he kicked, "the hell," kicked again, "were," kicked twice, "you," kicked the back of his thigh, "thinking?" He kicked him a little harder as Sirius rolled over exposing asscrack above his pants.

"Harry!" Sirius' voice came out extremely high-pitched. "Help!"

"Harry's not going help y-"

"What's up?" Harry asked perfectly alert, standing right behind Remus.

Remus jumped having not even heard the other Lord Black approach. "Dammit Harry," he said clutching his heart. "Help me kick this idiot."

"I've got company!" Sirius harshly whispered, from his curled fetal position on the floor.

"You smell like puke, Moony. Didn't remember a hangover spell last night, did you?" Harry said distracting him from kicking Sirius. He was looking straight at Remus, waiting on an answer while helping Sirius to his feet.

Remus sniffed the air and winced at his own acrid odor before remembering what he was doing. "I can't believe you did that to me," Remus whispered angrily staring at Sirius.

"You needed to get laid," Sirius argued, in between noticing how bad his own mouth tasted and rubbing his sore jaw. "It was a win-win situation."

"Not with… her," Remus spat out.

Bellatrix had slipped on a robe and was tying the belt, standing about ten feet back of them. "Why does everybody hate me?"

"You," Harry said pointing at Remus. He turned to Bellatrix and finished, "And you?"

Bellatrix nodded rubbing her belly hopefully.

"That's bloody brilliant," Harry cheered, before yelping and grabbing his own shin. "OWW! Dammit Moony!"

"She already used dark magic on our rapebaby!"

Harry had to bite his tongue from suggesting that rapebaby made a good name but the mention of dark magic intrigued him. He looked at Bellatrix. "Gender forcing?"

Bellatrix nodded.

Harry leaned in towards Remus and whispered, "That's what the other you and Tonks did too."

Remus looked back at Harry in disgust. "Why would you tell me that? Why?"

Harry opened his mouth to reply and shut it. "I don't think you'd like any of the answers I'd give to that question." He saw Remus frowning and shrugged sheepishly. "It wouldn't be necessary if you weren't already a dark creature."

"That's exactly what I said," Bellatrix helpfully added, while massaging her lower stomach.

"Great minds skullfuck alike," Sirius mumbled under his breath.

"Is everything okay?" came a feminine voice from inside Sirius' bedroom. She and her twin were wearing identical bathrobes as they joined the crowd in the hallway.

"No!" Harry shouted pointing at the pair. "What are you… How… But…"

"Twins," Sirius exclaimed happily throwing an arm around each girl. "I got them both this time, so no surprises in the morning."

"No," Harry said shaking his head in disbelief.

The girl in Harry's room chose this moment to come out, wrapped in only a robe. "Did I just hear…" She locked eyes with the two women standing behind Sirius and gasped in surprise. "Tracey? Stacey?"

The two identical looking sisters squeaked in surprise at the sight of their also identical looking sister. "Lacey!"

Sirius looked at the girl behind Harry and then back at the two sisters he had assumed were only twins next to him. He whipped his head back and forth, crying out, "Why does this keep happening to us?"

Harry looked back at Lacey and could tell there was no doubt Tracey, Stacey, and Lacey were identical triplets. He turned back and scolded his godfather, "Why did you pick up two girls who looked just like Lacey?"

Sirius was about to defend himself before he fully realized the situation. He started to chuckle victoriously. "I got two, you got one. I win."

Stacey and Tracey were just staring at their sister incredulously. Stacey broke the silence declaring, "But Lacey, you… you're a lesbian!"

Harry felt the young woman inch closer to him for safety.

Tracey scoffed as incredulous as her sister. "And you're a virgin!"

Lacey was blushing as she tried to hide behind Harry, just barely peering over his shoulder. She softly admitted, "A day ago, both of those would have been true."

Harry tried to fight it but his eyes were twinkling.

"Fine," Sirius sighed and admitted, "You win."

"Of course I do," Harry said, thumping Sirius on the shoulder.

"What the fudge is going on here?" Remus snapped, feeling his fury dissipating at the strangeness of the morning and getting really angry that he was less angry.

"Fudge?" Stacey asked curiously. She turned to Tracey, "Does he realize he said fudge?"

"Hey guys," Tonks' voice carried from down the stairs. "Have you seen my dad? I don't think he ever made it home last night."

"Oh fuck me," Remus grumbled quietly to himself.

"Dibs!" Bellatrix called out.

"No!" Remus said pointing forcefully.

"Dad? Is that you?" Tonks called out as she hurried up the rest of the steps. "There you are," she announced taking notice of the crowd forming. "Umm… good morning Harry, Sirius, triplets I don't know."

"Ooh triplets," Bellatrix imagined, keeping a hand over her womb.

"My second favorite death eating aunt," Tonks said glancing coldly at Bellatrix.

"Hang on," Tracey asked. "She's your aunt?"

Tonks and Bellatrix both nodded.

"But Sirius," She turned to the man wrapped around her and her sister. "Last night you said Remus was going to sleep with her?"

"You what?" Tonks asked her rapidly paling adoptive father.

"Hold on, it's not what you think," Remus tried to explain.

Bellatrix helpfully added, "I just want a baby."

"For breakfast?" Tonks asked in confusion.

Bellatrix stomped her foot in a childish show of frustration. "Why does everyone think I'm some kind of monster?"

"Maybe because you're a murderer," Tonks stated unequivocally.

The three triplet sisters were all looking at Bellatrix. She made no attempt to deny it, admitting, "We all have our quirks." She ignored them for only a moment, before arguing, "Oh stop it. You were a lesbian virgin and you two clearly have issues."

Tracey, Stacey, and Lacey all harrumphed in unison.

Remus saw Tonks looking at him in disappointment. He could feel her judging him and he had to resist the impulse to kick Sirius more.

"In fairness," Harry felt like making a half-hearted attempt to mollify the situation. "You were saying he needed to get laid."

Tonks looked at Harry with a frown. "That was so he'd be less irritable. Not because I wanted a little brother."

"If it happens, it'll be a sister for you," Bellatrix assured her.

"Oh a sister?" Tonks repeated. "Well that's okay then, Dad. Why don't you go fuck my murderous aunt a little bit more?"

"Maybe I will," Remus retorted, thinking Tonks was being harsher than necessary.

"Really?" Bellatrix asked.

"No," Remus told her. "Not really."

Bellatrix flashed open her robe.

Remus gulped. "Okay there's a chance."

"Listen Tonks," Harry interjected. "I'm not trying to make excuses for anybody, no matter if they were drunk or desperate enough to sleep with Bellatrix. But really, this is all Sirius' fault." Harry finished pointing both thumbs over his shoulder at his godfather.

"What?" Sirius yelped. "My fault? I'm not the one who came up with Harry's Secret Plan to Get Bellatrix Knocked Up, now am I?"

"Don't you pin this on me," Harry turned to glare at Sirius.

Sirius was fighting back laughter and could see Harry was as amused as he was. "You're the one who told me to get Moony plastered and send him to her room."

"Why you little-" Harry exclaimed as he slammed Sirius to the ground and began to strangle him.

"It was Harry's idea!" Sirius called out as soon as Harry let up.

Harry went back to mock strangling Sirius while using magical arms to pinch him all over.

Sirius was yelping and flopping around like a fish, pinned underneath Harry. "Help! Kreacher!"

Kreacher appeared with a loud pop and grumbled, "Yes, Master?"

Tracey and Stacey who had huddled over by Lacey both shrieked loudly at the appearance of the house elf. They saw no one else present was surprised and began to scream even louder.

"Oh right," Harry said. "Muggles."

"Oops," Sirius added, while still pinned down.

Harry stunned the three triplets quickly, silencing their piercing shrieks. "You should be more careful," Harry said helping Sirius up.

"Enh," Sirius mumbled indecisively. "They were probably going to have to be taken care of anyway."

"I can help with the bodies," Bellatrix offered, finally seeing an opportunity to contribute to the family.

"Oh brilliant," Tonks said rubbing her forehead. "Expanding this family is a wonderful idea."

Sirius and Harry exchanged a pitying look. Sirius explained to Bellatrix, "We're just gonna memory charm them of the things they're not supposed to know." He paused and glanced at the house elf. "Same with Kreacher."

Kreacher looked at Sirius and Harry in fear. "You know how to memory cha-"

"Obliviate," Harry tiredly cast on Kreacher before he could finish the sentence. "Dammit, Sirius. That's another hour you're going to be performing at the park."

Kreacher shook his dazed little head. "Masters?"

"Go back to whatever you were doing, Kreacher," Harry ordered, happy to see the house elf pop away.

"I just wanted to make sure my dad was okay." Tonks was talking to herself. "It's too early for the Harry and Sirius special brand of insanity."

"Is she talking about me?" Bellatrix asked the others uncertainly.

"Hey Harry," Tonks said tilting her head towards him with a rueful grin. "I don't think things could possibly get worse."

"Don't say that!" Harry snapped. "I told you never to say that around me." He stopped and looked around the hallway for any death traps about to be sprung.

After ten seconds of silence, Harry relaxed and let his wand arm fall. "I guess we got lucky that time."

A massive explosion sounded and the entire building shook.

"Dammit," Harry swore and ran down the hall towards the front door. He stuck his head around the window to get a quick view and whipped it back instinctively. He then processed what his eyes saw in that split second. No groups of Death Eaters, nor an angry mob with torches. Just a muggle construction crew tearing down the building across the street.

"Huh," Harry said, moving directly in front of the window to watch the street scene. "It's just the muggles across the way."

The entire group had hurried down the stairs after Harry and they were all crowding around the window now to see the destruction going on.

"How'd they do that?" Sirius was asking while leaning over Harry's shoulder.

Remus and Tonks were on the other side watching as well, while Bellatrix was peering around the edge curiously.

"Hello," Harry said pointing down the street. "Look over there. You can see the dust outlines of a couple of disillusioned blokes."

"What? Where?" Sirius asked curiously.

"I don't see them," Tonks was looking.

"Are they Death Eaters?" Bellatrix asked.

"Probably," Harry answered, still pointing in their direction. "It could be the Ministry or someone else, but my money's on Death Eaters."

Remus was looking where Harry had pointed. "Are they crouching?"

"What are we looking at?"

Harry stopped suddenly having recognized a voice he wasn't expecting to hear. He turned around and couldn't see past the bodies crowding him. "Umm… what are you doing here?"

"I'm trying to see what you're pointing at," she answered sticking her head out. "But Tonks oversized rump is blocking my view."

"Ginny!" Tonks exclaimed moving out of the way.

"Hi Tonks."

Bellatrix curiously looked at the ghost. "I don't believe we've met. Ginny, was it?"

Ginny let out an eep of surprise not noticing there was an uninformed person present. She floated and leaned down towards Harry. "I don't want to alarm you, but Bellatrix is standing right behind you."

Harry glanced at the woman and back to Ginny. He leaned towards the ghost and answered, "I was aware of that fact. But did you realize that she's not deaf and can hear you just fine?"

"Great," Bellatrix grumbled. "Another one who hates me and probably won't tell me why."

"What's she doing here?" Ginny asked at a normal volume while watching the elder woman pout.

"Primarily she wants a baby," Harry calmly answered. "That's why Sirius and I are going to do our best to stick Moony into unavoidably provocative situations with her."

Ginny saw Remus and Tonks both look worried. She smiled and asked, "What kind of situations?"

Sirius shrugged. "Maybe handcuff them both to a couch and cover them in chocolate syrup."

"Yeah," Harry agreed. "She's got that pale complexion, so use dark chocolate."

Tonks saw Remus was picturing it as his eyes' widened slightly. She punched him in the chest, "Stop that."

"Could you use a cherry syrup so I can at least pretend it's blood?" Bellatrix suggested.

They all turned to look at her and collectively concluded she wasn't going to be winning any mother-of-the-year awards anytime soon.

"How about this," Remus said as a bright idea came to him. "I'll help Bellatrix out, if she can convince Tonks that it's something I should do."

Bellatrix looked over at Tonks hopefully, trying to get a better measure of the young woman.

Tonks looked away from Bellatrix and got right into her adoptive father's face. She was looking him straight in the eye, not daring to use any magic, but simply trying to get a read on his emotions.

Remus was beginning to get worried as Tonks was staring at him. He suddenly realized she was threatening to hand him over to Bellatrix.

Tonks smirked as she caught the flash of fear in Remus' eye. She looked away and clapped her hands. "Alright then. Go make me a little sister."

Remus was cornered and fought down a whimper at the eager look on Bellatrix's face.

"It's too early in the morning. And now that I know dad's not been taken by Death Eaters," Tonks gave Bellatrix an unwelcome look, "present company excluded, I'm going to go to home and go to bed."

Remus felt ashamed, not knowing Tonks was going to check on him last night.

"Harry," Tonks firmly ordered. "Don't bring a girl home tonight. I've got to work until graveyard's first break, but when I'm off, I am going to ride you raw. Good day."

Tonks apparated away with a pop just as Harry nodded meekly, "Yes, ma'am."

"She added that phrase for my benefit," Remus stated distastefully.

Ginny shrugged. "She could have been trying to give Bellatrix some ideas."

"Is anyone going to fill me in on this new ghost named Ginny?" Bellatrix asked. She saw them all trading looks with no one speaking up. "Fine. I figured as much. Come along, Remus," Bellatrix beckoned. "You've got work to do."

Remus was luckily able to avoid a moral dilemma so far by letting others make his decisions for him. But he felt like he was going to get into even more trouble with his daughter if he did what she told him to do. "It's my day off," Remus begged. "Can't I just come back tonight?"

"You'd prefer to wait," Bellatrix clarified, "until Tonks, your daughter, is in the room down the hall?"

Remus winced and conceded. "Oh fine. Let's get this over with."

Harry and Sirius were left standing by the window, while the building across the street was being demolished. Ginny was floating next to them, "So… slow morning?"

"Want to go see if they're marked Death Eaters?" Harry asked looking at the disillusioned pair.

"Alright," Sirius nodded. "Apparate around the corner."

Ginny just remained floating by the window, knowing Harry hadn't gone far, since he hadn't pulled her with him. She watched as a glamour-covered old woman was being pulled down the street by a hyperactive dog on a leash. The dog was sniffing the air and bounded over near the two hidden wizards. He happily lifted a leg and peed on their disillusioned feet. The dog bounded away around the corner pulling the old lady with him.

Another pop and Sirius and Harry were back in the front room.

"Death Eaters?" Ginny asked.

"Death Eaters," Harry agreed having used a snake to confirm it. "But I get the feeling they're just here to observe."

Sirius nodded. "In which case, I may need to make a habit of peeing on them every day. Sounds like a good way to start the day."

Harry was scratching his head. "Are we forgetting something?"

Sirius looked at Ginny and shrugged.

A number of shrieks sounded from up the stairs. "That's right," Harry said snapping his fingers. "The muggles."

They hurried up the stairs where two of the girls were horrified that they couldn't wake up their sister, and screaming their heads off in response.

Sirius looked at Harry and asked, "You mind if I get the camera, since, I mean, you're already going to be obliviating them…"

"Sirius, that's horrible," Harry said shaking his head in disgust. He paused and nodded, "Okay. Get the camera."

Harry and Tonks were standing across from the three transfigured midgets settling limply into the sofa. Remus was slumped against the right armrest, Kreacher was hanging over the side of the left armrest, and Sirius was slouched down the middle. All three were laboring to catch their breath.

Harry was smiling brightly, even more so when the midgets would frown at him. "It appears you all fell short of the one hour you owed."

"That counts!" Sirius whined in a squeaky nasal voice.

Harry glanced over at Tonks. "What do you think? Was that long enough?"

"I don't know," Tonks said crossing her arms and looking at midget-sized Remus. "How long did it take you to screw my mother's sister—you know, a member of the criminal organization who murdered my mother and father? Did that fall short of an hour? Hmm?"

Bellatrix felt annoyed and proud that her niece could hold a grudge. She mumbled from the doorway, "I said I was sorry."

Remus was panting still and claimed in a charmed high-pitched voice, "Yes, it was definitely under an hour."

"He's lying," Bellatrix chimed in.

"I hate you!" Remus squeaked staring at Bellatrix.

"Oh Merlin," Bellatrix deadpanned. "Someone hates me. What ever shall I do?"

"Alright," Harry interrupted. "Since you failed to complete a full hour-"

"It's not our fault we had to leave!" Sirius complained over Kreacher's quiet whimpering.

"Yeah," Remus agreed. "Blame whichever concerned parent called the police. Don't blame us."

"As I was saying," Harry continued. "We may be willing to give you credit for the hour, if you can at least prove that you've learned from the experience. So tell us," Harry said waving his hand towards Tonks and himself. "What have you learned?"

Sirius was slid back into the couch cushions. He turned his head towards Remus on his right and the surprisingly docile Kreacher on his left. "What?"

"What have you learned?" Harry repeated. "Didn't you learn anything today or do we need to repeat this particular life lesson?"

Remus raised his stubby little midget arm into the air and said, "I've learned why people include the words 'and unusual' in the phrase 'cruel and unusual punishment.'"

"Thank you, Moony," Harry said with a smile. "Now I know you were trying to be a smart-ass, but you did point out something constructive that you learned. Sirius, what about you?"

"I learned," Sirius mused while scratching his disproportionately sized chin. "I learned there's no way in hell midgets can run away on foot, unless they have fences to crawl under."

"Or unless," Remus added, "the pursuers are really tall. Then you can double back by diving between their legs."

"Good point," Sirius applauded. "And I learned accidental midget head butts are another reason you should always wear a protective cup."

"Don't forget giants stubbing their toes and secretly charmed slappable bars. Two more very good arguments for wearing a cup," Harry added while reminiscing past pain. He turned to the quietest midget. "Kreacher, have you learned anything?"

Kreacher was still feeling revolted with his current transfigured form but earnestly answered, "Kreacher learned children cry when he hugs them. And they kick too."

Tonks coughed and explained, "I think the reason they cry has more to with the fact that you kept sneaking up behind them and hugging them unexpectedly."

"And they probably could sense your inherent evil," Sirius added.

"Probably," the house elf nodded. "Kreacher could definitely sense theirs."

Harry asked, "Is that all you learned, Kreacher?"

Kreacher could feel the noose tightening and shook his head. "No Master!"

Harry tilted his head, silently asking Kreacher to elaborate.

Kreacher looked around frantically for help.

Remus felt pity for the house elf and supplied, "Did you learn anything when Sirius tried to jump through the policeman's legs and missed?"

"Yes!" Kreacher cheered happily. "Kreacher learned children laugh when humans get hit in their penis places!"

"Not just children," Harry said with a snicker.

"I wouldn't say 'learned' as much as I reaffirmed what I suspected," Remus said, "in that people do not keep midgets on leashes and take them for walks."

"I think we also learned," Tonks jumped in while giving Harry a scolding look, "that just because you're wearing a glamour, doesn't mean you should introduce yourself by saying, 'Hi, I'm Vernon Dursley. I'm a horrible person and I keep my midget son locked in a cage.'"

Harry rolled his eyes. "Maybe you learned that…"

"Well hang on," Tonks replied, confronting Harry. "What did you learn then?"

"Me?" Harry repeated. He gave it a bit of thought and said, "I learned people get upset when you drop kick a midget." He was shaking his head in surprise, "Even if it's a biter."

Sirius was tugging on the straps across his chest. "I learned that just because you can fit into a toddler's leash harness, doesn't mean it'll be comfortable."

"Oh!" Kreacher raised his hand. "Kreacher learned it's easy to tie a leash in a knot, if Kreacher loops it around Master's neck first."

Sirius frowned at Kreacher. "Don't think I've forgotten about that."

"Kreacher also learned carousels can be magicked to go faster."

Remus grinned. "I suppose I learned that toddler harnesses are strong enough to handle the centrifugal forces of a carousel."

Sirius sighed. "I learned that if you're being dragged on the ground by a magicked carousel, then it's funny to throw up. But only for as long as it takes to make one revolution."

"Yes," Kreacher agreed thinking of another. "Kreacher learned Master had a bacon and bacon sandwich for lunch."

Sirius nodded while scratching his normal sized head on his midget sized body. "And I reckon I learned that I need to chew my food more."

"I learned," Harry said smiling brightly with Tonks, "that sometimes three rolls of film just isn't enough."

"And I learned," Tonks deviously grinned, "how useful disillusioning a pair of omnioculars can be."

"See?" Sirius said. "We all learned a lot. No need to repeat or ever mention this day again."

"Is that it?" Harry asked Tonks who still looked skeptical. He turned back towards the sofa. "Nothing else you guys learned?"

"Kreacher learned Master can be a cruel and vindictive bastard," Kreacher happily supplied.

"I already knew that," Sirius and Remus both said at the same time.

"I don't mean to… belittle you," Harry said, relishing in the staggered groans from everyone other than the confused house elf. "But Kreacher meant it as a compliment."

"Can you change us back now?" Remus begged. "And put an end to the most humiliating experience of my life?"

Tonks scoffed, "You slept with Bellatrix."

"Fine," Remus corrected. "Second most humiliating."

"I'm right here," Bellatrix whined from the door.

The four other humans turned and saw Bellatrix leaning against the doorjamb. After a moment's worth of acknowledgement they turned back towards themselves.

"Besides," Harry said. "You should at least wait until after Monday's Quibbler comes out before deciding on your most humiliating moment." Harry glanced over at Bellatrix and corrected, "Or second most."

Sirius popped the top on a nice cool butterbeer and relaxed back in his recliner. He peered through his omnioculars and saw the heat signatures of two people still at home. He looked over at Harry who appeared to be focusing his eyes on the layers and sets of wards.

"So?" Sirius asked. "You said you'd tell me when we got some down time. What did you see? I know it wasn't just grey mist or you would've told me that this morning."

Harry had taken the animagus potion the night before and it had been every bit as fruitless as his previous attempts. "It was almost all just grey mist. I wish it had been just mist, then maybe I could convince myself it was really an invisible Demiguise."

"You saw something else?" Sirius asked setting his omnioculars down.

Harry shook his head. "Nothing new. It was like the trance McGonagall put me under. And again a blurry figure started to come into focus. It was like I was invisible but could see my reflection."

"Harry's form got killed," Sirius melodiously ridiculed. "Harry's form got killed."

"I woke up before the shape came into focus," Harry said with a shrug. "Could be anyone… but the way it carried itself, it had the same mannerisms as me. It's like it showed up just to ruin my aspirations of a Demiguise form."

Sirius looked through the omnioculars again. "Both are gone. You want to run some diagnostics on the outer wards? Trigger test?"

Harry shook his head. "Let's not rush ourselves and cut out the legwork. They could be back at any time. And I don't want to simply trust the information Bellatrix provided when we can verify it ourselves."

Sirius was scanning through the place with his omnioculars. "When she gets knocked up, let's move her into her own place."

"Why wait?" Harry said feeling an owl trip one of his perimeter wards. He looked up as the owl flew straight toward them.

"We got mail," Harry told Sirius as he looked over the back of his chair.

"Can they get through the Fidelius?"

"We're invisible until it crosses the charm, but it's an owl," Harry replied. "They know where to go by sense, not by sight."

The owl flew down and landed on the back of Harry's chair. He untied the letter and recognized the handwriting on the envelope immediately.

Harry handed the letter to Sirius without opening it. "Can't she pretend I'm a perfectly normal excessively emotional teen who just doesn't want to hear from or talk to his parents?"

"Another letter from Lily?" Sirius asked happily, cracking it open. He slowly read through the short missive and announced, "She's inviting us to Hogwarts. A meal, a tour, access to the world-renowned library? She just doesn't give up, does she?"

Harry looked over at Sirius while remembering one of the things Bellatrix had told him. "Invited us to Hogwarts? You know there are a number of books on warding and animagi in the restricted section."

"You want to go?" Sirius asked in surprise.

"It's not a half bad idea," Harry said indifferently. "And there is one thing I'd like to check."

"You do realize Dumbledore won't leave us alone for a second," Sirius added.

Harry settled back into his recliner. "That's assuming we don't split up. If we split up, one of us can keep Dumbledore busy, while I go and check my thing."

"Subtle, Harry," Sirius tiredly grumbled.

Harry began to weigh the reasons to go to Hogwarts against the reasons to decline the invitation.

"You really think we should go?"

Harry shrugged. "I get the feeling she's going to keep inviting us until we say yes."

"Probably," Sirius agreed. "And afterwards we can hit the Hog's Head and see how Gin is doing."

Harry looked over at Sirius and slowly nodded. "Yeah. Let's go to Hogwarts and have dinner with my… yeah."

Chapter 19

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Big thanks to IP, Chuck, Jim, Draco, and all the folks who help me straighten out my chapters as their input greatly improved this one. You may think this chapter is filler, but I prefer to think of it more like an interlude. And I realized we're closer to the end of this fic than I first thought. Not completely sure but there's probably somewhere between seven and a dozen chapters to go. Thanks for all the reviews. I do read and appreciate every one. And I try to answer any legitimate questions asked (that means I won't tell you who That Fucker is. But if you guess it exactly right and back it up with reasons properly I may tell you to shush...).

"You know putting Grimmauld under a Fidelius isn't that bad of an idea even if we do move Bellatrix into her own place."

"If?" Sirius squeaked. "What do you mean if? And you've got a problem Harry. Your solution to everything is putting it under Fidelius. It's not healthy."

"It's a fantastic charm," Harry indignantly argued.

"And if we put it over our place that would mean no more bringing muggles home."

Harry shrugged. "I know. But we made the decision against it before we publicly kicked Voldemort's ass."

"Our gift though, Harry," Sirius pleaded. "We should use our gift. We owe it to sex. You know we do."

Harry always had trouble arguing against sex.

"And don't give me that hotels or their places bollocks," Sirius said shaking his finger.

"Fine," Harry said. "I'm not saying we have to. But give it some consideration."

They arrived at the entrance to the newest branch of Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes located in Hogsmeade. Harry opened the door and let Sirius in first.

"Attention shoppers," Sirius yelled loudly. "There is an extremely irritable werewolf in here. Do not antagonize him."

"Sirius," Remus called out from behind the cash register wincing at the sudden yelling. He rubbed his ears, grateful that the store was currently empty. "I'm not above jinxing your eyebrows into thinking they're foreskin."

Sirius blinked. "That would make my head look really odd. Both of them, come to think of it."

"You feeling okay, Moony?" Harry asked as he leaned on the counter next to Remus.

Remus half-heartedly grunted positively. "Considering last night, yeah, about normal."

Sirius was still walking through the aisles looking at the goodies for sale. "I bet you'd be feeling better if you just let me keep you company, instead of you know who."

"Voldemort?" Harry inquired.

Remus turned to Harry. "You think I spend the full moon with Voldemort?"

Sirius laughed as he picked up a product, smelled it, and set it back down. "I'd forgotten about all those nicknames like You-Know-Who."

"Bleh," Harry said sticking out his tongue. "Easy for you to forget them. You never even got one after breaking out of prison."

"I should have gotten one," Sirius realized and began to daydream aloud. "He-Who-Could-Not-Be-Contained."

"Twelve years," Remus reminded.

"For-Too-Long," Sirius added.

Harry decided not to crush his godfather's hopes of being nickname worthy. "I swear if I heard Hermione's spiel about 'fear of a name increases fear of the thing itself' one more time, I was going find You-Know-Who and jam my You-Know-What You-Know-How into his You-Know-Where… hole."

Remus tiredly looked at Sirius messing up one of the displays. "This has been great guys. I'm so glad you dropped by."

"Sorry Moony," Harry apologized. "Aren't you closing soon?"

Remus nodded. "Officially we're open until ten." He waved his wand towards the front turning the sign off and locking the door. "But it's close enough for me."

"Nice work ethic," Sirius nodded. "Tonks would approve."

Harry jumped in with a smile. "We've got some good news, some bad news, and some great news."

Remus looked up curiously. "Give me the bad news."

"No," Harry firmly retorted. "I wasn't asking what you wanted first. The good news is we're kicking Bellatrix out."

"What?" Remus asked worriedly. "Kicking her out?"

"She doesn't know yet," Sirius commented.

"Why?" Remus said looking at Harry and Sirius in disappointment.

"Well that ties into the bad news," Harry said with a clap of his hands. "See, the reason we're kicking her out is that we've got a new house rule: no pregnant chicks."

"That seems a bit harsh," Remus said before stopping in sudden realization of what Harry had just implied. "You mean she's…"

"Carrying your furry half-breed beast," Sirius agreed. "Yup."

"That's…" Remus was struggling for words. He straightened up and defiantly whined, "That's not bad news."

Sirius looked at Harry in confusion. "I guess it depends on how you look at it."

Remus frowned. "So then what's the great news?"

Harry grinned brightly. "We've submitted an offer for the flat next to yours."

Remus took a moment before connecting the good news and bad news with the great news. He closed his eyes and sighed. "She's always going to be at my place, isn't she?"

"I'm really not sure," Sirius said walking up to the counter where Harry and Remus were. "But just in case, let me be the first to say… ha-hah!" Sirius laughed while childishly pointing.

"Ha-hah," Harry echoed and pointed at Remus. "Second."

"This is…" Remus was still processing the situation. "This is big. Where is she? I should talk to her."

"She was at Grimmauld Place," Harry said checking with Sirius.

Sirius nodded. "I think she was planning on a night in. I remember something about drowning herself in the bathtub."

"Whatever," Harry said waving Sirius off. "We're going to the Hog's Head, Moony. Care to join us?"

"No," Remus said shaking his head. He started locking up the register and shutting down everything else. "I'm going to go see her. This is… wow."

"Congratulations," Harry said finally realizing how much Remus was smiling. "Forgot about that part. Way to impregnate."

"Thanks," Remus agreed patting Harry on the back and urging them out of the store. "Come on, come on."

Sirius and Harry were pushed out the front door and Remus activated the store's lockdown wards.

"Slow down," Harry argued as Remus was frantically locking up.

"See you later guys," Remus snapped and apparated away with a loud crack.

"It's not like you don't have eight and half months or so," Harry mumbled towards the empty air.

Sirius and Harry walked through the wizarding village and down to the familiar dingy pub.

"Grab us a pitcher of draft," Sirius said. "I'm going to hit the loo."

Harry carefully walked up to the bar and saw Gin smirking at him. "Please don't nut me. You know Sirius is waiting in the bathroom just hoping to see the pictures change."

"What's in it for-" Gin began when a group at a back booth called out for her. She pasted a clearly mocking smile on her face. "I'll be with you in a minute, Harry."

Harry turned to his left and saw a very cute redhead watching him unabashedly. Harry looked away and tried to smother his grin. He walked over to her cataloguing just which parts of her form fitting robes were pulled taut. "You know an attractive young woman like yourself stands out quite a bit in a place like this."

"As does as a Lord Black," the redhead playfully retorted. She turned forward to face the bar, looking away from Harry finally.

Harry was mesmerized by the nape of her neck and her profile when she looked away. "So what is it that brings an attractive young woman like yourself into a place like this?"

"Are you flirting with me, Lord Black?" she asked with a small grin distinctly lacking in innocence.

"Please, call me Harry," Harry said noticing his godfather walk up. Harry had been waving Sirius off the whole way but the older man barged right up to him anyway. Harry warned, "I hope there's an emergency."

"No, not exactly," Sirius replied. He glanced at the redhead wearing a sultry grin. "Sorry to interrupt you. I just need to speak to Harry for a second."

The young woman was seductively pulling the cherry stem from her mouth as she swallowed the fruit that had been on the bottom of her drink. "I can wait."

"What?" Harry irritably asked his godfather.

"Listen, Harry, you remember when you gave me a hard time for hitting on that nineteen year old installing the floo?"

"She was eighteen," Harry corrected and glanced at the redhead again, guessing her to be early twenties.

"Yeah, about that…" Sirius said before reaching over and tapping the redhead on the shoulder. "What's your last name?"

She glanced at Sirius oddly and answered. "Potter."

"See ya, Harry," Sirius cheerfully said, slapping Harry on the back as he walked away.

Harry's entire body froze in shock, suddenly realizing why the young woman had seemed familiar. He turned to look at her closer. He wasn't saying anything just staring at her in abject horror and fascination.

She blushed slightly under the intense scrutiny. "Don't tell me my parents have managed to scare you that badly."

"You're Sarah Potter," Harry said in a calm dulcet tone. "Sarah… Potter."

"Yeah," Sarah agreed. "And you're Lord Harry Black. My little brother's hero."

"I…" Harry stuttered, becoming disgusted with himself for having entertained certain thoughts. "I…"

"Want to buy me a drink?" Sarah suggested with a smile, shaking the ice in her empty glass.

"I…"

Sirius came up from behind Harry and saw he was struggling. "Listen, Miss Potter. I'm sorry but I'm going to have to take Harry here. A situation has come up that requires our immediate attention."

"Nice meeting you," Sarah said tipping her glass back so she could chew up her ice.

Harry wanted to smile seeing his 'sort of' sister was such an understanding genial person, but he knew how smiling at her would look. He was stuck in a loop of inaction as Sirius turned him around and led him back towards the other side of the bar.

Sirius sat Harry down on a stool and spun him around, attracting his full attention. "I wasn't lying, Harry. A situation has come up that I think we need to address."

"What's up?" Harry asked, acting more alert than he felt.

"I just met a young woman who was drowning herself in butterbeer," Sirius explained.

"Butterbeer?"

"I'm guessing she has a low tolerance," Sirius assured him. "Anyways, she has had what she calls an unfortunately boring life. Bemoaning the fact that she never got into a fight in school, never went on an adventure, and claims to have never done anything spontaneous on a lark."

"Okay," Harry said not sure where Sirius was going with this.

"When I heard this, I knew immediately it was up to us to correct this oversight," Sirius continued. "We need to make an adventure. Just go somewhere random, find something fun to do, and take her with us."

Harry was a bit skeptical but shrugged. "Alright."

Sirius turned Harry around towards the corner of the bar where a brunette was lackadaisically resting her chin on the bar. "Harry, I'd like you to meet Hermione Granger."

"Hermione?" Harry said unable to believe his eyes. "Your hair looks great."

"I'm not going to sleep with you," she mumbled, still hunched over the bar.

"No, it's just," Harry commented. "Your hair is so straight and wavy… It's not frizzy at all."

"I'm still not going to sleep with you." She finally lifted her head up and saw Sirius Black smiling widely at her. "Please tell me you're not still on this."

Sirius sat down right beside and swung his arm over her shoulder. "You were not meant to live an unfortunately boring life."

"That was the butterbeer talking," Hermione said shaking her head.

"You've earned an adventure and we're here to give it to you," Sirius insisted. "You know it'll do you some good."

Hermione's face curled up in a pout as she pondered the best response. "Fine," she conceded. "I suppose you could be right. So when were you thinking?"

"Oh no," Sirius assured her, grabbing her drink and downing the rest of it. "We're doing it now."

"Now?" Hermione squeaked in surprise. She looked at her watch. "But it's already past ten."

Harry shook his head in disappointment. "Oh, Hermione."

"The fact that you're concerned that it's already past ten just further proves how important it is that we do this immediately," Sirius assured. "And besides, it's not ten everywhere."

Harry checked that he had his satchel with him. "I've got some energizing potions. And I can't help but notice it's about 8 in the morning on the Sydney beaches."

"I was thinking New Zealand waterfalls maybe," Sirius suggested.

Harry shrugged. "It's two in the afternoon in Vegas."

Sirius shook his head. "Since when has time ever mattered in Vegas?"

Hermione saw the two Lord Blacks conversing back and forth and couldn't take it. "You can not just up and go anywhere you want."

Harry smirked at one of his first friends. "Are you a witch or not?"

Hermione resisted the urge to huff. "You still need permits for international travel."

Sirius unceremoniously lifted Hermione up off her bar stool. "Come along Miss Granger. You're traveling with two noble Lords."

"What does that matter?" Hermione questioned curiously.

"Harry?" Sirius prompted.

"When in service of matters pertaining to an ancient and noble family, a Lord is not restricted by such pedestrian laws," Harry happily recited. "Before you ask, it is up to the Lord's discretion. And I say this is a family matter."

"You don't even know me," Hermione argued but didn't resist in the slightest as she was led out the front of the Hog's Head.

"That's what makes it spontaneous and random," Harry argued.

"Where do we start?" Sirius asked, wrapping an arm around Hermione.

Harry snaked his arm around Hermione from the other side. "I'm thinking let's start in Egypt. Just to take a peek."

" Egypt?" Hermione asked excitedly.

Sirius turned to Harry. "I'll help, but you're pulling us."

Harry nodded and began to focus on the target for a long distance apparition.

"Why Egypt?" Hermione quietly asked Sirius.

Sirius leaned towards her and whispered, "He still wants to ride on the back of a nundu."

Hermione's eyes widened fearfully. "Ride on what-" She was cut off as she felt the squeezing sensation and loud sound accompanied with disapparition.

The group of three slammed into place on the muddy bank of a river. Harry and Sirius were trying to hold Hermione steady but they all fell backwards onto their bums.

Hermione screamed and scrambled away from them. "What do you think you're doing? Oh god. I think I'm going to be sick." Hermione was on her hands and knees trying to catch her breath.

Harry jumped up and was brushing off his robes. "How much did you have to drink?"

"I'm not drunk," Hermione snapped without even looking up. "I'm just not used to being forcefully apparated and kidnapped."

"I told you she needs our help," Sirius assured Harry.

Harry reached into his satchel and found a bottle of water. He held it out for Hermione, "Water?"

Hermione accepted the bottle and eagerly drank it up. "This is a bad idea. Take me home."

"Sorry Hermione," Harry said shaking his head. "I have an old friend who would be very disappointed in me if I did that."

"You really are kidnapping me," Hermione said with a frown as she sipped the chilled beverage. "I don't know who you think you're dealing with-"

"Hermione Jean Granger, only daughter of Samuel and Delilah Granger," Harry recounted. "Both muggles and both dentists. How am I doing so far?"

Hermione had her wand out in an instant and was pointing it at Harry and then Sirius intermittently. She was slightly worried that neither seemed concerned nor had they drawn their wands even. "What do you want from me?"

Harry carefully withdrew his wand and nodded at Sirius to do the same. "I swear on my magic, I mean you no harm, no ill will, and only wish to break the monotony of your so-called unfortunately boring life."

Sirius made the same pledge and they both tucked their wands away.

"Happy?" Harry asked while digging into his satchel.

Hermione's wand arm lowered and she looked at the two Lord Blacks curiously. "Oaths can be broken."

"Oh brother," Sirius grumbled. "Why don't you cut loose for once? We're here to have some fun. Midnight skinny-dipping?"

"No!" Hermione insisted angrily knowing all too well the reputations of both Lord Blacks. "Where are we?"

"You're in denial," Sirius replied unable to help himself.

Harry groaned, pinching the bridge of his nose. "Feel free to curse him for that."

"What?" Hermione asked in confusion.

"That's the Nile," Harry said pointing towards the river. "He was making a punny."

Hermione giggled unable to help herself.

Harry saw Hermione laugh and turned to Sirius. "It's worse than we thought."

"I think we need skinny-dipping," Sirius said lifting his robe off.

"Stop!" Hermione said abruptly turning around. "I won't go along with this insanity unless you both stay fully clothed."

Sirius frowned and pulled his robe back on. "At least she didn't say anything-"

"Me too!" Hermione quickly added.

"Nuts," Sirius sighed. "Fine. Fully clothed adventure. That sounds just… wild."

Harry cast a few location charms and decided, "We're a couple kilometers south of where we want to be. You guys feel up to some hiking?"

"Let's float," Sirius suggested digging into his pocket. He withdrew a small yellow packet that he tore in half. The packet quickly expanded into a full-size octagonal raft that he dragged down to the river's edge.

"You carry an inflatable raft with you?" Hermione asked in confusion.

"Of course." Sirius nodded. "In case of emergencies or sudden pool parties."

Harry climbed into the raft and held out a hand to help Hermione in.

"Sudden pool parties?" Hermione questioned while delicately stepping into the raft.

"The parties aren't sudden. The pools are," Sirius added pushing the raft off the bank and hopping in himself.

"Don't ask," Harry interrupted Hermione.

Hermione saw them drifting out into the river and looked around. "Don't we need oars?"

"Naw," Sirius said. "That's what we keep Harry around for."

Harry had extended his invisible magical arms and was slowly paddling them downstream.

"That's right! Your magical appendages," Hermione brightened as the scholar inside her shined through. "I'd love to study them sometime. See what they can really do."

Harry and Sirius exchanged looks, both highly amused. Harry nodded at his godfather. "Go ahead."

"All of his magical appendages?" Sirius asked with a snicker. "Or just the invisible ones?"

Hermione blushed as she realized what she had said. "I didn't mean it like that."

"We're just giving you a hard time," Harry assured her while his arms continued to break the stillness of the water with small gentle splashes.

Hermione's cheeks were still pink as she replied, "Yeah I get the feeling that's exactly what you both want to give me."

Sirius gasped and turned to Harry. "A lewd joke! We're making progress already."

"You two are shameless," Hermione admitted with a grin.

"Pretty much," Sirius agreed digging out a bottle of firewhiskey.

Harry was leaning back looking up at the expansive sky. "That's a bright moon."

"It was full last night," Sirius reminded thinking of Remus.

Hermione took a moment to appreciate her surroundings, the crystal clear reflection on the river's surface, the nighttime sounds of frogs and insects, the gentle breeze of the comfortably cool night. "It's beautiful."

"And just think," Harry added. "If we hadn't kidnapped you, can you ever see yourself going for a float down the Nile on the spur of the moment?"

"This is crazy," Hermione half-heartedly complained. "You're just lucky it's a nice night."

"So tell us about yourself," Harry stated. "Why is it that you think you've had an unfortunately boring life?"

"I said it once," Hermione chided. "You don't need to keep using that phrase."

Harry accepted the bottle from Sirius and took a swig of the firewhiskey.

"Speaking of my life," Hermione turned towards Harry accusingly. "Just why do you know so much about me?"

Harry winked at her and offered the bottle. "That's classified, I'm afraid."

"Declassify it," Hermione ordered taking the bottle and knocking back a big gulp. She quickly began to cough as she swallowed the harsh liquid.

Harry was biting his lip and glanced at Sirius. Sirius just shrugged and supplied, "In another life, I bet you and Harry were best friends."

Hermione was wiping her face after the minor coughing fit and handed the bottle to Sirius. "What does that mean?"

"Don't do this, Hermione," Harry instructed. "Don't try to analyze things, don't break it down until everything has an explanation and you understand it all. Tonight is about you cutting loose and having some fun."

"You're not stalking me, are you?" Hermione warily asked.

"No, I'm not stalking you," Harry assured her. "Don't you trust me?"

Hermione was closely watching Harry looking for any clue to his mystery. "I don't know why, but for some reason I do."

Harry smiled brightly.

She turned to Sirius, "You, not so much."

"Good instincts," Harry agreed.

"Hey," Sirius said in defense of himself. "That's… alright fine. So tell us. You got a job? A boyfriend?" He paused before hopefully adding, "Maybe a girlfriend?"

Hermione glanced at Sirius and was going to ask but Harry immediately offered, "Yes, he really is that perverted."

Hermione nodded and decided to just trust her gut. "I'm the Assistant to the Deputy Director of Non-Human Relations for the Ministry of Magic."

"That's a heck of a title," Harry agreed thinking that was significantly lower than the position his Hermione had been offered by the Ministry. "How's the job?"

"It's fine," Hermione answered immediately.

"Ouch," Sirius said with a wince. "Sorry to hear that."

"It's not bad," Hermione continued. "I mean the work is good. House elf mistreatment is a much more important issue than people realize."

Harry had to look away to keep from laughing at her.

"I'm serious!" Hermione indignantly replied when she saw Harry's amusement.

"Hey, me too," Sirius was forced to interject.

"I'm not laughing at you," Harry explained to Hermione through his chuckles. He turned to Sirius, "And I'm definitely not laughing at you."

Sirius shrugged.

"It's just," Harry grinned at Hermione. "It's nothing. You're right. Most house elves do deserve better."

"Thank you," Hermione agreed. "And just so you know, jokes about your name Sirius, are the quickest way to get a woman to never want to sleep with you."

"Hey," Sirius replied.

"Ever," Hermione added. "Ever."

Harry smiled at Sirius' pouting. "Since you so kindly brought up the subject, Hermione, tell us, is there a significant other in your life?"

"No," Hermione answered. "Well, not really."

"Not really, huh?" Harry jumped on the phrase. "And does this man know he's not significant?"

Hermione looked away. "Probably not. I tried to explain that we should just be friends, but he talked me into calling it 'taking a break.'"

"Want us to kill him?" Sirius offered.

"No," Hermione glanced over at Sirius trying to judge the veracity of his comment. "Please don't."

"Fair enough," Harry agreed. "What else you got? Tell us something juicier. Like why you feel your life is boring."

"It's not boring," Hermione argued. "It's just… I don't know. I feel like I've missed out on things. And I feel like there should be more I'm doing, instead of being stuck in a job where the fact that I'm a woman doesn't matter, but the fact that my parents are muggles is one of the most important things about me."

"Pureblood bastards," Harry angrily mocked.

"That's us," Sirius agreed. "Well, me anyway. You're not exactly a pureblood."

"Shhh," Harry mock hushed the older man. "That's supposed to be our little secret."

"You're not a pureblood?" Hermione asked curiously. "But you're Lord Black."

Harry shrugged. "My mum was muggleborn." He paused and saw Hermione was looking for more explanation. "I got the title from my godfather. He died. Left me a big house and an evil house elf that told me to use a certain ring to fix the wards on the place. I put on the ring, fixed the wards, and only later found out it was a hereditary ring. The house elf was hoping the ring was going to kill me, not make me the new Lord Black."

Hermione frowned at the description of the elf. "He may have just been confused."

"No," Sirius assured her. "He was trying to kill him."

"So how are you Lord Black, then?" Hermione asked Sirius.

"Long story," Harry said. "We're not going to tell it. Besides, I think this is what we're looking for." Harry said paddling them off to the large recess where the river curved east.

"What are we looking for?" Hermione asked, seeing lots of dense foliage and signs of paths that had grown over years ago.

"This village was destroyed in 1893 by a nundu," Harry explained hopping out of the raft and dragging it up the bank. "It was the second time in three hundred years the village was visited by one."

"You're genuinely looking for a nundu," Hermione commented stepping out of the raft. "Have you been checked by a mind healer in a while?"

"Come on Granger," Sirius chided with a smile. "Grow a pair."

"I'm a woman," Hermione reminded.

Sirius frowned at the literal interpretation and added, "Grow a pair of tits?"

Hermione crossed her arms over her chest. "My breasts are just fine, thank you very much."

"That they are," Sirius happily agreed, drawing his wand and catching up to Harry.

Hermione looked out towards the river and thought she saw something large make a splash as it surfaced and dove back down. She quickly decided she didn't want to be alone and hurried to catch up to them. "Wait for me."

She ran past Sirius and caught up to Harry, grabbing onto his hand. "Don't you dare leave me alone out here in the middle of the night."

Harry looked down at their entwined hands and smiled at her. "You'll be fine." Harry reached an area with some rotted and broken down structures that once were huts. "This is the place."

"This is creepy," Hermione said, holding her wand in her free hand.

"If you see a nundu," Harry ordered. "Let me know."

"Sure thing," Hermione skeptically agreed.

"What do they look like?" Sirius asked staring off into the darkness.

Harry grinned as Hermione immediately responded to a question just like the Hermione he went to school with.

"They resemble leopards, but are more than three times their size, larger even than any of the muggle great cats. Contrary to popular belief they cannot turn invisible. In fact it is the rosettes on a nundu's back that have illusionary abilities allowing them to smoothly blend into their surroundings."

Sirius blinked and turned towards Hermione. "Okay…"

"Great big leopards," Harry summarized.

"Gotcha," Sirius agreed pulling out his omnioculars and turning back towards the darkness. "Are they ever normal sized leopards?"

"Maybe a baby nundu," Harry suggested while squinting in the distance. "Why?"

"Because I think see a baby nundu coming down from a tree through there," Sirius pointed. "It's crawling backwards down the trunk in goofy way."

"Really?" Harry said hurrying over towards Sirius.

"What?" Hermione squeaked knowing leopards were nocturnal hunters. "Come on guys. Hunting nundus is funny enough in theory, but let's not anger the dangerous wildlife please."

"Gimme those," Harry said grabbing the omnioculars from his godfather. "Oh I see it! It's creeping across the ground this way."

"Err," Sirius interrupted. "You need to look to your right. It's still in the tree I think."

Harry panned slightly and gasped. "Sweet! There's two baby nundus."

"They are not baby nundus!" Hermione whispered insistently. "But we should still get out of here."

Harry was continuing to focus on the large felines with the omnioculars switching between night vision and heat signatures.

"You can go back to the raft, if you want," Sirius suggested.

"I'm not going out there alone," Hermione hissed. "Come on you guys, let's go."

Harry sighed and handed the omnioculars back to Sirius. "Hermione's right."

"Thank god," Hermione relaxed for a moment.

"They're not baby nundus," Harry agreed. "Their heads are normal sized for those bodies. They're just leopards."

"I'm right about leaving, too, though, right?" Hermione pleaded. "Right?"

"They're headed this way," Sirius happily cheered.

"We should go." Hermione tried lying as she pulled on Harry's arm. "I'm a bleeder. And carry many contagious diseases."

Harry stood his ground shaking his head. "They just want to come over and say meow. That's cat for 'Hi Hermione.'" He paused and scratched his chin. "Or is it 'Die mudblood?' I get those two mixed up."

Hermione smacked Harry on the arm. "We don't have time for your stupid jokes."

"Yeah really, Harry," Sirius said with a frown. "We barely have enough time for the smart jokes as it is."

"You're not helping," Hermione whined, wanting to run but unprepared to leave Harry's side.

"Here," Sirius handed her the omnioculars. "You can see them too. They're right through there."

Hermione took the omnioculars and was surprised to find they showed heat signatures. "There are three of them!"

"Ooh, three," Sirius grinned. "First person to scratch one behind the ears gets free drinks."

"You're on," Harry quickly agreed. "Belly rubs count too."

"You guys are insane," Hermione pleaded. "What happened to swearing not to harm me?"

Harry patted Hermione on the top of her head and assured her. "We'll be fine. It's not like leopards can cast anti-apparition jinxes."

"That'd be scary if they could," Sirius agreed with a shiver.

Hermione twitched as she felt a magical wave run over her. "What was that?"

Sirius closed his eyes, concentrated, and grunted when nothing happened. "Ack. Anti-apparition."

Hermione quickly tried to apparate and slammed into the ward. She whimpered loudly and was starting to shake.

"Oh crap," Sirius's voice squeaked and took a step back.

Harry just chuckled happily. "Sorry guys. I couldn't resist."

Hermione started punching Harry as he removed the anti-apparition ward. "That wasn't funny! That was mean and nasty!"

Sirius snickered. "Actually it was pretty funny. I think a little pee came out."

Harry laughed and tried to calm Hermione. "Relax. The leopards can sense your fear."

"Everyone can sense my fear," Hermione begged. "I'm not making it a secret."

"Here kitty, kitty, kitty," Sirius said as one of the leopards emerged from the shadows and stopped to watch the three people. "Oh aren't you a big kitty."

"Grrr," the front leopard growled loudly trying to scare them off.

Sirius paused and turned towards Hermione. "Do leopards eat people?"

"There are some conflicting opinions on whether the aggressive behavior first observed-"

"Hermione," Harry interrupted.

"Yes," Hermione summarized as she gripped onto Harry's arm. "Yes they do."

A second leopard was hunched to the ground and inching forward with its shoulder blades up threateningly. "Grrr."

Sirius looked over and saw the second leopard had stopped moving forward. He got the feeling that was a bad sign. "I think I'm gonna…" With a sudden crack, Sirius apparated a safe distance behind Harry and Hermione.

"Rhawr!" Both leopards roared as they leapt through the air at the gunshot like sound.

Harry's invisible arms easily stopped both cats, slamming into them hard enough to flip them tail over head onto their backs. "Coward," he called out to Sirius.

Another crack sounded as Sirius apparated right next to Harry and Hermione. "You're the coward."

Hermione was unable to let bad logic go by without comment. "That doesn't make any sense."

"Speaking of big pussy," Sirius segued with a jerk of his thumb. "There's another leopard back there."

Harry was pushing the angry cats away, trying not to seriously injure them despite the fact that they kept coming.

"This is unnatural behavior," Hermione said, hunched down keeping a hand on Harry at all times. "Leopards aren't pack hunters. Occasionally they'll share territory but they shouldn't all be attacking."

"I knew it," Sirius argued. "Baby nundus."

"They're not baby nundus," Hermione insisted.

Sirius saw there was no reasoning with Hermione. "I'm going to make sure the raft is okay."

"Wait," Harry called out grabbing onto Sirius' arm just as he apparated. There was an extraordinarily loud crack as Sirius disappeared and Harry was left standing there holding Sirius' detached left arm. He glanced at Hermione, his face showing worry for the first time. "Oops."

Hermione screeched as several leopards charged and were again rebuffed by Harry's invisible arms.

"You splinched me!" Sirius shouted loudly in the distance.

"Sorry," Harry shouted back.

Hermione was watching the now four different leopards all prowling around her and Harry. "Go away!" She shouted while picking up rocks and throwing them at the leopards. "Get out of here!"

The cats were jumping away from the rocks but not backing down any.

Harry's mind began going off in dangerous directions. He turned to Hermione and said, "Cover me for a second."

"What?" Hermione yelped as Harry dropped to his knees. She hurriedly cast banishing charms at every leopard whether they were attacking or not. "What are you doing?"

"Shh," Harry shushed while casting a series of various charms on the unattached left arm he was still holding.

Harry jumped back to his feet and knocked back a quietly approaching leopard. "You missed that one. It could've killed us."

Hermione turned to look at Harry in disbelief.

"Now remember," Harry said. "Whatever happens, don't tell Sirius." And just like that, Harry chucked the extra appendage through the air like a stick for a dog. "Fetch!"

All four leopards closest to them chased after the lightly blood-covered limb.

Harry and Hermione just stood there watching as a fight quickly broke out for the arm. Two of the leopards each had an end and were wrestling in a vicious tug of war, while a third chomped down right in the middle, bending the arm at the elbow.

"No ear scratching or belly rubbing yet, right?" Sirius asked stealthily rejoining them.

"What took you so long?" Harry asked.

"Hello, splinch?" Sirius said pointing towards his empty sleeve. "I wasn't about to try apparating back to you."

"Well good," Harry said subtly glancing towards the leopards grouped together. "Because the sound of apparition is part of what's making them attack."

"Really?" Sirius asked.

Harry nodded.

Sirius began searching the ground around where they were standing. "What did you do with my arm?"

Harry flashed Hermione a look and innocently replied, "What arm?"

Sirius saw the leopards were growling in a pitched battle for dominance and suddenly took notice of what they were battling over. "What the-… Oh my-… Harry!"

"I'm sorry, Sirius," Harry assured. "I tried everything I could, but you know how Hermione gets-"

"You threw it and yelled fetch," Hermione argued.

Harry frowned. "No one likes a tattle tale."

Sirius was tempted to transform into his dog form but knew even if he managed it, he'd only have three legs and he'd be up against a pack of leopards. "Get me my arm back!"

Harry looked over and saw all of the leopards were now surrounding the arm, snapping their jaws, and swatting dangerously at each other. He glanced back at Sirius, "They really seem to like it."

"Harry!"

"They could be starving, you know."

"It's my arm."

"Fine," Harry said lifting his wand struggling to decide on what spell to use. Finally he sent a couple spanking hexes at the leopards and that just seemed to piss them off as two of them began to charge again.

Harry glanced back at Sirius. "You really need an extra arm? One could be plenty."

"Dammit Harry," Sirius swore.

"Oh for Merlin's sake," Hermione grumbled. She swung her arm in a wide motion and lobbed a large conjured cantaloupe through the air. The mid-sized fruit landed right next to one of the leopards. Her second attempt collided with the back of a leopard that sent it whimpering off.

"Good thinking," Harry agreed remembering when Hermione taught him this spell as well as the more draining version he preferred. He slashed his wand upward and swept his extended arm underhand, lobbing a conjured watermelon right next to the leopards.

Hermione and Harry repeated their motions raining down large round fruit and sending the leopards scampering in circles. Cantaloupe and watermelons were crashing into the leopards backs and bouncing off the ground in random directions.

Sirius could only look at his poor mauled arm in disbelief.

"You know you could try summoning it while we distract them," Harry suggested, sending another watermelon arcing through the night sky.

Sirius had his wand out and was attempting to summon his arm. "It's not working."

Harry was about to give up on hiding his giggles. "Maybe the leopards haven't figured out anti-apparition yet but they've mastered anti-summoning charms."

Hermione cracked first and started laughing.

Sirius realized he'd been had. "You bitches."

Harry caught Hermione's eye and joined her in laughter.

"I really thought they were chewing my arm up," Sirius admitted, holding his remaining hand over his heart.

"Yeah, about that…"

"Harry!"

"Sirius," Hermione explained. "I didn't see what Harry cast on your arm, but those leopards would have torn that thing to shreds by now if it wasn't protected."

"Shoo!" Sirius called out. "Go away!"

The tall grass on the other side of the leopards began to sway and a violent thrashing was heard.

"Or at least stay over there," Sirius corrected, taking a step back and moving behind Harry.

One last watermelon from Harry landed flush on a leopard's rump and it yelped out. All of the leopards then turned tail and ran leaving the arm behind as an afterthought.

Harry looked at Hermione curiously, while staying alert looking for danger.

Hermione shrugged. "They've been acting like a pack. I think we scared the leader away and the rest fell in line."

Harry looked over to see how confident she was in her theory.

"Maybe," Hermione added uncertainly.

Sirius jogged up over to his un-summonable arm. "Dammit Harry. That's gonna leave a scar."

"I did one shallow cut so a little blood would come out before I charmed it," Harry argued. "Most of that is just leopard slobber."

"That's a deep gash not a shallow cut," Sirius pouted.

"Don't be so melodramatic," Harry chided.

Hermione gasped loudly and fell backwards. "We should be dead." She mumbled to herself. "We should all be dead."

"That's melodramatic," Sirius said pointing towards Hermione. "I'm being reasonable."

Harry ignored his godfather and hurried over to Hermione. "What's going… holy shit! That thing is big. Is it dead?"

"This is insane," Hermione said shaking her head. "There's no way…"

Sirius walked to the edge of the high grass and saw what they were looking at. "Hey, nundu!" He glanced at Harry and walked right up to the massive beast. He rubbed his hand on its belly. "First."

"There's not a mark on it." Harry could see its eyes were still open but the magnificent creature was clearly no longer among the living. "What happened?"

"It's so soft," Sirius said rubbing the nundu's belly. "What is this thing? About four meters, you think?"

Harry saw Hermione had been shocked senseless and walked up to the head large enough to eat him in two bites. He pushed up the top lip and saw rows of sharp teeth. "It's still warm. I think this might be the pack leader and the reason the others ran away."

Hermione realized Harry was addressing her and nodded. "You're probably right. But what killed it?"

"I don't see any blood," Sirius commented, lifting up the large tail and fighting his animagus urge to sniff the beast's rear end. "Heart attack?"

Harry wrapped his hands around the front teeth and slowly pulled the massive jaws apart. He slammed the mouth closed and looked up. The others looked at him inquisitively as he repeated the motion and looked in the nundu's mouth again. "You gotta be kiddin' me."

"What is it?" Hermione asked.

Harry sighed. "The nundu suffocated. It couldn't breathe."

"Are you sure?" Hermione asked, finally stepping up to giant magical mammal. She looked in as Harry held the jaws open. "Oh."

Sirius walked around the supposed most dangerous creature in the world and looked through the sharp jagged teeth. He barked out a laugh when he was able to see down the feline's throat. Sticking out the behind the swollen tongue was the top half of a large watermelon. "I should have guessed."

"I didn't mean to kill it," Harry pleaded. "It was an accident."

"There's no way," Hermione shook her head, still in disbelief. "A nundu has never been subdued with less than a hundred wizards. It's simply not possible."

Sirius grinned. "You don't know our Harry too well obviously."

"I just wanted to ride on its back," Harry defended. "I didn't even know it was here."

Sirius was running his fingers through its silky smooth thick fur. "I bet it's easier on your bits to ride something this soft." Sirius grabbed a handful of loose skin with his only arm and climbed his way on top of the nundu. "Oh yeah, this would be great… I mean if you hadn't killed it first."

Harry just looked at the nundu in sorrow before smiling slightly. "It is cool seeing one up this close."

Sirius clambered to his feet and stood triumphantly atop the nundu. "I'm the king of the jungle. Top of the bad-ass chain." He was bouncing up and down, just trying to keep his balance. He looked down at the reflective multi-colored spots in the fur. "This thing is softer than my bed."

"Sirius, get down," Harry ordered.

"You're just jealous I got up here first," Sirius countered bouncing higher and higher on the swollen belly of the beast.

Harry saw Hermione walking around to the front examining the thick whiskers on the nundu. Harry pleaded, "Sirius, I really don't think you should-"

"Don't be such a baby," Sirius scolded while kicking his legs out with each successive jump as if he were on a trampoline. "What's the worst that could happen?"

Harry slowly opened his eyes having recognized the familiar sterile smell of a hospital and the feel of starched sheets. He looked up and saw Sirius closing the door behind him. He glanced to his left and saw the other bed in the room was occupied by Hermione.

"I've got muffins for everyone who's forgiven me," Sirius happily exclaimed.

"Hah," Hermione indignantly scoffed without even looking up.

"I said I was sorry," Sirius pleaded.

"You got banana nut?" Harry asked, trying to remember exactly why he was hospitalized again.

"That's the spirit," Sirius cheered handing Harry a muffin. "What about you, Hermione? Cream cheese or blueberry?"

Hermione's anger deflated momentarily. "Did you say cream cheese?"

Sirius happily passed her a muffin and watched as she greedily took a bite and sighed in contentment. "I knew you forgave me."

Harry looked over and saw Hermione's hair looked a lot frizzier than he remembered and he was briefly reminded of his former best friend. "My memory is still a bit fuzzy."

"Yeah," Sirius agreed. "The healers said this might happen."

Harry noticed Hermione wasn't as confused as him, but she was staying quiet. "I remember… oh crud. I remember a nundu. And… and watermelons?"

"Yeah," Sirius said, plopping down into the chair next to Harry's bed, staying a safe distance away from Hermione. "Okay, listen. Since we're all going to heal and be just fine, I can safely tell you that it was… hilarious."

"My breasts are purple!" Hermione scolded.

"And I told you I'll believe that when I see it," Sirius shouted back. He gently added, "Please?"

Hermione harrumphed and went back to giving Sirius the cold shoulder.

"Maybe later then," Sirius continued. "But I mean, have you ever seen those slow motion videos of a muggle standing in front of a cannon firing?"

Harry heard Hermione pout again and looked back at his godfather. "What?"

"Because it was just like that," Sirius cheered. "The way Hermione's body crumpled and her eyes bugged out when that watermelon came shooting out of the nundu's mouth and slammed right into her stomach."

Hermione was growling softly.

"And a little bit of her chest," Sirius corrected. "Or so she claims."

"I'm not showing you my tits," Hermione snapped.

"That's not what the Daily Prophet says," Sirius playfully whispered to Harry.

"What?" Harry questioned. "I mean… what?"

"What did you say?" Hermione asked looking straight at Sirius.

"Nothing," Sirius defended.

"You were supposed to bring the newspaper. Where is it?" Hermione demanded.

Sirius shook his head. "Not until you're nicer to me."

"Can you just tell me why…" Harry paused. "Hang on. You were jumping up and down on the nundu. That's why the watermelon blasted out of the dead nundu's mouth."

"You know that's one of those lines," Sirius idly commented, "that may never have been uttered before in all history."

"So why am I hospitalized and you're not?" Harry asked. He looked over at Hermione, "You should've killed him not me."

Hermione looked at Sirius. "Day's not over yet."

"Anyway," Sirius avoided Hermione's eyes and continued. "As it turns out, it appears the watermelon that had been blocking the airway and suffocated the nundu also was holding back the last of the nundu's poisonous breath."

"Oh dear," Harry commented as images came back to him. He turned to Hermione. "I threw up on you. Sorry about that."

Hermione was growling again.

"Yeah," Sirius agreed. "You two got the worst of the nundu's breath. I got my stomach pumped, arm attached, a couple potions, and released after an hour."

Harry looked down at his left arm. "So why is my arm bandaged?"

"That's Hermione's fault," Sirius said pointing his finger at the frowning young woman.

Harry looked at her and saw no explanation or apology coming. "Huh?"

"She wasn't crazy about being vomited on and shoved you-"

"He tripped," Hermione argued.

"Maybe a little of both," Sirius agreed. "But you fell backwards right into the open mouth of our dead nundu friend. Impaled yourself on a fang."

"That's right," Harry remembered with a smile looking at the bandage. "This will be even better than a tattoo with the matching basilisk scar on my the other arm."

"That was also when you managed to inhale the rest of the nundu's breath," Sirius added.

"Oh."

"Anyways, through my quick thinking," Sirius continued.

"Hah," Hermione scoffed again.

"I knew we needed your power to apparate us back to London. So I grabbed my arm, rounded up Hermione who was panicking-"

"I think I was entitled to a little panic after you cracked three of my ribs," Hermione explained.

"And together we apparated into the lobby of St. Mungos," Sirius finished. "Which was especially entertaining, because you happened to bring the dead nundu you were impaled on with you."

"Nice," Harry cheered.

"Yeah, it was great," Sirius laughed. "Two people just fainted right at the sight of you all bloody, hanging halfway out a gigantic nundu's mouth. I was swinging my splinched arm around, demanding help and poking people. And then you two both started convulsing… classic. Good times."

"Excellent," Harry agreed and looked over to the horrified look on Hermione's face. "You okay?"

"That was not excellent," Hermione shrieked. "That was not classic. That was stupid and that was dangerous."

"Po-tay-toe, Po-tah-toe," Sirius retorted. "Didn't you have fun?"

"No," Hermione said. "You two even made my hair curl."

Harry nodded. "I was wondering if I was remembering that right."

"It gets frizzy when I'm stressed or worried," Hermione explained.

"I knew it," Harry triumphantly announced having always suspected he was to blame for that.

Sirius chuckled and jerked his thumb towards Harry. "Imagine going to school with this one."

Hermione paled and shook her head. "My nerves would never have survived, let alone my hair."

"You're made of stronger stuff than you think," Sirius assured her.

Hermione took that as a compliment and tried to smile. "May I please see the paper now?"

Sirius reached into his inner robe pocket and asked, "May I please see-"

"No," Hermione answered immediately.

"Fine," Sirius agreed and handed over the Daily Prophet. "Congratulations. We made the front page."

Hermione accepted the paper and looked at the top article. Nundu Hunt Successful: Two Lord Blacks and one Ministry employee were all it took to subdue the most dangerous magical creature known to wizardkind.

"I'm convulsing in the picture," Hermione complained.

"Harry's hanging out of the nundu's mouth and convulsing, so I don't think you really should be complaining," Sirius argued.

Hermione quickly scanned the article that made the supposed hunt sound far more dramatic and dangerous. Her name was mentioned several times as part of the trio of hunters but not in any way that offended her or made her sound bad. "This is all wrong, but I don't see why you didn't want me to read this."

Sirius looked at Harry briefly and quietly admitted, "There's another article on page three."

Harry saw the hesitancy in Sirius' statement and looked over at Hermione as she hurriedly opened the Prophet to page three.

"What!" Hermione shrieked. "What the hell is this?" She continued to mumble to herself as she read through the article.

"What is it?" Harry asked Sirius since it appeared Hermione wasn't going to be helpful.

"Turns out we're gay lovers," Sirius said with a shrug. "Rita Skeeter seems to think we're both tops and that's how we both managed to get the title of Lord."

Harry furrowed his brow. "What does that have to do with Hermione-"

Hermione interrupted as she loudly read, "Once again thumbing their noses at tradition the Lords Black have chosen plain looking muggleborn Hermione Granger to carry their gay baby! Who the hell does she think she is? Ohh, I am going to give this Rita Skeeter a piece of my mind."

"Gay baby?" Harry questioned. "That's not even proper writing. It makes it sound like our baby is gay."

"Well if you're gay and I'm gay," Sirius argued. "Then there's no way I'm raising any hetero baby. Not if I have anything to say about it."

"That's our baby," Harry scolded. "You will love it no matter what."

"See how easy that was?" Sirius grinned. "I'm the top, you're the bottom, acting like a sissy already."

"Why aren't you more upset by this?" Hermione questioned, realizing Harry and Sirius were joking about the article.

Harry looked at Sirius and back at Hermione. "Because it's not true?"

"Well," Sirius wavered. "They were right in that just the two of us went out and bought muggle pregnancy tests together."

Harry nodded. "You know that mixed with the whole dual Lords thing isn't really too much of a stretch."

"That's not the point," Hermione insisted. "These are outright boldfaced lies."

Harry tried to calm her. "Your picture is on the front page. People will know you're not plain looking."

"Thank you," Hermione smiled at the compliment before going back on her angry rant. "But reporters can't just make up stories because they want to."

Sirius wagged his finger. "You weren't this upset even though you said the front page article was all wrong."

"Well, if you want," Harry suggested. "I'm pretty sure Rita Skeeter has the illegal animagus form of a beetle. You could use that to blackmail her."

"Two wrongs don't make a right," Hermione argued.

"But seven lefts do," Sirius helpfully added earning a few odd looks.

"Or you could capture her in her animagus form and keep her locked in a jar for a year," Harry offered.

Hermione frowned harshly. "Not even you idiots are that cruel. Kidnapping and holding her hostage for a year is more than a touch extreme."

Harry glanced at Sirius and shrugged.

"Besides," Hermione explained. "People would notice she was missing and be looking for her everywhere."

Harry rubbed his chin in thought. "You'd think so, wouldn't you?"

"No," Hermione shook her head decisively. "I'm going to write a letter to the editor and if they don't print a retraction then I'm going to pursue a civil suit against her and the Daily Prophet."

Harry was about to comment on how crazy that idea was when a healer entered the room.

"Our potions lab has just finished mixing your salve, Miss Granger," the healer said while handing her a decent sized white jar. "The bruising was extremely deep but rub this into the affected area twice a day and it should be gone within a week."

"Thank you," Hermione replied. "So am I free to go?"

"Take it easy for the next day or so, but yes," the healer smiled as he turned to leave. "You are free to go."

She ran into the bathroom and changed into her cleaned robes. When she came back out, she looked over at Harry and Sirius and realized this was goodbye.

Sirius offered, "If you need any help with that rubbing-"

"Stop." Hermione was fighting the urge to curse him and wondered just when she got so violent. "I know… well I suspect anyway, that you two had good intentions, but please… don't do me any more favors." She turned to walk out the door.

"Wait," Harry called out. "At least you can appreciate your unfortunately boring life a bit more, now, right?"

Hermione's face twitched at the phrase but found herself quickly agreeing with the sentiment. "Maybe."

"So if you ever need a dose of excitement," Harry offered and given the look on her face added, "perhaps a smaller one, something like dinner, or a big brother to talk to the ex-boyfriend who can't take a hint. Just give us a shout, okay?"

Hermione's face softened showing no real hard feelings. "Give me a couple years to think it over. Goodbye Harry, Sirius."

Harry and Sirius waved goodbye as the Hermione of this world walked out of the room.

"There goes the mother of our gay baby," Sirius wistfully commented.

Harry turned to Sirius. "Whatever happened to the nundu?"

Sirius smiled brightly. "All taken care of. And I broke into Hermione's place and left her a present in her living room."

"Oh?"

"No, not the Padfoot kind," Sirius clarified. "She's got a brand new coffee table with four of the sturdiest legs with giant paws you'll ever see."

"Nice."

Sirius shrugged. "It should make for a good conversation piece."

"And us?"

"Great big nundu skin rug in front of the fire place," Sirius said with a lecherous grin. "And a mounted head that still has your blood on its teeth."

Harry smiled just picturing it. "Man, we're cool."

"Hard to believe we didn't completely win over Hermione yet," Sirius agreed.

Harry shrugged. "Yeah, I'm not sure the Hermione of this world is prepared to live in ours."

"No?"

"But I know the Hermione I grew up with would definitely appreciate our efforts to loosen her up a bit." Harry frowned. "Assuming she wasn't completely jealous of her hair."

Chapter 20

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"Are you sure this is the place?"

Harry nodded. "You remember the oculamagi spell I taught you?"

"Yeah," Sirius grumbled. "But that one gives me a headache. Can't I just use the one I normally do? Or the omnioculars?"

"The one you normally use is the one built into the omnioculars."

"Perfect," Sirius cheered.

"How many times do we have to do this?"

"But I like the omnioculars."

"I do too," Harry agreed. "The omnioculars are great for heat signatures, seeing through solid objects, recording, playback, zooming, and settling arguments over estimated nipple size. But for seeing magic, only the simple and generic spells can be put on them. You could cast the same spell on a window, my glasses, or any other object. The spell I taught you goes deeper into optical perception for when you need to see the real differences in magics, the subtle nuances."

Sirius frowned. "This is going to be a learning experience, isn't it?"

"Yes, and besides, what I'm about to do could just about blind you if you used your spell. Now come on," Harry urged.

Sirius was pouting but cast the spell over his eyes and turned towards Harry.

"Watch carefully," Harry said before clapping his hands together, sending out a wave of magic. Harry pointed over to their left. "There. Did you see it?"

Sirius looked in the direction Harry pointed. "No, I didn't see anything."

"Look right there and pay attention," Harry said, clapping his hands together again.

Sirius blinked. "I missed it. Do it again."

Harry clapped out another heavier wave.

Sirius turned to Harry hopelessly and complained, "I don't see anything."

"Turn around," Harry said as he clapped and sent a wave behind them. "See how various spots appear dependent on their innate absorption of the magic?"

"Sort of," Sirius agreed.

"Now look this way," Harry said repeating the gesture in the original direction.

"No spots?" Sirius asked. "That's what I'm supposed to see?"

Harry nodded. "That is the sign of a weakened Fidelius charm."

"How could you possibly see-" Sirius quickly changed directions realizing what Harry said. "We're breaking down a Fidelius? I didn't think that was possible."

"It only works when the secret keeper is dead," Harry explained. "If you know the general area, you can find a spot that's hiding magic, then you flood the surroundings, and you can locate the keystone. If the secret keeper is alive though, you won't get anything."

"How long did it take you to find this?"

"Long enough," Harry said walking up to where he believed the Fidelius to be.

"And you're sure this place is abandoned?"

Harry shrugged. "It's an old bunker Grindelwald used for human experimentation. Some wizards, mainly women and children though."

Sirius turned to stare at Harry. "Well that's pleasant."

Harry nodded. "I'm going to flood the area. You should see the anchor stones start to light up. The red one is the keystone. When you know where the keystone is, blast the bloody hell out of it. Once it's moved enough, the Fidelius will come crashing down."

Sirius felt a headache forming but nodded, keeping his eyes open. "Do it to it."

Harry cast a large scale net and began to expel wild unformed magic. On the scale required, Harry knew it would be tiring but was confident he could manage it.

"Anytime you're ready," Sirius chided.

"You've got the easy part," Harry whined as his body began to tremble. He kept funneling more and more magic into his net, trying to ignore the exhaustion he felt.

"You want some sex to go with that wine?"

Harry snorted before grunting under the effort. "Don't make me laugh."

Sirius happily taunted. "Well then probably shouldn't look at my-ooof!" Sirius crumpled to the ground as an invisible arm punched him in the crotch. Sirius' voice went up two octaves and squeaked out, "You bastard."

"Dammit," Harry said, closing his eyes trying not to lose his hold on the net. "Come on, hurry up and blast it."

Sirius took his sweet time getting back up, easily spotting the five anchor stones glowing brightly as the magic of the net became thicker. One of the points of the pentagon had turned pink and was unmistakably the keystone. "None of them are red yet."

"Keep… looking," Harry wheezed, forcing more magic out.

"Does dark pink count for anything?"

"Padfoot!" Harry snapped.

"Fine," Sirius grumbled as he carefully aimed his wand and fired four quick blasting curses one after the other. The sudden precise jolt shifted the keystone just enough.

The air around them lit up brightly and Harry finally let go of his hold on the magical net. "Oh, thank Merlin."

Sirius watched entranced as multi-colored sparks began to wink in and out of existence through the air. It started slowly with just a few specks here and there before turning into a shower of magic crashing down. A loud crack echoed around the clearing and a thick metal door was visible where there used to be none.

"You're sure this thing is empty?" Sirius asked walking up to the rusty door.

"Wait," Harry panted out, hunched over, catching his breath. He dug up a pepper-up potion and swallowed it down.

"What is it?" Sirius asked. "Is the door booby-trapped?"

"No," Harry said shaking his head. "There's nothing on the door. Probably so you'll relax and let your guard down."

"So we're not going in the door?"

"No, we are," Harry said standing up and opening the door. "Just… how do feel about the sound of children screaming while being burnt alive?"

Sirius looked at Harry oddly. "I suppose I would be against the sound of burning, screaming children."

Harry waved Sirius on down the concrete stairwell. "If this is anything like I expect, then… well, remember how I said Grindelwald used this for experimentation?"

Sirius stopped and looked at Harry. "There's really creepy stuff and creepy kids in here, aren't there?"

"Some of the experiments didn't exactly die. Frankly, I'm not sure they could. And it's very possible they've…" Harry's voice dropped and he mumbled the words, "bendurned inna livinafury."

"You mind repeating that so that I can understand it?" Sirius insisted. "You know I'm not moving until you do."

"I was saying it's likely there are mutated living Inferi children just inside that door," Harry said pointing towards the end of the corridor they were in.

"Living Inferi?" Sirius repeated incredulously. "Why do dark wizards have to keep out-eviling each other?"

Harry shrugged. "For the same reason they also act like peacocks, trying to be more dignified and slick talking than everyone else?"

Sirius frowned. "Uncontrollable homosexual urges?"

"I was thinking daddy issues," Harry replied. "But that was as good an answer as any."

"Fire kills them?"

"Dark wizards? Usually."

"Not dark wizards," Sirius grumbled. "The living Inferi."

"Oh them. Yeah, fire holds them back," Harry explained. "I'm not so sure they can be destroyed considering the body keeps moving even if you cut off the head."

"Lovely," Sirius commented.

Harry swirled his wand creating a fire whip that encircled and protected his body. "I'll go for the cube. You make sure the door doesn't close behind us."

Sirius copied Harry's motion and was also surrounded by a spiral of fire. "I can do that."

Harry nodded. "Ready?"

Sirius nodded back, keeping a constant distance between them, so as not to burn each other.

"Go," Harry called out swinging the door open and running into the dark chamber. He sent a lumos charm up to the ceiling illuminating the room, as several decaying zombie like young girls all came to life.

Sirius stood just inside the door, watching a dozen of the creatures focus their attention on Harry. He sent off a couple of basic incendio charms when a half dozen of the freakish zombie children turned towards him.

Sirius winced as they started screaming but kept coming. He glanced over and saw Harry vault up the first step towards the altar at the end of the room.

Harry took one step up the stairs when a blue spell came zipping out of the darkness and rammed into his abdomen with the force of a dozen bludgers. His cloak absorbed some of the impact but he was launched bodily through the air sliding to a stop halfway between the altar and Sirius.

Harry groaned in extreme pain.

"Harry?" Sirius asked curiously.

"Not… part… of the plan."

Sirius saw the Inferi started chattering nonsensically and were quickly converging on Harry. "Dammit," he swore, turning to the nearest Inferi. He released the ring of fire surrounding him and cast a cutting curse straight at the young girl's neck, slicing cleanly through. A banishing charm sent her body flying backwards and he quickly grabbed her slimy head by the hair. He positioned it as a makeshift doorstop holding the metal chamber's exit open.

Sirius charged towards Harry letting loose fire charms and whips the whole way. "Stay down!" he ordered sending waves of fire straight over the top of Harry's body.

"Not a problem," Harry wheezed, grateful for the assistance.

As soon as Sirius was close enough, he re-cast the ring of fire to protect himself and Harry from the screaming Inferi children.

"You okay?" Sirius asked noticing Harry had started to sit up before collapsing back to the ground.

"Why is it always my ribs that break?"

Sirius answered right away. "Because your arm or leg would be much harder to deal with."

Harry rolled over onto his belly. "Good point." He was able to push himself up and smiled weakly at his godfather. "Thanks."

Sirius pulled Harry up to his feet. "I didn't see what happened. Just saw you doing your impression of a watermelon in a nundu's mouth."

"I don't know," Harry commented putting pressure on his lower ribcage. He looked through the flames of Sirius' protection as a scraggly ancient looking figure emerged from the shadows. "What the fuck…"

Sirius saw the pale withered looking man catch the light of the lumos above. His flesh was similar to the Inferi, decaying horribly. He had an empty eye socket that appeared to be a black bottomless pit. "Does that guy look familiar to you?"

The old twisted man's posture shifted into a much more imposing stance. He lifted a thin bony hand and another blue spell erupted straight from his palm headed straight for the Lord Blacks.

Harry's invisible magical arms grabbed the nearest mutant Inferi and held it up in the path of the curse. It exploded with a wet shower of pungent decay as the half-blocked spelled collided with them both.

Sirius' fire shield dissipated as they were knocked to the floor.

"Fuck," Sirius grumbled.

Harry hurriedly cast three incendiary spells setting the nearest approaching Inferi alight with purple flames. "Get that fire shield around us," Harry instructed as he cast a strong magical shield to deflect the next powerful blue spell headed their way.

Sirius sent a line flames spiraling around them, preventing any Inferi from reaching them as the old zombie wizard's spell reflected off Harry's shield and crashed into the ceiling. "Who or what is that thing?"

Harry sent a blasting curse at the wispy old silent man.

The pale figure just held the same hand up and absorbed the incoming spell.

"Dammit," Harry swore. He glanced at Sirius and made sure the Inferi weren't getting to close. "What it is, I'm really not sure. But who… well… I think that's the body of Grindelwald."

"What?" Sirius squeaked glancing at the man sending another blue spell their way. "I thought Dumbledore killed him."

Harry shook his head and answered quietly over the still screaming young female Inferi. "Not sure about this world, but in ours, Dumbledore defeated him. He just didn't exactly kill him."

"What'd he do?" Sirius asked flinching as another blue spell got a bit too close for comfort.

Harry shrugged. "Albus' portrait didn't know the exact magic, and even if it did, it wouldn't have told me. But I'm pretty sure he sort of… eradicated his soul."

"Oh, is that all?"

Harry shrugged. "If the same thing happened here, and someone were to have tried resurrecting him, unaware of the condition of the former Dark Lord's everlasting soul, well," Harry nodded towards the decaying old wizard. "I reckon that might be what happens. No soul, no mind, just a dumb, powerful semi-animated weapon."

"Think we can take him?" Sirius questioned, sending flames towards more nearing Inferi.

Harry deflected another blue spell into far wall. It let out a loud clang as it hit and the whole chamber shook. Harry sighed. "I think we better try soon or he's going to bring this bunker down on top of us."

"I don't suppose they forgot to protect the cube from summoning?"

Harry shook his head. "It looks like it takes the Grindel-zombie a second or two to absorb spells, and he's chained to the wall. The closer we get the harder it'll be to avoid those impact blasts. On the plus side, that's all it seems able to cast." Harry turned towards the loud Inferi that kept coming. He shouted back, "And at least he's not screaming like these other bitches!"

Sirius saw how irritated Harry was getting and asked, "Feel better now?"

"No." Harry frowned. "Shit!" He hurriedly tried to block the blue spell, just barely getting a shield up in time, though he was knocked off his feet, dangerously close to the flames of Sirius' fire cage.

"Careful," Sirius warned holding Harry back and helping him to his feet. "We're over-thinking this one," Sirius said, canceling his ring of fire and tossing Harry his wand. "Cover me."

Harry snatched the wand from midair as Sirius transformed into his animagus form and began to run straight towards the poorly animated corpse of Grindelwald. Harry used Sirius' wand to cast a fire whip that he swung over his head like a lasso, fending off screeching Inferi children, while he used his own wand to send spell after spell towards Grindelwald.

The decrepit wraith-like thing was too busy absorbing spells from Harry to cast anything at the large black dog sprinting towards him.

Sirius bounded up the steps and leapt onto the altar. He grabbed Ravenclaw's cube in his mouth as his momentum took him sliding off the back side of the altar.

Harry was trying to hold back all the Inferi while still raining spells down on Grindelwald but he was tiring too quickly.

A blue spell rocketed at Sirius' back but the animagus was running in so many random directions that it flew past, missing him and crashed into the ground. Unfortunately the canine's surprise at the close call took him right into the path of Harry's fire whip. There was a loud sizzle as it burnt Sirius' tail.

Sirius had a mouthful of founder's artifact and could only whimper and whine as he barreled by Harry. He leapt straight over the slimy Inferi girl's head still serving as a door stop and was clear of the hazardous chamber.

Harry saw Grindelwald's body seemed to be turning greener and shaking from all the magic it had absorbed. His instincts were telling him something bad was about to happen. He turned and ran right after Sirius, kicking the girl's head out of the way, as the heavy metal door clanged shut when an impact spell slammed into it.

Sirius had transformed back and was rubbing his bottom with a painful wince. "You burnt my tail."

"Not now," Harry snapped, pulling Sirius with him as he dashed for the exit.

Sirius felt the bunker begin to shake and realized Harry running away was a sign he should be running too. He gripped the cube tighter and took the stairs three at a time up and out of the bunker.

Harry swung the metal door shut and pulled the handle sealing it closed. He relaxed momentarily and saw Sirius was as winded as he was.

The ground rumbled threateningly and Sirius looked at Harry. "Maybe we should…"

"Good idea," Harry agreed and the two of them started to run further away from the bunker as the entire forest shook from the massive underground explosion.

The metal door was launched high into the air as a column of pungent black and brown flames kissed the tree tops.

Harry had tumbled to the ground, right near Sirius and was watching the night sky. He pointed out the falling door as it came crashing down, landing with a thud embedded into the soil.

Harry once again let out the breath he had been holding and laid back tiredly. "What was that cover me?"

"It worked, didn't it?" Sirius said handing the cube to Harry.

Harry accepted one of Rowena Ravenclaw's less famous inventions and wondered if it had ever been coated in so much dog slobber before. "Yeah, it did."

"You didn't have to burn my tail," Sirius grumbled rubbing his sore bottom.

Harry frowned. "And you didn't have to force me to cover you with my broken ribs without giving me a second's pause."

"Again with the whining," Sirius chided with a smile. "No one likes a wimp, Harry."

Harry grumbled. "Come on. Let's drop this off at home and get to St. Mungos."

Sirius stood up and helped Harry to his feet. "We really should look into hiring our own healer."

Harry grunted his assent. "That's actually a good idea."

Sirius' eyes glittered mischievously. "I bet Sarah would make a house call for you."

"Die."

"Mmm," Tonks moaned happily. "I swear the house elves must hide the good ice cream for you because it was never this tasty when I was a student."

Lily licked her spoon and asked, "What flavor you got there?"

Tonks turned her tub around to look at the handwritten label. "Butterscotch Fudge Chunk Delight."

"That is a good one," Lily said snagging a spoonful from Tonks' tub. "Try this."

Tonks scooped a heaping spoonful of swirled pink and white from Lily's tub. She put it in her mouth and let out a contented sigh. "That's nummy."

"Cherry Marshmallow Cheesecake," Lily announced, pointing at her tub. "This one's low fat frozen yogurt."

"That's not low fat," Tonks argued. "No way."

"That's what the house elves tell me," Lily insisted. She tried to hide her little smirk as she added, "Although, I may have instructed the house elves to lie to me a little bit."

Tonks pat her chest a little bit and let out a loud echoing belch. "Wow. That even tasted good the second time."

Lily raised a curious eyebrow. "Are you challenging the champion?"

"Let's see what you got," Tonks taunted.

Lily opened her mouth and swallowed a gulp of air. She raised her hand and repeated with another gulp before letting loose a deep reverberating burp, more than twice as loud and long as Tonks' had been.

A house elf appeared with a pop. "Did youse call for me, Missum Potter?"

Tonks had to look away, because she was struggling to hold back her laughter.

Lily waved off the confused and curious elf. "No, Irma. If I did, I didn't mean to."

" Okays," Irma the house elf happily replied and popped away.

Tonks gave up holding back and outright laughed at Lily.

Lily raised an arm in victory. "Still the King."

"You summoned a house elf," Tonks said through her snickering. "That's a magical gift if I've ever seen one."

"Not a gift," Lily insisted. "It took years and years of practice."

"James must be so proud," Tonks said, wiping away a fake tear. She grabbed another spoonful from Lily's tub.

Lily shook her head. "He'd probably ask Madame Pomfrey to give me a check-up."

"Your husband doesn't know?" Tonks gasped and mischievously grinned. "What to do with this morsel of blackmail. What to do…"

"You will do nothing," Lily said, shaking her spoon at Tonks. "Unless you want your Dad to hear about how lovely your graduation party really was."

"Oh lordy," Tonks happily recalled. "One of these days it'll be you calling me to bring clothes and bail money. Then, then I shall I regain the upper hand."

Lily smiled. "Just think how much you've matured since those days."

Tonks sighed. "I really don't have any good blackmail material on you, do I?"

Lily shook her head proudly.

"I've got tons on Sarah," Tonks idly commented. "But nothing juicy on you."

"You've got-" Lily had to pause and squint, tilting to the side as she passed gas. "You've got what on Sarah?"

"Nuh-uh," Tonks retorted. "It does me no good if I were to tell you."

"Come on," Lily urged, letting out another squeaking fart. "You can tell me."

"Maybe once the statute of limitations has passed," Tonks cruelly hinted. She made a face and leaned back, "You're putting some stink out."

Lily shrugged unconcerned. "Ice cream always gives me the toots."

"Speaking of the toots," Tonks smoothly segued. "What did you and Harry talk about when you two snuck off?"

Lily smirked. "Why Tonks Lupin, do I sense… jealousy?"

"Oh please," Tonks shook her head. "You're the last person I'd be jealous of when it concerns Harry."

"What's that supposed to…" Lily stopped as her eyes widened. "You know!"

Tonks blanched and tried to backtrack. "Know? Know what? What did he tell you?"

"You know why we both feel weird around each other," Lily insisted. "You know what he's hiding."

"I don't know what you're talking about," Tonks lied unconvincingly.

Lily didn't believe her. "Phooey. He's your Lord too."

Tonks shook her head. "He only plays the Lord card when it's advantageous for me."

"Of course you know what he's hiding," Lily realized. "You've slept with him enough."

"I'm not sure 'enough' is a word I would've ever used," Tonks said with a grin. Her smile faltered, suddenly remembering who she was talking to.

"So," Lily cajoled. "What's it like? Rough? Gentle?"

Tonks began to feel uncomfortable.

"Is he big?"

Tonks began to feel really uncomfortable.

"Oh relax," Lily said swatting Tonks' shoulder at the face she was making. "I would never cheat on James. But that doesn't mean you can't share all the juicy, carnal details."

"It's… fine."

"It's more than fine," Lily argued. "Or you wouldn't have kept coming back, what is it, three, maybe four times?"

"A few more than that," Tonks admitted. "But it's not what you think. He's a friend. We go out drinking. Some nights, I'll meet someone. Some nights, I won't. It's the same for him. And on some of those nights when neither of us is going home with someone, we'll just… go home together."

"If you say so," Lily half-heartedly agreed.

"Every unattached girl should have a spare wand she can call on when she needs it."

Lily innocently asked, "And just how many inches is that spare wand?"

Tonks chortled at having walked into that one. "You are horrible."

"Just looking out for my girl," Lily grinned. "You know I consider you family."

"I know," Tonks grinned, tilting to the side as she too let out a little flatulence. "It's just… weird talking to you about Harry."

"Why is it weird?"

"It's just…" Tonks stopped herself from saying too much. "Never mind."

"You're the one who brought him up," Lily pointed out, scraping the bottom of her tub for one last spoonful.

"Well I wanted to know what you thought of him," Tonks argued.

"But not because you're feeling protective or jealous over him," Lily said.

"No more protective or jealous than I would over Jimmy," Tonks assured her. "Like you said, we're family. And so is Harry." Tonks quickly added, "For me."

"I certainly hope you don't have the same sort of feelings for Jimmy that you do for Harry," Lily warned.

"He has gotten pretty cute," Tonks playfully commented.

"Tonks!"

"I'm just kidding," Tonks assured her raising both hands in surrender. "In case you forgot, I changed more than a couple of Jimmy's diapers."

Lily grumbled. "You probably changed more than his father did."

"But if you really want to know," Tonks said. "I was asking what you thought of Harry, so that I could make fun of him, next time I see him. Not because I'm jealous."

Lily was scrutinizing Tonks trying to figure out what exactly that implied. "Truthfully, I'm not sure what to make of him."

"He's a good guy," Tonks assured her.

"He's definitely cute," Lily admitted. "In some ways he reminds me of how I envisioned James to be."

Tonks knew she was treading into dangerous territory. "Really?" she said unable to keep the squeak from her voice.

Lily nodded. "You never really knew us that well before we lost our Harry, but James was a lot more…" she paused trying to think of the best word. "Happy. He laughed all the time and got into a lot of harmless trouble. When he was with Sirius, not your Lord, but Harry's godfather Sirius… those two caused so much havoc. Kinda like the way the two Lord Blacks are, now that I think about it."

Tonks smiled sadly, silently urging Lily to continue.

"I never realized just how much of that was Sirius' influence on him," Lily admitted. "Losing Harry was enough to break both of us, but losing his best friend too… it was like James decided he had to grow up in an instant. In some ways, I think he blamed Sirius as much as he blamed himself for Harry's death."

Tonks nodded. "I've heard some stories from Dad and seen pictures, but even still it's hard to imagine James that way."

"I love my husband dearly," Lily agreed. "But even I, sometimes, think he needs a little more…" She swallowed another mouthful of air and let loose a thick, guttural burp.

Tonks snickered happily. "You are the King."

The two women looked up as Sarah Potter walked in the room.

Sarah saw her mother and Tonks lying on opposites ends of the couch in Lily Potter's staff quarters. She sniffed the air twice and frowned. "Have you been eating ice cream?"

Tonks and Lily both just laughed in response.

"I take it Dad's not here?"

Lily shook her head. "He's working late tonight."

"Well in that case," Sarah looked both ways and pushed out her stomach as she let fly a fart that put even Lily's belching to shame.

"Good lord," Tonks snickered.

"I've been holding that in since lunch," Sarah explained as she walked over towards the chill-cabinet and grabbed a tub of ice cream.

"Yeah," Lily smiled weakly. "At that, my daughter is the King."

"It sounded like you were drowning a kelpie," Tonks vividly described.

"Tell me about it," Sarah grumbled plopping down into the empty chair. "You know, one time, I actually summoned a house elf."

Tonks just laughed and pointed at Lily.

"How was your day?" Lily asked, not in the mood to explain to her daughter.

"Tiring," Sarah said digging into her tub of Double Mocha Peanut Butter. "I think I pissed Poppy off. She made me clean and organize the entire store room."

"Better than bedpan duty," Tonks offered.

"Don't remind me," Sarah said with a grimace. Her face brightened as she turned to Tonks, "But I ran into someone very interesting at the Hog's Head the other night."

"Oh yeah?" Tonks asked glancing towards Lily.

Sarah smiled devilishly and she swallowed a mouthful of ice cream. "A certain adorably cute Lord Harry Black was flirting with me."

"What?" Tonks scoffed out before she could stop herself.

Lily and Sarah both turned towards Tonks. Lily smirked, "Care to revise your opinion on jealousy?"

Tonks opened her mouth, unable to think of what to say.

"Relax," Sarah assured her. "Nothing happened. Not that I was opposed to the idea, but he got all freaked out when he realized who I was and who my parents were. Thanks a lot for that, Mum."

The relief on Tonks' face was clear as day. Lily noticed it and asked, "If it's not jealousy-"

"It's not," Tonks interjected.

"Then it must be that something else you know," Lily added. "Care to share?"

Tonks bit her bottom lip and added, "You know what? Let's go with jealousy."

"You're no fun," Lily pouted and turned towards her daughter. "And you, young lady, need to stop thinking about Lord Harry Black that way."

"What's going on?" Sarah asked, waggling her spoon between Tonks and her mother.

"There's something funny about him," Lily explained and saw Tonks wasn't going to be forthcoming. "Tonks knows what it is."

"What is it?" Sarah asked curiously.

Tonks shook her head. "No way. My lips are sealed."

"So you do know his secrets," Lily grinned victoriously.

Tonks pretended to zip her lips shut and shook her head.

The two female Potters were all set to pounce on Tonks, who was increasingly feeling as if she were cornered. She was saved by the appearance of James Potter.

"I've been doing paperwork for seven hours straight," James complained as he walked into his wife's quarters. "And I… good lord. What's that smell?"

Lily flashed a look at Tonks and Sarah, calmly answering, "Your son let off a dung bomb earlier."

James shook his head. "I swear it's those Lord Blacks. They're a bad influence on him."

"You know what? It's late," Tonks said jumping up. "I should get going. See you tomorrow, boss. Night Lily, Sarah."

"Good night, Tonks," James said as she hurried out the portrait. He walked back towards the bedroom taking off his wand holsters as he went. He stuck his head back in the front room and added distastefully, "It was a super dung bomb, wasn't it?"

Lily had to gulp and cover her mouth to hide her amusement.

James smiled at his wife, turning back towards the bedroom. "You and your dainty little burps."

Bellatrix cast a lumos charm, illuminating the darkened room. "Huh."

Hundreds of portraits covered all four walls like a rogue's gallery of angry and disgruntled stares.

"Well that's… different."

"She's a Black," Phineas Nigellus announced from his frame by the door.

"Have you come to help us?" a harsh looking old woman asked.

Bellatrix frowned. "Help you? Help you with what?"

"She doesn't know," Phineas explained, narrowing his eyes at Bellatrix. "Those two Lords of yours have locked and bound us all to our frames."

Bellatrix looked around the room recognizing many names and families, suddenly putting two and two together. "Ohhh."

"Yes," Phineas mocked. "Oh."

"I don't think I'm supposed to be in here," Bellatrix admitted. She saw the look on Phineas' face and added, "And what are you doing here? You're a Black."

"Those thieves are trying to enslave portraits' loyalty to create some sort of cockamamie spy network," Phineas explained.

"But you're a Black," Bellatrix repeated. "Weren't you painted and charmed to the family?"

"One of his portraits was," Harry answered from the door. "But that's the frame I swiped from the Headmaster's office at Hogwarts."

"Oh," Bellatrix turned around and saw Harry did not look pleased. "I'm not supposed to be here, am I?"

"You shouldn't have even been able to find this room," Harry said with a frown.

"I asked Kreacher if there were any other rooms to explore and he led me here."

"Kreacher!" Harry shouted.

Kreacher didn't appear with a pop but slowly walked down the hall, grumbling to himself stopping outside the door. "Stupid mudblood Master. Yelling louder. Kreacher doesn't care. Punish Kreacher. Kreacher will make babies cry-"

"Shut up," Harry ordered forcefully.

"Yes Master," Kreacher acquiesced despite being clearly proud of his actions.

Harry was tempted to just punt the troublesome servant but restrained himself.

Bellatrix suggested, "I'll kill him, if you don't want to."

Harry paused to consider the offer.

"I'm trying to quit smoking, drinking, and the Unforgivables for the duration of my pregnancy, but one little curse here and there shouldn't hurt."

Harry looked over at Bellatrix.

"Or you could just obliviate him," she said.

Kreacher looked up in surprise. "You know how to memory charm house elves?"

"Obliviate," Harry instinctually cast on Kreacher. "I really wish people would stop saying that."

"What's up?" Sirius asked walking down the hall. He saw Bellatrix looked ashamed. "What's she doing here?"

"Kreacher led her here," Harry said.

"I thought he couldn't even get in," Sirius said, keeping his guard up.

Harry looked over at Bellatrix.

"He probably can't," Bellatrix admitted. "He snapped his fingers opening the door when I couldn't see it."

Sirius glanced at Bellatrix warily and whispered to Harry, "Does she…?"

"I think she's probably figured it out," Harry skeptically replied, wondering if his godfather was drunk.

"You're thieves!" a portrait shouted. "The pureblood bandits!"

"Death Eater bandits," Sirius shouted back.

"That's never been proven," almost two dozen portraits screamed back in unison.

"Who are you trying to convince?" Sirius argued loudly.

"Umm… guys?" Bellatrix interjected. "My Lords?"

Harry pulled Sirius away and shut the door to the portrait room, silencing all the extra voices immediately. He turned to Bellatrix expectantly. "Hmm?"

"I know I've sworn loyalty," Bellatrix said. "But if it's all the same to you, I think you should obliviate me."

Harry and Sirius looked at each other in surprise.

"You didn't want me to know this, I didn't want me to know this, and I think we're all better off if I don't know this," she explained.

Harry and Sirius just stared at Bellatrix waiting for the catch.

"Idiot Masters probably can't even cast a memory charm," Kreacher grumbled to himself.

"Shut up you wretched little turdnugget," Sirius snapped. "We've obliviated you plenty!"

Kreacher's head snapped up. "You know how to memory charm-"

"Obliviate," Harry tiredly cast on the disgruntled house elf. "God dammit Sirius. You make me do that too many times and it'll fry his brain."

Sirius glanced at the glassy-eyed elf. "And that would be bad why exactly?"

Harry opened his mouth before snapping it shut with a click. He looked at Kreacher and instructed, "Go to the top floor and clean the attic. Don't leave that floor unless we call for you."

Kreacher popped away instantly, unable to creatively interpret such a clear and specific order.

"That bugger's become a liability," Sirius said.

Harry nodded. "I know."

"Hello?" Remus yelled out from the living room. "Sirius? Harry? Bellatrix? Anyone home?"

"Go stall Moony," Harry instructed. "I'll obliviate her and be right out."

"Oh come on, I wanted to," Sirius begged.

Harry turned to Bellatrix. "Your call."

"Harry," she said immediately.

"Good call," Harry said with a grin.

"Bitch," Sirius snapped.

"You're just jealous because she likes me more than you," Harry retorted.

Sirius frowned before smiling and patting Harry on the back. "Thanks Harry. I feel better when you put it like that." Sirius turned and walked towards the living room. "I'm here, Moony!"

Bellatrix sighed. "You're never going to like me, are you?"

Harry shrugged. "To be honest at this point, it doesn't have much to do with you. We just like not liking you. Although, I do know one way you could get into me and Sirius' good graces…"

"Yeah?" Bellatrix asked hopefully. "Actually, why don't you tell me after obliviating me?"

"Good point," Harry agreed, drawing his wand, and freezing her in place.

"Hey Padfoot," Remus greeted. "Where is everybody? Bellatrix wasn't in her room."

"I don't know," Sirius said scratching his chin. "You think she rejoined the Death Eaters?"

"Sirius," Remus tiredly said, showing he was not amused.

"Oh relax," Sirius said. "Harry's with her. They just had to do something real quick. They'll be out in a second."

"What did they have to do?" Remus asked.

Sirius hesitated for a moment, trying to think of a suitably funny and insulting response.

"Padfoot," Remus sighed. "Just tell me the truth. Is it about the baby?"

"Yes," Sirius answered immediately. "It's about the baby."

"You're lying."

"Yes," Sirius replied without pause. "I'm lying."

"I'm going to check on her," Remus said getting worried.

"Wait," Sirius said stopping him.

"What?"

"Don't interrupt them," Sirius said.

"Why not?"

"Because I'm supposed to stall you."

"That's it," Remus decided. "I'm checking on her."

"How you doing, Moony?" Harry said walking into the living room.

"Harry," Remus asked. "What did you do to her?"

Harry frowned at Sirius. "What did you tell him?"

"Nothing," Sirius insisted. "I was just stalling him."

"You know telling someone you're stalling them," Harry criticized, "is poor stalling technique."

"Lying didn't work too well either," Sirius admitted with a shrug.

"Will someone just give me a straight answer," Remus whined.

"I had to obliviate her," Harry said. "That's all."

"What?" Remus asked in confusion. "Why would you obliviate her?"

"Because I asked him to," Bellatrix replied entering the room.

"There you are," Remus said in relief. "Wait, why would you ask him to?"

Bellatrix shrugged. "If I knew the answer to that, then he probably didn't do a very good job obliviating me."

Remus frowned. "And you're okay with that?"

"They're my Lords," Bellatrix admitted with a shrug. "If they were willing, I'm sure I had a good reason."

"You want to watch a movie?" Harry asked Sirius.

"Yeah," Sirius said. "Moony's probably just going to poke the little fetus in the eye. Put up a silencing charm, would you?"

"We're not gonna-" Remus defended.

Bellatrix interjected. "We're not?"

Remus quickly looked at her and shut up. He weakly added, "Never mind," as Bellatrix dragged him up to her room.

Sirius just shook his head. "That's one fucked up couple."

"You are quite the matchmaker," Harry said as they walked into the muggle room with their home theater.

Sirius flopped down into the couch. "Yeah. When my pranks backfire, they backfire big."

"You know, I said I'd give her a shot to get in our good graces," Harry said peering around the corner towards Bellatrix's door.

Sirius paused to think it over and asked, "She's getting a new face?"

Harry shook his head and cast a spell on her bedroom door. "Nope."

Immediately, the sounds coming from the bedroom were magnified and echoing throughout Grimmauld Place. Bodies shifting and moving could be heard quite clearly in the midst of some heavy breathing.

"If you want, I still have that memory," Sirius said recalling the time he'd silently observed them waiting for Remus to notice him.

"Shh," Harry shushed, listening in.

"Oh Remus," Bellatrix moaned happily. "Oh… Moony."

Sirius made a face and quietly asked, "She calls him Moony?"

Harry held up a hand, urging Sirius to stay quiet.

"Oh Bellatrix," Remus moaned her name out.

"Umm…" Bellatrix stopped. "Never mind."

"What?" Remus asked worriedly. "What is it?"

"It's nothing," Bellatrix assured him. "Keep going."

"Is it the baby?"

"No, no," Bellatrix answered immediately. "It's just…"

"What?" Remus asked, clearly awaiting an answer.

"It's… well…" Bellatrix sighed. "You're pronouncing my name wrong."

Sirius looked at Harry who held up a finger to shush him.

"I'm pronouncing it wrong?" Remus asked weakly. "But I've always pronounced it Bellatrix."

"It's alright," Bellatrix assured him. "I don't really mind that much."

Remus was perturbed. "Well then how do you pronounce it?"

Harry turned to glance at Sirius while Bellatrix's voice got all husky and sexy. "It's pronounced… Billy-trucks."

"What?"

"Billy," Bellatrix heaved out the name as she slapped Remus on the ass. "Trucks."

"Billy-trucks?" Remus repeated in disbelief. "Since when?"

"It's always been pronounced Billy-trucks," Bellatrix assured him.

"Always been…" Remus stopped and put two and two together. "Harry!" he shouted at the top of his lungs.

Harry and Sirius winced at the loud shout.

"Silencing charm?" Bellatrix reminded just as Harry turned around and canceled the spell on her door.

Remus came bursting out of her room, wrapped in only a sheet. "Harry!"

Harry was shushing Sirius who was biting his tongue, trying not to laugh.

"What's up Moony?" Harry asked innocently. "Billy-trucks not giving you any trouble, I hope."

"Harry!" Remus scolded. "She trusted you."

"Well that wasn't very smart," Sirius mumbled.

"Billy-trucks," Harry greeted looking over Remus shoulder. "You know what this is about?"

Bellatrix stood there completely naked. "No idea."

"This is about," Remus started before noticing Bellatrix was naked and Sirius was staring. "Put something on!"

"You know you're a Black, Billy-trucks," Harry said. "You don't have to take orders like that from anyone."

"Stop calling her that," Remus snapped. "Her name is Bellatrix."

"I think I know my own name," Bellatrix said with a frown, putting her hands on her hips.

"I think you need to put some clothes on."

"I think it's impressive Remus still has an erection."

"I think…" Harry paused and turned back to Sirius. "Really? The erection is what you're thinking about?"

Bellatrix raised her hand. "It's what I'm thinking about."

Sirius nodded with a smile. "Okay now I'm thinking about Billy-trucks again."

"Stop thinking about her," Remus squeaked turning around and trying to block Bellatrix from view. "Your name is Bellatrix. Harry obliviated you and is playing a cruel joke."

"Are you sure?" Bellatrix asked skeptically.

"Yes, I'm sure," Remus insisted.

Bellatrix tilted her head curiously. "You don't think maybe I'm pranking you, trying to get them to like me better?"

"No, I-" Remus stopped at the smile on her face and saw Harry and Sirius were grinning brightly. "Oh… oh, you're good."

"And naked too," Sirius cheered with a big thumbs up. "Fantastic."

Remus could tell he'd been had and found himself smiling as much as everyone else.

Bellatrix looked down to where Remus was holding the sheet up. She put a hand on his chest and softly raked her nails down. "Are you thinking what I'm thinking?"

"I am," Sirius answered confidently.

"I do believe so," Remus opened up his sheet and pulled Bellatrix's naked body up next to his so that they could both be wrapped up.

Harry watched them wiggle back towards Bellatrix's room. He picked up the remote and saw Sirius was still grinning. "Old naked horny people can be pretty cute."

"Yeah," Sirius admitted before his face contorted. "Wait no. We're supposed to hate her."

"We like Moony," Harry offered. "And we like naked."

Sirius seemed to accept that rationalization. "I guess that makes it okay."

Albus had been sitting in his office, pondering the mystery of the Lords Black. The Dark Lord Voldemort had been tentative in his actions for several months. But ever since the Dark Lord's very public defeat at their hands, he'd essentially disappeared completely. Without the need for reactions to the Dark Lord's actions, Albus had a lot more time to spend musing on the enigmatic young Heads to the Black family.

Albus had been unable to locate any information on their past at all. He was nearly certain they weren't from anywhere in the United Kingdom, but he had yet to find any indication on where they came from. Even their accents seemed genuine, though Albus knew that could be accomplished through magic. No accredited schools of magic reported any former students matching either of their descriptions.

It was almost as if they didn't exist until a couple months ago.

Their behavior and interaction with others, in particular the Lupins and Potters, was intriguing, but both of those families had recent history with the Blacks.

Albus felt there was something he was missing but he couldn't quite put it all together. His silent musings were interrupted by a whistle and burst of smoke from one of the many objects cluttering his desk.

He immediately leapt to his feet and headed out towards the Forbidden Forest to see what this particular informant had to say.

Albus masked his presence as he walked. He knew very well that this man was Alan Weston, despite Weston's attempts to hide his identity. But if a disloyal Death Eater felt more comfortable behind a supposed veil of secrecy, Albus wasn't going to shatter his delusions of privacy.

"Good evening," Albus greeted appearing in a quiet moonlit clearing.

"Listen," Alan Weston softly said as he looked both ways. "I don't have long."

Albus' eyes unfocused while turning his head from left to right. "You haven't been followed."

"Neither have you," Alan retorted, acting insulted that the Headmaster still treated him like an amateur.

Albus smiled and inclined his head. "What can I do for you?"

"I'm guessing you heard," Alan explained. "The meeting with the bloodsuckers went as expected."

Albus nodded. "I had heard, but it's nice to see you've returned in good health."

"The Dark Lord's attention hasn't been on the Ministry, your Order, or even the man in black," Alan said.

"No?"

Alan shook his head. "He's been getting all the texts and information he can on researching parallel dimensions."

Albus' eyebrows rose at not having heard this yet. He just nodded, urging Alan to continue.

"From what I've seen, he's been singularly focused on them: recent theories, ancient scrolls, how or where they exist, everything," Alan explained. "I don't know if he's recruiting help or planning to take a trip. But I thought you should know."

Albus nodded, processing the information. "I am glad you told me."

"I should go," Alan said, looking over his shoulders into the darkness. "You know how to contact me if you need to."

"Indeed I do," Albus replied, trying to think of why the Dark Lord was researching parallel dimensions with such determination. "Take care of yourself."

Alan pulled his cloak tighter and took off on a brisk walk into the darkness.

Albus turned and began to slowly walk back towards the castle. He knew the Dark Lord wouldn't be so single-minded on merely gaining a new advantage. Voldemort was too cautious for that. Albus knew if the Dark Lord was as focused as Alan claimed then it was because the Dark Lord feared something.

He couldn't understand why the Dark Lord would fear a parallel dimension.

Albus gasped loudly and stopped where he was. Suddenly everything started to make sense, including the mystery of the Lord Blacks. The Dark Lord didn't fear a parallel dimension. He feared a traveler from a parallel dimension. Especially one so powerful that he could stand up to the Dark Lord.

Albus smiled at the idea that Sirius and Harry Black really did just appear mere months ago, most likely both travelers from another dimension.

Albus had just started walking again when he paused in surprise once more. It finally dawned on the Headmaster, that the Dark Lord did not fear dimension traveler Lord Harry Black.

The Dark Lord feared a full grown Harry Potter, godson of Sirius Black, and viable subject for the prophecy of the Dark Lord's downfall.

Albus had a skip in his step and a smile on his face as he hurried back to his office, wondering how best to utilize this new information.

Chapter 21

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Harry's bad mood was plain to see as he childishly stomped into the kitchen.

Sirius looked up from the Daily Prophet and smiled at Harry. "No luck?"

Harry grunted negatively.

"Maybe I can help," Sirius offered.

"I don't need to be laughed at," Harry grumbled. "And it's not like you could keep an eye out for me."

"True," Sirius agreed. "But between the two of us, I'm the only one who's successfully mastered the animagus transformation."

Harry frowned, unable to disagree with that. "Alright then, have you got any ideas on how to make this work? Because nothing I've tried has worked."

Sirius folded up the paper, relishing the opportunity to be a proper godfather. "So what have you been trying?"

"Now that I know my form, I've been trying to self-transfigure my fingers and hands first."

Sirius frowned. "And how's that working out for you?"

Harry shrugged. "One time my fingers got really blurry, but I was already dizzy and hit my head earlier, so that might have been nothing."

"Yeah," Sirius slowly drew out the word. "I think you're going about this all wrong."

"I assume you have a suggestion," Harry added. "Or else that was awful advice."

"I do," Sirius said. "You're still thinking of the exercises and steps necessary for normal animagi. Most people have to think about things like structural and physical differences that need to be treated with caution. That's why you're supposed to magically determine how to bridge the gaps between your two different outer shells."

"Outer shells?" Harry said doubtfully.

"Yes, outer shells," Sirius repeated. "You are Harry and only Harry. Harry was born a wizard, and has had the outer shell of a wizard for all of his life. He now also has the option of another outer shell."

"Did you actually study this stuff or just take some really good drugs you found in a desert?"

"Do we need to do a show of hands again to remind people which of us can do this?" Sirius retorted with a condescending look. "As I was saying, outer shells. This is important. You have to stop thinking of yourself as a wizard first. You are Harry first, and a wizard second. Just like I am Sirius first, and a wizard second. And occasionally, I'm Sirius first, and a bad dog second. Always thinking of your own identity first is how you exert control over your different shell's instincts." Sirius rubbed his chin in thought. "Not really sure what a ghost's instincts would be. Maybe being generally depressing and having a slightly superior attitude?"

"That's not how ghosts are," Harry argued, feeling oddly defensive.

"Anyways," Sirius continued. "For most people, it's the small amount of success they get from seeing their hand turn into a paw or whatever that opens their mind to the possibility. To really grasp the idea that you are as much a dog or a ghost as you are a wizard. And there's like a mental switch that is flipped. You know not only is it possible, but it's real and it's you. Once you hit that it just takes months and months of practice to fully transform your whole body."

"You think I'm going to need months and months of practice?"

"No," Sirius assured him. "I don't. I don't think you're going need hardly any practice at all. I think once you flip that switch, you'll transform instantly. I don't think there will be any gradual change from corporeal and alive to incorporeal and 'not exactly alive.' But I do think," Sirius grinned brightly. "I do think figuring out how to flip that switch and then control it is going to be a lot harder for you."

"Great," Harry sighed. "I'd kinda guessed that much on my own. My question is how?"

"Will it," Sirius firmly replied.

"Will it?"

"Yup," Sirius said. "There's no secret incantation, no special place inside you, no spirit animal or totem to guide you. You simply will it."

"That's what I've been trying to do for the past week," Harry insisted. "It's why I keep getting headaches and crapping bloody diamonds. I spend so much damn time just concentrating as hard as I can on willing it that my crap has turned into granite."

Sirius chuckled in commiseration. "I tried sniffing James and Peter's bums just to get in the right frame of doggie mind."

"Did that help?"

"Not so much, no."

Harry closed his eyes. "Thank you for telling me a pointless story that put the image of you sniffing Wormtail and my Dad's butts permanently into my head."

"You're very welcome," Sirius replied happily. "And you know, your body reacted instinctively once already. We could try and… force the issue again."

"You want to try to kill me."

"If it'll help," Sirius said flashing a grin.

"It won't," Harry grumbled. "Unless you actually were to put my life in genuine danger, I'd know it's a fake. And I'm not ready to risk dying just to try and control my form."

"Are you sure?"

Harry nodded. "Alive is still better than dead. And alive but grievously injured, I'd like to avoid for as long as possible."

"That's just it," Sirius said. "For your ghost side, alive shouldn't be better than dead."

"I'm not willing to get a death wish," Harry argued.

"Hey," Sirius pondered aloud. "What if, when you were a baby, you got killed and turned into a ghost-"

Harry closed his eyes. "Stop."

Sirius ignored the interruption. "But you had enough magic and transformed yourself back into a living baby-"

"Stop please."

"And so now you're more like a ghost, with a wizard alternate form. And have been unknowingly living in your secondary form for decades," Sirius added with a grin. "Like Wormtail did."

"Just stop."

"It makes so much sense," Sirius nodded, thinking back to what he knew of Harry. "I mean hundreds of mothers would have sacrificed themselves out of love for their own children. Why would Lily be able to-"

"Sirius!" Harry snapped. "Stop. I'm not dead. I'm alive. Boy-Who-Lived? Dumb name. But accurate."

"Hmm."

"Besides, I didn't die. The spell rebounded off me and hit him."

"Oh yeah," Sirius realized. "It couldn't have hit you normally. So what kind of shield did Lily-"

"A blood ritual of binding," Harry explained. "It was probably done when we first went into hiding. Because when Voldemort killed her, it sealed the binding on me. If anyone else had killed her, that's who the binding would have protected me from."

"A blood ritual?" Sirius repeated. "But she was your mother. You're already as blood connected as you can be."

"That part neither I nor Hermione could figure out," Harry admitted with a shrug. "But I'm not dead."

"Hmm, I'm thinking," Sirius mused. "Do me a favor, close your eyes."

Harry looked at him dubiously.

"Just trust me," Sirius begged in irritation.

"Alright," Harry agreed, squinting his eyes shut. "What am I doing?"

A giant deafening boom sounded just behind Harry's right ear.

Harry slapped a hand over his severely stressed ear. "What the hell?"

"Damn," Sirius said with frown.

"I can't hear you," Harry shouted back at Sirius while gently putting pressuring on his ear.

Sirius rolled his eyes. "I said-"

Another massive explosion of sound erupted this time, right next to Sirius, sending the older man sprawling to the floor in the other direction.

"Not so funny now, is it?" Harry shouted at Sirius.

"I can't hear you!" Sirius exclaimed back, rubbing his ear, wondering if he should be worried at the small amount of blood trickling out his ear. "Truce?"

"What," Harry screamed back, rubbing his ear as well.

"What?" Sirius asked cleaning out his good ear.

"I can't hear you," Harry responded.

"What did you say?"

"I said I can't hear you!"

"What?"

"This is stupid."

Sirius frowned. "Don't call me kid. I was trying to help you."

Harry looked at Sirius in surprise. "Drying the elf puke?"

"Just stop trying to understand me. You have no idea what I'm saying."

"I give up," Harry said shrugging in resignation. "I'm done trying to understand you. I have no idea what you just said."

Sirius sighed, shaking his head at Harry. "I hate you."

Harry looked at Sirius curiously, wiggling his pinkie in his ear. "What kind of soup?"

"Cream of cock and balls," Sirius replied moving his lips excessively, mocking Harry's inability to hear clearly.

"Is that French? Coq aux bailles?"

Sirius looked at Harry doubtfully.

"I'm not a huge fan of creamy ones. But if you get a big chunk of meat in my mouth, I'll take a cream."

Sirius's eyes widened and jaw dropped at double meaning.

Harry slammed an invisible arm right into Sirius' throat, sending the man into a coughing fit. "You really think I wouldn't recognize the words 'cock and balls?' Have some faith in me, Sirius."

"Dammit," Sirius croaked out while rubbing his throat. A raspy tinged voice snapped, "That really hurts."

"Maybe you should've thought of that when you were deafening me," Harry retorted.

"I was trying to scare you," Sirius explained. "You know, maybe frighten you half to death?"

"You're an idiot."

"Yeah but if it had worked, I would've been a genius."

"I don't think I want to know the kind of world where you count as a genius."

"Laugh it up."

"That wouldn't be a world where up is down. That'd be a world where up is… jello."

"Look buddy. Last time you were thinking about becoming an animagi, you were fearful for your life, and possibly your life really was in danger. Scaring the bloody form out of you…" Sirius trailed off in thought. He snapped back to reality, "Jello on the ceilings is a damn good idea. I'm going to talk to Moony about making a charm or a wheeze."

Harry looked at his godfather in consternation. "Wow, Sirius, thanks for all the help. I'm really glad we had this talk."

Sirius either completely missed or ignored the sarcasm. "You're very welcome." Having accomplished his mission, he turned and walked right out of the room.

Harry leaned back in his chair and pulled out an animagi text that he'd read several times before. He glanced at the door briefly considering the idea of scaring the form out of him. He was on high alert expecting Sirius to attempt to frighten him again.

Harry re-read the passage and set the text down. He took a deep breath and made the decision to try again. He stood up in the middle of the room, and went through his exercises. He was blocking out as much outside noise as possible, focusing on how different it had felt to be a ghost. The stillness of everything, the enveloping silence, the foreign sensation of solid matter.

His brow was covered in sweat as he continued concentrating solely on the animagus transformation. He was so single-minded he didn't even hear her the first time.

"What're you doing?" Ginny repeated louder, sticking her head over Harry's right shoulder.

Harry's heart just about stopped at the sound of her voice. He spun around defensively and instinctively started to bullshit. "Listen, I can explain-" Harry's explanation came to a sudden halt when his arm swung around and connected solidly with a slap across Ginny's cheek.

Harry whimpered in surprise but looked down and saw he was still solid. He hadn't transformed, as he had feared. He then considered the fact that he just slapped a ghost and wondered the odds Ginny might not have noticed. "On second thought, now might not be the best time for explanations."

Ginny rubbed her cheek in glorious amazement. She crept forward faster than Harry could backpedal and stuck her hand straight through his heart. When her fingers met no resistance, Ginny frowned and pouted, "Aww… I thought we were finally permitted to touch each other."

"Oh thank Merlin." Harry whispered a quiet prayer. He looked down at his hands and reached out, horrified to discover he'd just poked Ginny in the tit.

Ginny gasped at the sensation. She looked at Harry's hand in awe.

"That's not right," Harry announced looking at his hand angrily. "You're a ghost. I shouldn't be able to-" Harry stopped in surprise as his hands met no resistance at all. He walked through Ginny's incorporeal body. He poked a finger through her shoulder and felt nothing. Immediately after pulling his finger back he poked again this time touching solid shoulder, eliciting a gasp from the young ghost.

"You know what this means?" Ginny sang merrily as she spun in a circle.

"I could guess."

"It means I still can't hold you, but you can hold me."

"I guessed wrong."

Ginny hopped up in front of him with her arms wide open. "Hold me, Harry."

Harry tucked his hands under his armpits. "No thanks."

"Harry," Ginny whined.

"Maybe some other time," Harry evasively offered.

"When," Ginny demanded.

"Never?"

Ginny didn't care for that suggestion and sought middle ground. "Umm… maybe some other time?"

Harry smiled. "That's just what I was thinking."

Ginny moved over to perch on the side of the chair nearest to Harry. "I'm here, you know. Just in case, you want to touch me. I'm cool with it."

"I'll keep that in mind," Harry said.

"So," Ginny conversationally began. "I don't suppose that bull-dyke man-hating bartender version of me got kissed by a dementor anytime recently?"

Harry looked at Ginny a little worriedly.

"Because I mean, if there's just a perfectly good spare Ginny Weasley body around, I've got dibs."

"No," Harry answered her earnestly. "No dementor kisses. I just saw her a couple nights back."

"Chin up, Harry," Ginny said trying to hold Harry's hand. She smiled softly. "There's still time."

Harry wondered if he was going to develop ghost-like characteristics such as dementia or wishing death on others. "Hey Ginny, what's it like being a ghost?"

"Harry, I'm soul-bonded to you," Ginny assured him. "I'm only a ghost for now. I'm waiting for you to get this madness out of your system before we spend the rest of eternity together."

"So a lot of lying to yourself and constantly avoiding the glaringly obvious issue," Harry replied. "Not bad. Not bad at all."

"There's a healthy amount of spying on naked people too," Ginny corrected.

"That's always fun," Harry agreed, liking the prospects of ghost-hood more and more.

"Why do you ask?" Ginny inquired. "And were you doing animagus exercises when I walked in?"

The color drained from Harry's face as he tried and failed to mask his emotions. "No," he squeaked.

"No?"

"What is this? The Spanish Inquisition?" Harry snapped as he got up and stomped away.

Ginny gasped joyously. "You know your form, don't you?" She saw the look on Harry's face. "You do! That's great. So what is it?"

"It's umm…" Harry stalled. "Umm…"

"What?" Ginny scoffed. "Oh come on. It's not like your form is a ghost."

Harry stumbled back and his body let out a poof of displaced air at her dishearteningly accurate guess. He looked down at his arms and hands and saw straight through the translucent light of his ghostly form all the way to the floor. He looked back up at Ginny and saw the female ghost had been shocked into a stupor.

Without another word, the ghostly form of Harry turned tail and ran out of the room and down the hall.

"Harry!" Ginny called out chasing after him, floating straight through the walls. She quickly caught back up to him. "Harry, wait!"

Harry could feel Ginny gaining on him and took a quick right, heading down the stairs.

Ginny just floated straight down, while Harry ran the long way down the curving staircase. He hit the bottom stair running and dove headfirst in a somersault, successfully avoiding Ginny. He glanced over his shoulder at her and ran headfirst into the book shelf.

Harry passed incorporeally through and continued running down the left side of the hall.

Ginny was floating behind him, at a less frantic pace.

Not finding what he was looking for, Harry crossed the hall and began running through the rooms on the other side.

Harry skidded to a stop when he found Sirius and Remus, working together. So far they had the ceiling half-coated with a gooey layer of lime green jello.

"Hey," Harry began pointing at the ceiling curiously.

"Hey," Sirius happily shouted back noticing Harry had transformed again.

"You two gotta do the reversal spell," Harry ordered quickly remembering why he'd been looking for them.

"Hello Harry," Remus mockingly greeted. "I'm fine. Thanks for asking. It's good to see you too."

"Listen, I don't have a lot of ti-" Harry cut off, yelping out a feminine shriek at the sight of Ginny floating through the wall. Harry ran straight through Remus and across the hall again.

Harry was sprinting through the rooms, staying one step ahead of Ginny the whole way. The next pass through the temporary jello room, Harry had enough time to yell, "The Spell!" He doubled-back seconds later. "Do it!"

"Alright, alright," Remus said aiming his wand at Harry. He paused and turned to Sirius, "What was the incantation, again?"

Harry turned and ran straight through Remus again, grumbling, "Oh you're hilarious."

Remus shuddered as Harry passed through him and into the next room. "No magical arms as a ghost?"

Sirius twitched having felt a chill rake through his brain. "They're ghostly too."

"He went that-a-way," Remus told Ginny's ghost while pointing over his shoulder.

"Do you know what…?" Ginny questioned.

"Ghost animagus," Sirius answered.

Ginny nodded as if she knew it all along. "I always wondered why I was taken from Harry at such a young age."

"You don't think the Killing Curse answered most of that question," Sirius inquired.

Ginny harrumphed. "It makes sense that it was necessary for me to learn and understand how we'd spend eternity together so that I would be able to help him master his form." Ginny smiled, clasping her hands together. "My Harry needs me."

"Did she-" Harry cut off with a yelp and disappeared right back in the wall he'd stuck his head through.

"Don't fight fate, Harry!" Ginny called out hurrying after him, floating out of the room. "She's kind of a bitch."

Sirius glanced over to see how Remus was doing.

"Ginny's going to molest him, isn't she?" Remus fearfully asked.

Sirius nodded. "Probably. But if anything can inspire Harry into figuring out how to transform back, it'll be Ginny and her bad touches."

"We'll get him next time he passes through here," Remus said. "But no slacking during your conjuring turn. Get back to jello blasting."

Harry was beginning to think he'd lost her finally. He glanced over his shoulder as he crept through the library wall.

"Hello love," Ginny greeted with wide open arms from just inside the library wall.

Harry whipped his hand around and tried to stop himself from crashing into Ginny. He tripped forward with a shriek, flailing his arms wildly.

Ginny reached out to grab onto Harry and grasped only air.

"Ahh!" Harry screamed, flapped his hands, and assumed a defensive position.

"Aww," Ginny pouted heartbroken.

Harry's frantic hand motions slowed down and he cracked open an eye. "Ahh?"

"Why can't we touch?" Ginny frowned. "I can touch other ghosts."

"Hey," Harry realized pushing his incorporeal arms through Ginny's incorporeal arms. "I can't touch you. Not even when I'm trying."

Ginny looked up to the heavens. "It's because I called you a bitch, isn't it?"

"Why can't I touch you?" Harry wondered.

"Maybe part of my helping you master your form will include figuring this out," Ginny mused.

"Huh?"

She turned to Harry. "It's not like you can instantly know exactly what it means to be a ghost."

Harry frowned. "There's more to it?"

"Of course, Harry," Ginny huffed exasperatedly. "That's why I had to die. So that I'd know all about being a ghost and could teach my soul mate."

"You think he'd mind if you help me too?" Harry asked.

Ginny shook her head. "You're such a kidder."

Harry started to feel a little guilty. "You're really going to help me even though I'm kind of a dick to you?"

"Of course," Ginny assured him. "This is undoubtedly another way for us to be together for eternity."

"Oh… joy," Harry forced out the words.

Ginny grinned brightly, forgetting her earlier disappointment. "We should start by getting you familiar with how it feels being a ghost."

Harry held up a hand to stop her. "Hang on. Let me go tell Sirius and Remus not to disturb us. We'll use the room I was practicing in."

Ginny floated along next to Harry while he walked through the walls until he reached the jello dripping room.

"Hey guys," Harry said attracting their attention. "I was-"

Sirius and Remus both called out the spell forcing Harry from his animagus transformed state. They were exhausting themselves but quickly they funneled enough magic to complete the change.

Harry popped back into his corporeal breathing form and stood there staring at them in shock.

Remus saw Ginny right behind Harry and knew they'd just been in time. It took a lot out of him, but it was worth it for the look on Harry's face. "You are welcome."

Harry's abject horror began to wear off and he found his voice. "You motherfuckers."

Ginny gasped happily. "Well, well, well. Look who can touch me again."

Sirius and Remus glanced at each other and didn't see all of the appreciation they expected from Harry.

"You complete, utter bastards."

"Perhaps now," Ginny whispered in Harry's ear, "we can talk about my payment for training you in the ways of the ghost."

Harry growled at Remus and Sirius. "You motherfuckers."

Sirius was catching on. "You changed your mind on that reversal spell thing, didn't you?"

"Figured that one out, did you?" Harry dangerously announced. "And before you ask, no, I have no clue when I'll be able to manage the transformation again."

Remus meekly defended. "You're the one who was begging for the spell."

"Can't you try and recreate whatever changed you this time?" Sirius asked.

Harry glanced at Ginny and shook his head. "I highly doubt it. The reason I feared transforming was what Roaming Hands Weasley here was going to do to me if I did. Now I know she can't touch me when I do. Not quite so scary."

Ginny was biting her cheek, deep in thought. "Have you tried triggering it with intercourse with a ghost?"

Sirius shrugged. "It's not a bad id-"

"It's a very bad idea!" Harry snapped out.

Remus snickered to himself.

"What?" Harry barked at him.

"Sorry," Remus apologized. "The whole ghost intercourse thing just reminded me of something."

Harry, Sirius, and Ginny were all staring at Remus unsure if they wanted to know what was on his mind.

Sirius couldn't contain his curiosity and asked, "What?"

Remus was still amused. "In your world, did you ever go as Sir Nicholas for Halloween?"

"Yeah," Sirius recalled. "I just covered the front of my pants in blood."

"Nearly headless?" Remus mocked in a high-pitched voice. "How can you be nearly headless?"

"Oh good god," Harry whispered in fright.

Sirius felt inordinately proud. "I made five Hufflepuffs cry."

"And two more had to get explanations from their prefects," Remus added.

Harry turned away from Sirius and Remus to leave the room. "It's going to be one of those days, I can tell."

Ginny floated dutifully along with him. "You know what might make you feel better, Harry?"

"What?"

"Getting to third base."

"No."

"Second base?"

"Stop."

"Did you write this?" Bellatrix exclaimed, rushing up to Remus with tears in her eyes.

"Write what?" Remus asked curiously, noticing she was clutching a letter close to her heart.

"What am I saying? Of course, you wrote this," Bellatrix continued, her mood changing from 'so happy she could cry' to 'self-deprecating' in the blink of an eye. "It's in your handwriting."

"It is?" Remus asked curiously.

Bellatrix's smile twisted into a frown. "Unless you've been writing love letters to some other woman named Bellatrix…"

"No!" Remus insisted, picking up on the warning signs that Bellatrix's mood was more volatile than usual.

"Some other man named Bellatrix?" Sirius asked, sticking his head in.

"No," Remus sputtered. "I haven't been writing anyone any love letters."

Bellatrix whimpered and was fighting back tears.

"Except that one," Remus said pointing towards the letter Bellatrix was guarding like precious treasure.

Bellatrix's sniffles twisted into a smile of pure bliss. "Oh Remus!" She lunged forward wrapping her arms around him. "This is the sweetest thing anyone's ever done for me."

Remus rubbed gentle circles into her back trying to calm her down. "Well… I'm… I'm glad you liked it."

Sirius and Harry were looking at each other worriedly.

"The sweetest thing?" Harry mouthed at Sirius.

"I know!" Sirius mouthed back.

"That's just sad," Harry softly concluded.

"I'm…" Bellatrix was still crying happily. "I'm not the kind of girl who gets too many love letters and… I just…" She gripped the letter tighter. "I'll treasure this forever."

"That's," Remus paused looking at Sirius and Harry helplessly. "That's why I wrote it?"

Bellatrix finally pulled back to look at Remus. "I think I'm going to lay down for a nap. Come tuck me in?"

"I will," Remus assured her. "I just need to talk to these two for a minute."

Bellatrix nodded in understanding. "Don't be long."

Remus stuck a hand out cautiously. "Do you mind if I re-read my letter?"

Bellatrix glanced between the letter in her hand and Remus. "I want it back."

"I'll bring it up with me when I tuck you in," Remus promised her.

Bellatrix handed the letter to him confidently. "You're so sweet."

Remus made a non-committal sound while keeping a smile on his face.

The three men watched Bellatrix leave the room. Remus spun around angrily. "Alright. What did you do?"

"What makes you think we did anything?" Sirius asked.

"Yeah," Harry agreed. "I'm not sure she even got the right letter."

Remus reluctantly unfolded the letter and saw a few verses of poetry had been scribbled in what appeared to be his handwriting.

"I never heard the final draft," Sirius pointed out. "So, speak up."

Remus pretended not to hear Sirius, but obliged with the request. He worriedly read from the parchment. "Bellatrix, oh Bellatrix, how I tire of your gay tricks."

"Snappy," Sirius critiqued.

"I doubt we could get rid o' ya," Remus continued in confusion, "with just a case of Chlamydia."

"Catchy," Sirius said a little too proud of his pun. "Oww," he swore grabbing his eye. "Why you gotta go there, Harry?"

Remus ignored them both and kept reading. "But I was thinkin' maybe ya, might trim down your labia."

Sirius snickered holding on to Harry for support.

"This is disgusting," Remus complained.

"Keep reading, keep reading," Sirius urged.

"Mud flaps belong on silly trucks," Remus read aloud shamefully. "Not on my sick and twisted little Billy-trucks."

Harry and Sirius were both laughing to see the way it pained Remus to say that name aloud.

"That's it. I'm done," Remus said, not wanting to read any further.

"No!" Sirius begged. "Come on! There's at least two more verses."

Remus sighed but gave in to temptation. He looked down at the start of the next verse. "It would take almost two Great Walls of China," He flipped over the first page and continued, "to actually plug your gaping va- Who wrote this?"

"My lips are sealed." Harry refused to answer.

Sirius wasn't quite so trustworthy. "I think that line was the work of your daughter."

"Tonks?" Remus asked in disbelief.

"No," Harry sarcastically replied. "The barely formed fetus in the ex-Death Eater's womb is a fan of limericks and contributed most of the second verse."

Remus just looked at Harry and Sirius, thinking he needed to have a long talk with Tonks.

"Remus!" Bellatrix yelled out in despair from the floor above. "Come fuck me!"

Harry and Sirius exchanged a surprised look while Remus failed to hide his blush.

"I mean tuck me in," Bellatrix loudly corrected, belatedly processing what she'd said.

Remus smiled weakly. "I should go."

"I didn't really mean tuck me in," Bellatrix earnestly admitted at the top of her lungs.

"Yeah, you should," Harry agreed. "But Moony? When you're, ahem, tucking her in, do me a favor and think of Sirius' arse."

Remus winced.

"Here ya go, big guy," Sirius happily followed Harry's lead, turning around and flashing a pale cheek at the other Marauder.

"Oh god," Remus said guarding his eyes in disgust. He scraped his tongue on the roof of his mouth trying to get the taste out. He flashed a winning smile. "Thanks."

Sirius watched Remus walk happily away and skip up the steps towards Bellatrix's room. He turned towards his godson. "Why did he thank me? Harry, why did he thank me?"

Harry opened his mouth and closed it helplessly. "Don't know. Don't care. It's just one of those days."

Sirius looked at Harry warily. "And just what happens on one of those days?"

"Usually?"

"Yeah."

"Too much."

"Too much happens?"

"Yeah."

"Yeah," Sirius repeated with a slow nod. "We still doing that thing this afternoon?"

Harry considered the question and shrugged indifferently. "Yeah."

Sirius could hear the tiredness in Harry's tone. "Are you getting all pensive and introspective on me?"

Harry realized he had been deep in thought. "Maybe."

"Did a vagina come with that attitude because you're acting like a girl."

"I've just been thinking about how things are different here because I wasn't in this world," Harry explained. "People who are happier, or for that matter alive, because they never knew me."

Sirius wasn't in the mood for a pity party. "Like say, Voldemort, for instance?"

"True enough," Harry admitted, catching the hint. "Let me just relax for a bit and then we'll go do the thing."

"You want to watch something on the muggical box?" Sirius suggested.

Harry lead the way up to their muggle entertainment room, grumbling. "You know saying it more often isn't going to make it a word. You just sound stupid, again."

"Words are for conformists, you vaptastic fantomiter," Sirius pouted.

Harry paused and glanced at Sirius. "Did you just now make that up?"

"You connest your baltfooling dushbunnets," Sirius replied with a knowing smile.

Harry turned away from Sirius and walked the rest of the way into the room. "Don't talk that way anymore. It makes me want to hurt you."

Sirius remembered how much his ability to make up real sounding nonsense words instinctively both scared and disturbed James as well. "Where's the TV remote?"

Harry pointed to the coffee table. "It's right in front of you."

"No," Sirius corrected. "That's the remote for the DVD."

"So watch a DVD."

"I still need the TV remote."

"Is it the skinny white one?"

"No, that's the receiver."

"What's the one in your hand?"

"This is for the cable box."

"Good lord," Harry grumbled turning towards the couch he was on. He sent out several invisible, magical arms and quickly searched through the cushions. He found some change, a pen, what looked like a finger, and a comb. He strengthened the arms and checked the cushions on the other couch. "Ah-ha!"

A remote came floating out from nestled down in the left side. "I am the king," Harry pronounced pushing the remote to Sirius.

Sirius sighed. "That's the laser disc remote."

"We have a laser disc?" Harry asked. "And what is a laser disc?"

"I have no idea. And I don't think we do, but our neighbors do," Sirius explained. "Last week I slipped on an invisibility cloak and borrowed that remote from the neighbors because I needed the batteries… for the TV remote."

"This is ridiculous," Harry snapped. He drew his wand and confidently cast, "Accio remote!"

The nearest remote jumped up towards Harry before popping loudly in a small burst of flames and sparks. All the other remotes followed shortly after zooming to Harry and then exploding, catching fire, or vibrating with smoke billowing out the top.

"Oops," Harry apologized forgetting that while his magical arms worked normally in the warded muggle room, magic did not.

Sirius looked down at the remains of the remotes from the cable box, the DVD, the neighbor's laser disc player, and the receiver. "Still no TV remote!"

They both looked up as Remus' pants came flying into the room stopping in front of Harry. The pants began to smoke, before they started shaking and erupted in flames.

Harry smiled weakly at Sirius. "Looks like Moony stole the TV remote and stuck it to his pocket for nefarious purposes."

Sirius glanced at all their melted and broken pieces of remotes and the smoldering remains of Remus' pants. He looked up at Harry, clearly not amused. "Guess you really showed him, huh?"

"I said 'oops,'" Harry defended. "Besides, we had too many remotes."

"I think we have too few now," Sirius commented.

"They sell these spiffy new super-smart remotes that can replace other remotes," Harry explained. "I remember seeing a mention of them on sale somewhere." Harry got up and walked over to the door. "I should have a muggle paper from last week still in my room."

"Hang on." Sirius stopped Harry from leaving. "I got today's right here."

"You've got today's?"

Sirius nodded. "Chicks dig a roguishly handsome man, especially one with the Financial Times tucked under his arm."

"That's…" Harry smiled as he took the newspaper from Sirius, "not a half bad idea."

Harry felt wetness on his hand and looked down to find the Financial Times was a slobbery mess.

Sirius grinned. "And on occasion, I'll get some hotties to play fetch with Padfoot, allowing me ample opportunity to sniff their crotches."

"Nice," Harry said with a forced smile. He wiped his hand off and slowly unfurled the newspaper. The large front page headline caught his eye.

Harry blinked and had to re-read it several times. "This can't be happening."

"What?" Sirius asked. "What is it?"

Harry turned the paper around displaying the front page. He read the headline aloud, "Piers Polkiss Cures Cancer."

Sirius frowned at Harry. "Isn't that a good thing?"

"I… guess," Harry answered helplessly.

Sirius scratched his head in confusion. "Do you know him?"

"Yeah," Harry unfortunately admitted.

"Ahh," Sirius said finally catching on. "This is because it's one of those days. And you were just talking about the differences in… oh dear. Was he one of the people you tried to save but couldn't?"

"No," Harry replied. "He's just a dick."

Sirius was not expecting that answer.

"And he's stupid."

"Stupid?" Sirius questioned. "It sounds like he's smart enough to cure cancer."

"There's no way," Harry argued. "Not the Piers Polkiss I knew."

"What's the article say?" Sirius suggested. "Maybe it's a different guy."

"I'm sure," Harry sarcastically retorted. "Because Piers Polkiss is such a common name."

"Could be."

Harry knew better than to grasp at that hope. He read the start of the front page. "Reverend Dr. Polkiss… what?"

"Huh?"

"Reverend Dr. Polkiss, last years' recipient of the Nobel Peace Prize-" Harry stopped and handed the paper to Sirius. "I can't do it. I don't want to read this."

Sirius took the paper and quickly scanned through the article. "Wow… this guy's a regular hero."

"He's no hero," Harry whined. "He's an evil, cruel person. He was the original mastermind behind the games of Harry-hunting and Tie-Harry-to-the-back-of-the-bus."

Sirius smirked. "Exactly how does one play Tie-Harry-to-the-back-of-the-bus?"

"It's kinda like Punch-Sirius-in-the-crotch if you were seven and a bleeder," Harry snapped.

Sirius winced and decided to avoid that road. "I guess without your aggravating presence in his life, he had a lot more free time."

Harry tried to ignore Sirius but couldn't contain his curiosity. He gave in and asked, "What did he win a Nobel Peace Prize for?"

"It says it in here somewhere." Sirius scanned backwards through the article looking for the passage. "Here it is! Blah, blah, blah… negotiated a truce between Israel and Palestine."

"No Harry," Harry grumbled. "And instead you get cancer cured and peace in the Middle East. That's real funny."

"I'd call it moderately funny," Sirius said wiggling his hand. "But you're not crying, so…"

Harry sighed. "I hate these days. And you just know it's going to get worse."

A burst of fire and wail of phoenix song announced Fawkes' arrival.

"When you say things like that," Sirius chided. "You deserve what you get."

"Meh," Harry grumbled know that on those days it didn't matter what he said. He looked up at Fawkes. "Who gets the bad news? Me or him?"

Fawkes hovered in place glancing between Sirius and Harry before he flew off and landed on Sirius' shoulder.

Sirius accepted the parchment from Fawkes' grasp and opened it up. "It doesn't look too long."

Harry closed his eyes. "Does he know?"

Sirius skimmed the first paragraph. "No."

"No?" Harry repeated in surprise.

"Yes."

"Yes?" Harry repeated in confusion.

"I don't know," Sirius summarized with a shake of his head. He slowly began to nod. "Yeah… he knows."

"Origins not extracurricular activities, right?"

"Right," Sirius agreed. "He's basically forcing us to confirm his belief."

Harry looked up curiously. "How's he managing that?"

Sirius straightened out the letter and leaned forward with a Dumbledore-like hunch. He rasped out the words like an old man. "I have puzzled over the familiarity I felt upon meeting the two of you. That was until last night when I came to an extremely unlikely and yet wholly possible conclusion."

"Ahh crap," Harry grumbled.

Sirius held up a hand to stop Harry and continued. "If this improbable theory of mine contains even a grain of truth, then putting it into a letter is a risk I shall not take. And so I ask you kindly to please humor this old man and come discuss my theory with me at your earliest convenience."

"Our earliest convenience?" Harry repeated. "I'm thinking it won't be convenient for a very long time."

"Oh really?" Sirius smugly asked. He continued to read the letter. "It would be remiss of me not to mention that so far I have not discussed my theory with anyone."

Harry sighed. "You can almost hear the noose tightening."

"If neither of you have any interest in discussing my theory, then I will seek other sounding boards. And I would hate to give my good friends the Potters an unlikely and uncertain hope when that hope and my theory could be easily confirmed or denied by either of you."

Harry laughed helplessly. "That cheeky fucking bastard."

"I know," Sirius agreed. "It's so… Dumbledore."

"He knows," Harry grumbled. "And he's trying to make it sound like he just guessed."

"You think someone told him?" Sirius asked. "We've seen Tonks and Moony both today and I doubt Gin risked her oath. Unspeakables maybe?"

Harry considered and admitted. "Maybe but we can't discount the possibility that he did guess it."

"How do you want to handle this?"

Harry informed, "I'll go talk to him tonight."

"Tonight?" Sirius asked. "Just you?"

"If you don't mind," Harry said. "I think I'd rather go by myself."

"You're not going to kill him, are you?"

Harry looked at Sirius silently.

"Because I'll get Tonks and we got your alibi covered."

"I'm not going to kill him," Harry exasperatedly replied. "But if we both go see him, we'll look like wayward students sent to the Headmaster's office. If I go alone, he'll see me as an equal."

"And he wouldn't see me as an equal?"

Harry shook his head. "There's a difference between defeating a dark wizard and defeating a Dark Lord. It's not really something…" Harry struggled to find the words.

"This is some of that crap you never want to talk about?"

Harry hadn't been sure Sirius had even noticed. "Yeah."

"And you're certain you haven't grown a vagina?"

"Yes, Sirius. I checked this morning."

"Okay," Sirius exclaimed looking around. "This place is creepier during the day than even the Shrieking Shack at night."

"The Shrieking Shack isn't scary," Harry argued. "You're part of the reason people think it's haunted."

"I'm not the one who starved eight children in the attic," Sirius argued. "They're the ones who scream on rainy nights."

"What?"

"Do you know nothing about the Shrieking Shack?"

"That's where Moony went to transform when he was a student," Harry replied. "His howls and screams during transformation are why people think it's haunted."

"People don't just think it's haunted," Sirius retorted. "It is haunted. By an entire Ravenclaw first year class. You know it was called the Shrieking Shack before I ever started at Hogwarts, right?"

Harry looked at his godfather curiously. "Really?"

"Yeah, really. Ask Albus tonight. He'll tell you." Sirius continued, "We tried to keep Moony company in there, but it was just too freaky with those screaming and whispering kids. That was why we started going out into the Forbidden Forest instead. It wasn't like we originally decided, 'Hey. Let's take the feral werewolf closer to the townspeople. Yeah, that's a good idea.' No," Sirius shook his head. "We just got freaked out by that place."

"Really?"

Sirius nodded. "But this place even has an even creepier name." He was looking around the dilapidated and unkempt grounds. "The Gaunt House. It sounds like the opposite of a children's playground."

Harry glanced at his godfather. "And what name would sound like a children's playground?"

" Happytastic Funtabalous Land," Sirius suggested. "What are we looking for anyway?"

"There's a family ring around here," Harry added.

"The Gaunt family ring?" Sirius asked. "I'm guessing it likes to bite fingers off."

"The Gaunts were just this lowest branch of the Slytherin line," Harry explained, ducking under a broken dust-covered support beam.

"Slytherin? You mean…?"

Harry nodded. "Merope Gaunt used love potions to get a booty call out of a muggle named Tom Riddle. Named the little hellspawn after her rape victim, I mean his father."

"Voldemort's a… junior?" Sirius smiled. "I bet calling him junior would tick him off."

Harry approached the loose floorboard in the back closet. "This is… ah crap."

"What?"

Harry jerked up and looked around. "I think I just broke a collapsing ward."

"What's a-"

"Collapsing wards do nothing but evaporate when any magical person or magic touches them. Even diagnostic spells to locate wards trigger them."

"Do they just feel like a slight breeze you barely notice that tingles everywhere?" Sirius inquired curiously.

"Yeah."

"Oh," Sirius answered. "Then I may have felt one when we approached the property."

"Crap," Harry said, running up to the broken dirty window.

"What is it?"

Harry stared off into the woods behind the house. "Someone or ones may be watching us."

Sirius looked into the darkness of the trees and saw nothing. "Want me to walk out there while you circle around the back?"

"No," Harry said shaking his head. "The ring's not here and I don't think that's Albus out there. Let's just get out of here." Harry grabbed Sirius' wrist and apparated them both away.

The man had been expecting the collapsing wards to fall soon but he was momentarily shocked to feel it happen during the late afternoon in broad daylight. He quickly ensured his cloak would mask his presence and silently appeared under the cover of darkness in the woods behind the Gaunt House.

He spotted the two Lord Blacks walking into the ruins of the old home in mild shock. Suddenly one of the mysteries he'd been puzzling over began to make sense. He was thinking furiously over all that he knew of them when he felt another collapsing ward fall.

The man thought the Blacks located that way too quickly and before he knew it, Harry was right at the window staring at him. The man didn't dare move as he saw Sirius walk up behind Harry, discussing something.

He finally exhaled when he both saw and heard the two Lords apparate away, right from inside the ruins of the Gaunt house.

The man heavily cloaked in black triggered a portkey on his wrist reappearing in a well furnished and protected home. He moved over towards his fireplace and tapped his wand three times on a highly magical stone.

He prepared himself a snifter of brandy and sat back in the chair where he did much of his deep thinking.

Two minutes later the fireplace flared and the man accepted the incoming call. Alan Weston's head appeared in the fireplace.

"You're thinking," Alan stated noticing the man known to many as 'That Fucker' was resting comfortably in a chair.

The man nodded. "I know who the Death Eater Bandits are and I know how the animagus got past my ward."

Alan blinked, admittedly impressed. "Who? How?"

The man looked over at Alan and replied, "It's because you're keyed into your wards."

"Me?"

The man in black nodded and took another sip of brandy.

"I don't follow."

The man took a deep relaxing breath and explained, "Any question of whether the Lord Blacks are really the Lords of the Black line has been answered."

"Wait," Alan paused. "You mean…"

The man nodded.

"So since I'm one of their vassals, if I'm allowed, then by extension they are allowed?"

"Something like that," he agreed with a grin.

"How many people's bitch am I?" Alan asked before jerking up in surprise. "I just realized another god damn Sirius Black isn't letting me have warm sheets. That's just fucking perfect."

The man in the chair sighed. "You're never going to let this go, are you?"

"It was a really nice dryer!"

Chapter 22

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: I'd like to claim that the delay on this chapter was abnormal and I'm about to jump right into a more regular writing and posting schedule, but I can't. Sorry. Feel free to do what I do and just blame my mom. (Not to mention she's ruined the punchline for one of my old favorite jokes. Q: What do you give the woman who has everything? A: Cancer. I know it's doubly tasteless now that it's true, but that's still funny.)

Nevertheless, I doubt the next chapter or two will take anywhere near as long as this one. Feel free to PM me and nudge me to hurry up on the next chapter, as those things more often inspire me to hurry than discourage me. Just realize that writing and posting this fic is a lower priority than usual for the near future. Big thanks to the usual folks who help me with this story: IP, Chuck, Jim, Sean, Rob, and others I'm forgetting. All comments, reviews, and feedback are appreciated.

Harry appeared with a pop just off the path leading to Hogwarts.

He began the slow trudge up to the castle, all the while reminding himself the man he was meeting was not the Headmaster he knew, nor was he an enemy.

Harry saw light coming from Hagrid's cabin and thought back to his many happy memories of time spent in a world similar to this one. The Whomping Willow was swaying in the night breeze.

Harry looked around him and saw no one in sight. He picked up a rock off the path and threw it straight towards the dangerous tree. The willow eagerly swatted the rock right back to Harry.

Recognizing the tree seemed in a playful mood, Harry picked up half a dozen more rocks with his invisible, magical appendages and proceeded to throw them all towards the tree. He easily kept up with the magical old willow catching all the rocks and throwing them right back as if the two of them were playing several simultaneous games of catch.

"Lord Black?" Albus cautiously asked as he walked up behind Harry.

Harry's arms caught all of the rocks headed his way and held onto them this time as he turned and greeted, "Headmaster."

The Whomping Willow let out a whistling sigh and appeared to deflate upon the realization that its fun had come to an end.

Albus smiled at Harry. "I can honestly say I've never seen the Whomping Willow used quite like that."

Harry launched a rock one last time towards the tree, admitting, "First time for me too."

The tree was fully capable of nursing a grudge and swung a thick branch right at the final rock, sending it flying up to the castle. There was a loud crack when the stone smacked against the window of the Headmaster's office and bounced helplessly off the magically reinforced glass.

Albus looked at the tree and his office's tower. "I think she's upset I interrupted you."

"She?" Harry asked. "The Whomping Willow is female?"

"Does she seem like a 'he' to you?"

Harry shook his head. "No, I suppose not."

"I did not expect to see you so soon," Albus admitted, inspecting Harry. "Am I only to be graced by one Lord Black this evening?"

"Just me," Harry answered and turned towards the castle. "Have you got time for a conversation?"

"For one as enlightening as this one promises to be," Albus waved Harry forward and began walking in step with him. "I will happily clear my schedule."

"You're enjoying this entirely too much," Harry admitted with a smile as he walked next to Albus.

"Shall I invite certain guests to join us?" Albus inquired. "Perhaps some others for whom-"

"No," Harry interrupted. "In fact, I was thinking we might both benefit from a charm of brotherhood."

Albus showed only slight surprise at the suggestion. The most common charm of brotherhood entwined two people to the point that they would know when their 'brother' was lying to them, telling them the truth, or hiding something. It additionally would protect one brother's secrets based on the will of that brother. So if Albus' desire to tell someone a secret of Harry's was not stronger than Harry's desire for Albus not to tell, then Albus would be unable to. "Do you really think that's necessary?"

"Necessary? No," Harry replied. "But I'm here offering to be as honest with you as you are with me. I'm also going to ask that you not tell any of your alternate sounding boards," Harry gave Albus an accusing look, "any of your theories about me or Sirius."

Albus had the decency to look bashful before replying, "Do you really think that's fair?"

"Extremely fair," Harry eagerly answered.

"Harry," Albus chided.

"Albus," Harry retorted as they arrived at the Headmaster's office. "It's fair because I'm limiting your freedom to discuss it with others, and in turn willingly discussing it with you myself. It's a charm of brotherhood. It's built for fairness."

Albus circled around to sit behind his desk. "I meant fair to others. People like the Potters for what they don't know, or the Lupins for what they do."

Harry plopped down into a comfortable chair. He knew Albus wanted him as an ally and couldn't resist the thirst for knowledge. "This charm, and this conversation, is for you and me. Not them."

Albus sat there silently for a minute before nodding. "I can accept that. Tea?" He swished his wand and conjured a complete steaming set.

"Tea second," Harry said casting a spell over his right hand making it glow. He stuck it out towards Albus. "Charm first."

Albus set down the teapot and cast the same charm of brotherhood over his hand. "Very well." He shook Harry's hand sealing the spell as both their hands faded to normal. "How do you take it?"

"One sugar please," Harry replied and accepted the cup of tea.

Albus took a sip from his cup and sat back. He set the cup down and smiled happily.

Harry saw how pleased Albus looked and resisted the urge to groan. "You know you're smiling more than Sirius does when his one night stand leaves in the morning."

Albus just grinned and sought confirmation. "Your godfather, Sirius?"

Harry set his cup onto Albus' desk. "You're just dying to jump right into things, aren't you?"

"I make no secret of my desire for understanding."

"A rather annoying old man once told me the truth is a beautiful and terrible thing," Harry quipped. "And that it should be treated with great caution."

"Who said that?"

"You did," Harry succinctly replied. "Well, not exactly you."

Albus nodded, having suspected as much. "You have me at a disadvantage."

"Said the blackmailer," Harry retorted.

Albus frowned but saw little point in quibbling over words.

"Just ask what you want to, Albus," Harry helplessly admitted.

"What have I done to give you such a low opinion of me?" Albus questioned. He added with a smile, "Or not exactly me."

Harry bit the inside of his cheek. "Can we start with something simpler?"

"Very well," Albus agreed. "How about this one: tell me Harry Potter, why are you so opposed to your family, to your parents, knowing just who you are?"

Harry winced. "Because I don't know them. And there's already enough drama in my life."

"But you do know the Lupins?"

Harry sighed and figured he should start from the beginning. "Alright, first off, I suppose you need a little alternate history lesson. Halloween 1981, in the reality I grew up in, the Dark Lord Voldemort attacked at Godric's Hollow."

Albus nodded, urging Harry to go on.

"My parents were home that night," Harry explained. "And that night they died protecting me. So I've never known any James or Lily Potter. Sirius, my godfather, came through the Exit-"

"The Exit?"

Harry nodded. "The Exit, the veil, the death chamber, the stone archway in the Department of Mysteries, whatever you want to call it, my godfather fell through it over ten years ago. I began researching it in February. A by-product of my work was Sirius fell out the other side and into this world just a few months ago. So when he woke up in a hospital bed, he asked for Remus Lupin, his best friend in our reality. Hence, Tonks and Remus knew about me and my history before I ever arrived in this world."

Albus was tempted to inquire about the specifics of crossing over but wanted to understand Harry better. "That does not explain why you have not told your parents."

"James and Lily Potter seem like nice people," Harry admitted. "But they're not my parents."

"Not exactly," Albus replied using Harry's own words.

"Sirius was going to tell James who he was," Harry explained. "But when they met Sirius realized just how different this James Potter was from my dad."

"Those two do seem to rub each other the wrong way, don't they?"

Harry shrugged. "I can see it from both sides."

"And yet you choose to continue to deceive your 'not quite' parents."

Harry gave Albus a significant look. "It's only dumb luck that in this world there is a middle-aged couple who dealt with the grief of losing a baby and raised two other kids. My parents never saw twenty-two. You really think getting to know the Potters will tell me anything about my parents? They never even met them."

"Then perhaps you could give a middle-aged couple who dealt with the grief of losing a baby some peace of mind to know in other worlds their son has lived a healthy, happy life?"

Harry laughed. "You're really something else."

"I shall take that as a compliment."

Harry took another sip of his tea. "I know you want to stay on our good side. All I ask is that you let us tell the Potters in our own time."

Albus took a moment to observe Harry. "I can agree to that as long as you keep me informed of the people you do share the knowledge of your unique origins with."

"Albus," Harry sighed tiredly and glanced over at Fawkes empty perch. "I am not your student, nor an Order member. Those I and Sirius confide in are our business, not yours."

"I understand," Albus backtracked. "I just think it's in both of our best interests to keep this to ourselves for now."

Harry looked at Albus speculatively. "I would have thought you'd be a lot more vocal in championing an awkward reunion of sorts."

"The fewer people aware that there is a new candidate for the prophecy, the better."

Realization crossed Harry's face and he shook his head. "Sorry, Albus. But that prophecy isn't about me."

"You defeated the Voldemort of your world, didn't you?"

"What makes you think that?"

Albus smiled. "You dueled him. And you were entirely too confident and comfortable. Sirius hid it pretty well, but his eyes showed worry and fear. Your only fear was for Sirius."

"Yes," Harry admitted with a mixture of pain and pride. "I did defeat my Voldemort. But I can't vanquish this one any more than you can."

Albus frowned at the truthfulness he sensed. "Are you certain?"

"I have some idea of the costs you paid to defeat your Dark Lord," Harry instructed. "And in case you missed it, Voldemort is not a dark wizard. He's a genuine Dark Lord and all that that implies."

Albus winced as though the confirmation hurt him. "I had hoped that wasn't the case."

Harry grinned helplessly. "The muggles have a saying about putting all your hopes in one hand and then sh-"

"I'm familiar with the saying," Albus interrupted. "Thank you, Harry."

"Just trying to help."

Albus frowned in thought. "Was the cost to you simply too high to pay again?"

Harry considered the question before answering. "Yeah… I don't know. I'm not sure to be honest. But fortunately for me, it's not possible to pay again so I don't have to think about it."

"What was your cost?"

Harry was surprised Albus was asking so boldly. He let no emotion show as he watched the old man.

Albus nodded in understanding and voluntarily admitted, "I sacrificed the ability to father children and then I lost the ability to fall in love."

Harry hadn't known the specifics but guessed it had been something close to that for Albus. He knew how high that cost would be to a wizard like Albus. With a lick of his lips, Harry softly admitted, "I sacrificed my mother's everlasting soul."

Albus blinked in shock. "And what did you lose?"

Harry slowly shook his head. "My sacrifice was deemed sufficient."

Albus couldn't even imagine what Harry felt. The word came out as a whisper. "How?"

"When I was a baby she gave her life to protect me from Voldemort. It meant his next Killing Curse marked my noggin and bounced back into his face. It also left me with a protection from him." Harry frowned adding, "until he overcame that too."

Albus nodded in comprehension. "And since you carried her protection…"

"I was able to offer a soul other than my own," Harry finished for him. He sighed tiredly. "The worst part is that whenever I'm near the Lily Potter around here, the old magic wakes up and pulls on her soul. I'm like a harmless but annoying personal dementor to her."

"She mentioned feeling a draw to you," Albus agreed. "I assumed it was a mother's intuition not a… soul-sucking vortex."

"Don't just think like a wizard. Any muggle will tell you it's always a soul-sucking vortex."

Albus saw the forced smile as Harry tried to joke about his sacrifice. He could tell this was not a burden Harry had dealt with as much as one the young man had simply ignored. He immediately concluded that Lily Potter would be a tremendous help to Harry.

"Stop scheming," Harry grumbled. "I feel you plotting against me."

"Sorry," Albus reflexively replied, well aware Harry would sense he wasn't sorry in the slightest. "I don't suppose you have a second mother's sacrificial protection and the willingness to barter their soul?"

Harry shook his head. "Just the one. But I do have a rather pesky ghost haunting me."

Albus hadn't expected such a serious response. "Do you think he…?"

"Nope," Harry snapped. "I tried her first. Didn't work. She's kind of sensitive about it now."

"I would imagine so."

Harry smiled wanly. "Unfortunately, it furthered her delusion that we're destined to be together forever."

"I know a tribal chief skilled in matters of necromancy and souls," Albus offered.

"Believe me I've thought it about, often," Harry assured him. "But she usually behaves. And she was a good friend long before she became an ex."

"You're haunted by an ex-girlfriend?" Albus clarified smothering his own amusement. "Say the word. I can send a letter to my friend."

"Nah," Harry shook his head thinking how he actually needed Ginny's ghostly expertise. "She's a nuisance, but it's nice to have someone else who remembers our old world."

Albus grinned as he felt the charm of brotherhood's nudge indicating that Harry was hiding something. "Old world? Does that mean you are here to stay?"

"Yeah, that's the plan. The Exit to our old world was destroyed after I got pulled in. Wouldn't know how to get back even if it was still intact."

"Not expecting any visitors? And no travelers beyond yourself and Sirius?"

"The one I studied was used for executions a century ago but it had been misaligned. When I corrected it, Sirius was the only one spit out in this world, from what I'm told."

Albus nodded. "I believe it was 1903 when the dementor's kiss replaced execution as the highest form of punishment in our courts."

"Sounds about right."

Albus took another sip of his tea, thinking over all he'd learned so far. "Do you think perhaps it is your hope that the prophecy doesn't refer to you that's influencing your interpretation?"

"I'm not some wayward child, Albus," Harry retorted as he sat up a bit prouder. "I didn't just get a lucky shot in a duel. It was several years after your death that I finally defeated the bastard. And I don't appreciate feeling like a pawn in the game you're playing."

Albus raised his hands in deference. "I am sorry if my conversation feels like manipulation to you. But it sounds like my counterpart may have wronged you and that is coloring your perceptions. To use your metaphor, I am not the chess master, but just another piece in the same game you are."

"I want no part of that game."

"I wish it were that simple," Albus admitted. "And while you may not be the king I'd hoped, you are still a knight, the same as me. Maybe you've not moved from your spot and maybe you won't have to, but I assure you, you are most definitely on the board."

Harry frowned. "I think you've driven the metaphor into the ground."

"I thought I might have," Albus admitted reaching for the candy dish on his desk. He pondered whether he even wanted to know. "Can I ask you a question?"

"Obviously, you've just done so," Harry said with a smirk.

Albus grinned. "I've used that line on you, haven't I?"

Harry gave an affirmative nod and urged Albus to continue.

"Would it be beneficial for me to inquire about the details of my counterpart's demise?"

Harry saw Albus was leaving the decision up to him. "It is not a situation that will repeat itself here, but it might help you to understand our relationship a bit better."

Albus sensed Harry was more affected than he was showing. "You were there, weren't you?"

Harry nodded. "Alright, first off, in my totally objective and unbiased opinion you should realize Severus Snape of my old world is a bigger asshole than you'd find on a blind giant's narcoleptic bride."

Albus looked vaguely unsettled as he processed the meaning. "Severus?"

"Yeah," Harry admitted before pausing. "I'm not sure the details of this world's Snape, but in my old one he joined the Death Eaters right out of school. There was probably some reason like the executive washroom for inner circle members had too much gold trim for his delicate sense of aesthetics. Whatever it was, he quickly turned traitor, secretly stabbing his new friends in the back, and became the Order's spy in the Dark Lord's organization."

Albus was fighting a smile. "You could just say you weren't aware of Severus' motives."

"You weren't exactly forthcoming with that information any more than Snape was," Harry retorted. "As a result, you were the only person who trusted him. Probably on either side, come to think of it."

"This is leading somewhere, isn't it," Albus encouraged. "You're not just insulting my Potions professor?"

"Contrary to what you imply, merely insulting your Potions professor is in fact an excellent and worthwhile way to pass the time," Harry argued. "But yes, I'm getting there."

Albus muttered to himself, "Maybe it's a Potter thing."

"How do you think Snape would respond if all the Potters were dead except for a baby, especially one hailed as the savior and hero of the wizarding world while still in diapers?"

Albus briefly wondered if Severus would be able to set aside his bitterness. He stifled a snort. "Understood."

"Anyways, I'm just trying to explain the fact that my entire fifth year at Hogwarts you avoided me, until the end of the year when Sirius died—or what passed for dead at the time—and you only then informed me of the prophecy."

Albus frowned uncertainly.

"I say this so you understand that in sixth year, when you'd finally started to become something of a mentor to me, it was a pretty shitty thing you did."

"And what did I do?"

"You petrified me and covered me with an invisibility cloak as Death Eaters stormed the Astronomy Tower. Then you allowed yourself to get captured and let or more likely invited Severus to strike you down with a Killing Curse, sending you to your death and a grisly fall."

Albus sat there silently allowing Harry to speak.

"I couldn't move until you were dead," Harry weakly relayed. "I know Severus Snape could never really take you, but I guess you wanted to give him iron-clad proof of his loyalty to the Dark Lord. I think you had to have been sick and dying anyway, but I couldn't even get confirmation of that."

Albus steepled his fingers in thought, "You will have a better idea of my counterpart's motivation but I am sorry you had to see that."

"That's when things really started to go to hell in a hand basket too. With you dead, people lost hope and just wanted to give up. The second war got really bad after that."

Albus was saddened but could identify with the burden his counterpart had carried. "Were we close?"

"Kind of, yeah," Harry paused thinking neither yes nor no sounded right. "I think we should've been closer and I don't doubt that you loved me like a grandson, but you messed up a lot where I'm concerned."

"Enlighten me," Albus cheerfully instructed. "So that I may avoid making the same mistakes."

Harry stopped himself from saying, 'just don't force me back to the Dursleys.' He took a sip of his tea and looked up at the eager Headmaster. "Don't worry. You can't make those particular mistakes again. I just had the one childhood to ruin and fragile emotional psyche to shatter. And besides, we've talked about my old world plenty. For all intents and purposes, that world was a long waking dream for me. Let's talk about this one."

"The experiences of our pasts define who we are today," Albus intoned. "But we can talk about this world. Would you like to join the Order?"

Harry fought a smile. "That was abrupt."

Albus nodded. "I suspect you will not accept my invitation at first, so I thought I should begin laying the groundwork for future overtures."

"Blunt honesty too," Harry grinned. "I'll give you points for effort."

Albus looked at Harry hopefully but nodded when the younger man made his denial clear. "Luckily for him but perhaps unfortunately for the Order, Severus Snape has never been a Death Eater in this world."

Harry gave a look of mischief. "Are you sure? Would you bet your life on that?"

"I trust Severus Snape," Albus said. "But alas, there are grains of truth in some of the stories surrounding his ill-fated attempt to join the Dark Lord."

"If I promise not to enjoy them too much, could you tell me the real ones?"

Albus scrutinized Harry. "I sincerely doubt you could make that promise."

"True," Harry agreed before forcing a twinkle into his eye. "Pretty please?"

"I hope that look you made rarely worked on me."

"Never tried it on you," Harry said. "But it never worked on Hermione."

"Hermione Granger?" Albus asked and received an affirmative response. "Is that why you abducted her and took her to Africa?"

"Just having a spot of fun," Harry replied. "And I'm quite sure my best friend Hermione would agree that this Hermione needed a kick in the pants and a poke in the-"

"Harry," Albus warned.

"…eye," Harry innocently finished. "Weren't you about to tell me about Snape's ill-fated attempt?"

Albus took his time but obliged. "Severus had been denied back when he was student. But he had an acquaintance prepared to vouch for him. I called in a few favors and secured him a Ministry exemption for all non-harmful dark arts."

"Non-harmful?"

Albus nodded. "Severus' potion making skills were never in question, but it was required that he demonstrate some other coveted talents. He led his initiation evaluators-"

"Wait," Harry interrupted. "Initiation evaluators?"

"They may have been having a laugh at Severus' expense, but yes, they referred to themselves as initiation evaluators. As I was saying, Severus led them to a muggle woman that he specifically targeted."

Harry grinned. "Yeah?"

Albus took a breath and reluctantly explained. "He intended to sow chaos and discord among countless muggles worldwide."

"He didn't attack the Queen, did he?"

Albus shook his head quickly. "That rumor is patently false. No, the woman is simply an author, just an extremely popular one. His plan was to 'torture' muggles with a poorly written story."

Harry goggled. "That was his grand plan?"

Albus winced. "Had I known his intentions beforehand I would have advised him against that course of action. But he had decided I would be better off ignorant of the details of his less than legal activities."

"I take it the initiation evaluators were unimpressed?"

Albus took off his glasses to rub the bridge of his nose. "More amused than anything else. He misinterpreted their laughter and cheers and made a few boisterous comments that have since taken on a life of their own."

"Like what?"

"I believe the Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes offer a shirt exclaiming, 'We will get them where we can hurt them the most. We will attack … at their leisure.'"

"At their leisure?" Harry snickered.

"There may have been some strutting and billowing of his cloak when he said it."

Harry smiled at the image before frowning in consternation. "Does that mean you have no ears within the Dark Lord's ranks?"

Albus schooled his face showing no emotion. "It shouldn't surprise you that I won't be answering that question."

"Good point," Harry admitted. "So what can you tell me about That Fucker?"

Albus was momentarily shocked. "Excuse me?"

"Are you That Fucker?" Harry asked while openly inspecting Albus.

"I assume you are referring to the mysterious wizard in black who occupies much of Voldemort's time?"

"Damn," Harry swore, knowing it was an unlikely possibility. "That would have almost made sense."

Albus could tell Harry had concluded that he wasn't the mysterious wizard. "What do you know of the wizard that led you to suspect me?"

"Not much," Harry admitted. "Just that it's someone strong enough and willing to stand up to the Dark Lord."

"I will admit that is a woefully short list."

"And," Harry interrupted. "And I know this mysterious wizard didn't show up until after the disappearance of Neville Longbottom. Perhaps someone who knows the two first candidates were dead and he needed to wait for another son born at the end of a July. Someone with a little too much faith in the prophecy, believing he cannot vanquish the Dark Lord. So he does all he can to thwart Voldemort without actively engaging him."

"You've thought this through," Albus replied slightly surprised he was a suspect.

Harry shrugged. "I would imagine that sometimes you… 'limit your arsenal' let's say. Because you are so widely perceived to be and looked upon as the consummate light wizard and role model."

"You think I could hide behind a mask and be a bit more ruthless?"

Harry snorted. "Do you really want me to answer that?"

Albus frowned playfully. "No, I think you've answered it quite clearly."

Harry scratched his head. "In retrospect, it does sound a bit nutty. Even for you."

"I'd like to think so," Albus agreed. "I should point out one fallacy of your logic is that the idea of waiting on a new subject for the prophecy is one that's widely shared by others. There are many people out there who actively avoid having children near the end of July for that very reason."

"Makes sense."

"Yes, well there are also those that induce birth just before midnight and the calendar turns to August, almost always leading to complications."

"You're kidding."

Albus shook his head. "I'm afraid not. It appears that night is as cursed as the Defense Against the Dark Arts position. Speaking of, have you ever considered teaching?"

Harry looked at Albus incredulously. "Bite me."

Albus chuckled. "A 'no' would have been sufficient."

"But not as effective," Harry assured him. "I take it you're not one of those keeping their eyes on the maternity ward around the end of July?"

Albus sighed and sat back tiredly in his chair. "For many years, I had been holding on to the hope that Neville Longbottom is still out there."

Harry noticed the use of 'had' rather than 'have.' "You don't believe that anymore?"

Albus looked at Harry innocently. "Not for the last couple of days, no."

Harry was quick to anger. "You still think its-"

"Please, Harry," Albus stopped him. "I firmly understand that you do not believe the prophecy applies to you. I may have reservations but I do not doubt that you have none. I'm not trying to pester you. I'm merely admitting that until a couple days ago, I had never questioned whether Neville was still out there somewhere. I had to believe he was. Your appearance gives me doubt."

"It's not me," Harry childishly pouted.

"Do keep in mind that until this conversation I was unaware that you already had defeated a Dark Lord and that Voldemort legitimately was one," Albus pointed out. "I don't think the prophecy refers to you, but I'm not certain. And you definitely… shake things up a bit."

"So you haven't squirreled Neville away for some special secret training?" Harry asked and saw the look on Albus' face. "Didn't think so. And you don't think Neville is That Fucker?"

Albus looked at Harry curiously. "I assume from your preoccupation that your world had no such unknown wizard in black."

"Nope. My world was quite a bit different from this one," Harry admitted with a shrug. "Hell, probably the second most dangerous person and right hand to the Dark Lord was Bellatrix."

"Really?" Albus asked in happy surprise. "I always knew Miss Black was quite powerful but… is that why you wanted to separate her from the Dark Lord?"

Harry blinked. "Sure, I mean, that and… she's hot."

"I hardly think being attractive should matter in this."

"Maybe not," Harry playfully admitted. "But it helps when we loan her out for sex to our guests."

"Harry," Albus reprimanded.

"Why do you think Jimmy likes coming over so much?"

Albus lightly reminded, "With the charm, I can tell when you're lying."

"Right," Harry agreed. "And Bellatrix is carrying Remus' illegitimate baby."

Albus furrowed his brow in uncertainty. "At least I thought I could."

Harry's eyes were twinkling merrily.

"Do you think perhaps I could speak to Miss Black?" Albus saw Harry's look and added, "I'm willing to swear an oath to protect her from incriminating herself."

"I'm not going to force her or even encourage her," Harry replied. "But I'll ask for you. It's up to her."

"Thank you," Albus said with an approving nod.

Harry saw Albus was already thinking about what to ask Bellatrix and changed the subject. "How'd he die?"

Albus looked up. "Who?"

"Neville."

"That," Albus answered in irritation, "I do not know."

Harry nodded, urging Albus to elaborate.

"The Longbottoms were protected by a Fidelius Charm that was not broken," Albus explained. "I, myself, put up several other monitoring wards and security measures."

"Anything interesting?" Harry asked. He explained, "Wards are something of a hobby of mine."

Albus inclined his head. "Are you familiar with the Greek wizard, Stavros?

Harry let out a low whistle. "Those are some nice wards. Inside or outside the Fidelius?"

"Outside," Albus replied. "I didn't know they could be placed inside."

Harry nodded. "You'll need two separate sets of stones, and the inside ones have to be placed first. Then put up the Fidelius on the outer set, and bring in a second caster unaware of the Fidelius secret. You have to cast them blind because of the Fidelius, but they come out a lot stronger, bound within the secret."

"Interesting," Albus commented imagining how difficult casting Stavros wards blindly would be. "I can tell you according to my monitors Neville never left the property. And after many inspections, I also can tell that he no longer lives within the wards."

"Yeah," Harry nodded. "That points to dead."

"The most damning evidence was his mother's intuition."

Harry blinked having not even considered Neville's parents. " Alice thinks he's dead?"

Albus nodded. "I wonder if perhaps she felt a bond with her son disappear. She was certain he was dead and took her own life a month after Neville's disappearance."

Harry was immediately reminded of the story he'd given Lily Potter and frowned. "That sucks."

"Quite."

Harry doubted the Neville he knew could even imagine leaving his parents with so much grief. "What about Frank?"

Albus smiled. "Were the Longbottoms friends of yours in your world?"

"Naw," Harry replied. "Bellatrix crucioed their brains out when Neville was a baby. But Neville was a friend of mine… 'til he died."

Albus frowned uncertainly. "Sometimes I think you're just messing with me."

"Who? Moi?" Harry meekly said before abandoning the charade. "I could never pull off innocent. Even in the rare times I was innocent."

"Funny," Albus deadpanned. "The charm seems to think you're lying."

"Alright," Harry softly conceded. "Maybe I can pull off innocent."

"Neville," Albus paused. "Neville was a very bright young boy. His situation gave him few social opportunities, but he had a love of learning and books that reminded me of myself."

"Nerd, huh?"

"The Longbottoms had a pond in their backyard covered by the Fidelius and Neville could almost always be found under the shade of a tree reading. He barely ever left the home and wards, but he still carried a Martin Miggs backpack with him everywhere he went. He got tired of having to choose which of his favorite books could fit so he got a hold of his mother's wand and managed to charm his backpack larger on the inside." Albus smiled sadly. "I was so impressed that I offered to charm it featherweight for him."

Harry gave Albus a moment as he saw the old man was lost in memories. "So how did the prophecy get out?"

Albus muffled a displeased grumble. "I was always opposed to it getting out to anyone. Rumors had been spreading and then the papers started reporting unsubstantiated prophecies. Frank explicitly ignored my strongly worded advice and leaked the real prophecy's content and details."

"Doggie got off his leash?" Harry suggested. He gulped at the look on Albus' face and apologized immediately. "Sorry. Continue."

"Frank and I rarely saw eye to eye on what was in Neville's best interests."

Harry was tempted to ask if Albus wanted Neville abused and unloved but held his tongue. "Like what?"

"There should never be a fine line between raising a son and raising a soldier," Albus answered. "And Frank felt Hogwarts would slow Neville down."

"That's like a kick in the balls to you, isn't it?"

Albus smiled. "I think the majority of the lessons at Hogwarts are not learned in the classrooms. Here is where children become young adults, learn to make friends, learn to care, learn to heal, and learn magic. Special students can always be accommodated with advanced tutoring but to view the Hogwarts experience as nothing more than training for-"

"Down boy," Harry interrupted. "I'm with you. Hogwarts, yay."

Albus calmed. He reached for his candy dish and popped one in his mouth. "Yay indeed."

"So what's Frank up to these days?"

Albus pursed his lips on the sour candy in his mouth. "I haven't seen him in six years. He's been trying to run away from his past. I visited him after he'd checked himself into a home for mental healing in Australia. The healer felt I would help Frank confront some of his issues. I don't think he's returned to England in over twenty years."

Harry frowned and wondered if catatonic Frank might have been better off. "So who do you think That Fucker is? Straight answer, please."

"I haven't the foggiest," Albus happily replied. "I spent many years trying to uncover more on the mysterious wizard in black."

"Surely you've got a guess," Harry pleaded.

"I have several guesses, none of which seem remotely probable. And no, I wouldn't care to share them," Albus grinned.

"Why not?"

"Harry, I don't know who he is but I have crossed his path on a couple of occasions," Albus explained. "One time I unwittingly walked right into a trap of his and found myself bound and wandless. He let me go with only minor humiliation, leading me to believe he is not an enemy. And the mystery of his identity has kept Voldemort occupied and confused for decades now."

"You?" Harry repeated doubtfully. "Don't know something and are willing to leave it be? Really?"

"Yes, really. The wizard in black has managed to keep his identity from both myself and Voldemort. And as long as it remains secret, Voldemort will be hesitant and tentative. I have a very good idea of how much worse things could be."

"From what I hear That Fucker avoids confronting Voldemort. Not that he's scared or unable but that he's just being annoying."

Albus smiled widely. "That sounds like vaguely familiar press for a couple of new Lords I know."

Harry realized he'd walked right into that one. "Yeah, but we're pretty."

Albus paused contemplating whether to contend that point before moving on. "I think it's possible that the wizard in black is doing all he can."

"What do you mean?"

"He is remarkably well-informed," Albus replied. "And it is entirely possible that the magic of the Dark Mark prevents people from directly confronting Voldemort."

"You think he's a Death Eater?" Harry asked in surprise while running through all the inner circle names he could remember.

Albus shrugged. "I have several guesses. Some more plausible than others."

"Oh yeah?" Harry questioned. "What's your craziest?"

"I haven't exactly ranked them," Albus replied. "But a number of questions remain about your counterpart's death."

Harry recalled what Bellatrix had revealed. "You think it might be me?"

"I never said that, I said questions remain. I don't know what you've been told, but there was nothing natural about the manner in which Voldemort killed you. Foul, dark magic unlike any I've felt before was involved." Albus shuddered. "It wasn't like any summoning ritual I've read about, but your deaths were not simple murder."

Harry smothered a grin. "You think Voldemort might have summoned a demon That Fucker?"

"You asked for the craziest," Albus replied. "But I get the feeling you know more about that night than I."

Harry looked at Albus before answering, "I suppose unless you're confronted with it, you assume Voldemort's claims of nearing immortality are nothing more than hollow boasting."

Dumbledore blanched and whispered out, "What?"

Harry winced and asked, "Have you ever heard of a… horcrux?"

Albus pursed his lips and searched the recesses of his mind. "I don't think I have."

Harry sensed only truth from the charm and nodded. He almost wished he could take that word back but figured he'd let the Headmaster figure it out on his own. "So that's your craziest?"

Albus considered pushing Harry on the subject but realized Harry wanted him to discover something himself. He would ask Harry more questions when he had the right questions to ask. "Well, I suppose now we should give serious consideration to the possibility of travelers from another world."

"Touché," Harry agreed.

Albus took a moment to choose his words carefully. "May I ask you something personal?"

Harry glanced at his watch. "Yeah, sure. But don't waste your last question on something you know I won't answer. I'm going to get going after this."

"I was hoping to hear in your own words why you aren't more opposed to the Dark Lord Voldemort."

Harry looked up. "Truthfully? I guess it's really that he hasn't done anything to me. I'm like the out-of-towner who just moved to a new country. While I'm not in favor of my neighbor's death, I don't feel any attachment to them. And as different as the worlds are, I can't see the same darkness in similar eyes nor do I receive the same kindness from the familiar faces.

"For me it's simply like everyone are strangers wearing masks of my old friends. If I have to view them that way, then a wizard wearing a mask of the Dark Lord must be held to the same standard. So far this Voldemort took his ass-kicking and has left me alone. My old Headmaster always told me it was the choices we make that define who we are."

Albus grumbled good-naturedly. "That sounds like my usual trite rubbish."

"I would probably try and argue that Sirius and I have already been through a war and deserve a break, but we're both adrenaline junkies who enjoy havoc too much for that excuse to hold water."

"You don't say," Albus dryly agreed.

"But the other main thing is that I absolutely adore the fact that my life in this world has been so relaxing and… normal! I'm just another wizard here. It's beyond refreshing."

Albus blinked in shock. He made sure the brotherhood charm was still in effect. "Well on behalf of this world, we're happy to have you."

"Thank you."

"Now do you mind paying a little rent and vanquishing the Dark Lord?"

"Albus…"

"I'm willing to treat you normal."

Harry felt the charm twitch. "Liar."

Albus was about to clarify when he sensed a warning. He held up a hand stopping Harry from talking just as the current Head Boy burst into the Headmaster's office.

Harry glanced over at the out of breath youngest Potter. "Jimmy?"

Jimmy was gob smacked staring at Harry and the Headmaster in turn. He was panting from sprinting down here and pulled the magical parchment out of his pocket to make sure his eyes weren't playing tricks on him.

Harry saw the Headmaster looking genuinely surprised and did not recognize the Marauder's Map for what it was.

Albus leaned forward and asked, "Mr. Potter? What is so important that you felt the need to burst into my office?"

Jimmy looked at the map and back three more times continuing to ignore the Headmaster. He stared right at Harry, begging for an explanation. "You're Harry… Potter?"

Harry flashed an irritated look at Albus and stood up. "I think that's about as crystal clear as a cue to leave can be."

"No, wait!" Jimmy pleaded. "I just… I mean… huh?"

"Do not pass on this golden opportunity," Albus warned Harry. "And I hope to speak to you again soon, Harry."

Harry glanced at his hand and then the Headmaster. "Feel like leaving the charm up?"

"Delighted to," Albus agreed.

Harry slung an arm over the confused and wary Head Boy's shoulder. "Tell me, Jimmy, have you ever played the obliviate game?"

"Harry!" Albus scolded.

"Good point," Harry nodded firmly. "Let's get you away from these pesky over-protective Hogwarts wards."

Jimmy looked to the Headmaster before turning to Harry and shrugging. "Okay."

"James?" Albus warily inquired.

"As Head Boy I can leave the grounds," Jimmy claimed. "Besides, he's my brother. What's he gonna do?"

"Yes Albus," Harry parroted. "What am I going to do?"

Albus slumped back in his chair in tired acceptance of the situation. "Good night, children," he pouted with emphasis on the last word.

"Refresh my memory," Jimmy said beginning the walk down the spiral staircase. "I think I've played the obliviate game before but I'm kind of fuzzy on the rules."

Albus really hoped Jimmy was kidding.

Chapter 26

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

The Noble and Most Ancient House of Black

in accordance with

GRINGOTTS of LONDON

on the 24th of May at 8:00 PM will be holding a PRIVATE auction of three distinct and separate lots.

Attendance by Invitation Only

LOT 1 - Ravenclaw's Cube: A personal project of the intelligent founder of Hogwarts, Rowena Ravenclaw's cube paved the way for the creation of the modern pensieve. This cube is believed to be the first man-made device capable of holding memories.

LOT 2 - Slytherin's Locket: The personal talisman Salazar Slytherin wore around his neck in the years after banishment from Hogwarts. Rumored to possess secret powers, the efficacy of the magic of the locket is not guaranteed by Gringotts.

LOT 3 - Hufflepuff's Cup: This ancient chalice was used by the kind-hearted founder to administer potions in the very first incarnation of the Hogwarts' hospital wing. It is unknown how long the cup has been in the Hufflepuff family, but it predates Helga Hufflepuff herself by at least six centuries.

Gringotts of London affirms and certifies the authenticity of all lots as announced.
If you believe you have received an invitation in error or did not receive an invitation you should have, please direct your questions and concerns to Gringotts. Ask for Bloodthrust.

"Bloodthrust?" Lawson questioned from behind his Death Eater mask. "A goblin is running this?"

"Yeah," Cavanagh said pointing at the formal announcement in the legal notices section of the Daily Prophet. "Check it out. They even included a picture of the goblin. I'm not sure, but I think it might be smiling."

Lawson flinched at the gruesome winking visage. "Have you informed our Lord?"

"Are you kidding?" Cavanagh scoffed. "I've been around too long to fall for that one."

Lawson frowned. "Does he not know yet? He's going to want his ancestor's locket."

A sudden and violent shout pierced the air right before both men felt the tattoos on their arms burn.

Cavanagh winced. "I think it's safe to say he knows."

Cavanagh and Lawson hurried in behind Simmons to their Master's chambers and found Jugson and the Dark Lord awaiting them. They could all feel the anger rolling off the Dark Lord and as he crumpled a scorched copy of the Daily Prophet in his left hand.

"Spread the word," Voldemort instructed as the three newcomers bowed and waited attentively. "It's open season on all Blacks."

Cavanagh looked his Master in the eye and was quickly reminded of his place as the Dark Lord shredded his meager mental shields and implanted a series of visual locations. Cavanagh forced his eyes closed as he tore his gaze away.

Voldemort's breathing quieted as he ordered. "You are to check those sites, but touch nothing. Understood?"

Cavanagh mutely nodded. He took careful measured steps as he left the room, still dazed from the rough mental intrusion.

"Lawson," Voldemort whispered dangerously. "You are to follow Cavanagh but do not interfere. He may pick up other tails, so make sure you are undetected. If he is killed or captured, you are to report immediately to me. Do not assist him. Understood?"

Lawson nodded firmly.

"Do not fail me." The Dark Lord turned to Simmons, indicating Lawson was dismissed. "Simmons. You are to find out everything you can about the auction in three days. I expect a full report by this evening."

Simmons nodded and briskly left the room, leaving Jugson alone with the Dark Lord.

"Your arm," Voldemort demanded as he twirled the wand in his hand.

Jugson pushed his sleeve up again, revealing the Dark Mark. He grimaced but made no other movement as his arm burned and the Dark Lord's magic was channeled through the Mark.

Voldemort smiled at Jugson's obedience. "Lucius is on his way. Open a line of communication with our contact at Hogwarts. I have a special plan that will require a few of our allies."

Jugson perked up at the mention of allies and a wide smile grew across his face. "I look forward to it, my Lord."

Voldemort scowled, angry at himself more than anything. He had managed to underestimate the Lord Blacks again. He wondered briefly if he had been too hasty in assuming they had nothing to do with the biggest thorn in his side.

"That fucker!"

"Don't you mean-"

"Those fuckers!"

Alan Weston winced. He knew he was going to be the bearer of bad news as soon as he saw the auction announcement.

"I cannot believe they would do this," the wizard ranted as he reread the legal notices section at the start of the Daily Prophet classifieds. "Auctioning off the Dark Lord's soul? That's madness."

"It is a bit nutty," Alan agreed.

The mysterious wizard was pacing across the room. "They have to know the only people who matter will see it's nothing but a trap."

"Oh right," Alan agreed.

"There's got to be more to this," the wizard concluded as he settled into an immaculate armchair. He looked over the paper again seeking out clues.

Alan recognized the other wizard's expression when everything slid into place. "What is it?"

"This isn't about Voldemort, this is about me," the wizard in black explained ruefully. "I did not see this coming. It's every bit as stupid as it is cunning."

"I take it we have them to thank for Malfoy's weeklong barbecue?"

"They got my note." The man nodded with certainty. He considered his options. "They're forcing me to attack a certain trap, look like a scared liar, or show up and play nice on their turf by their rules."

Alan frowned. "I'm guessing option one is out and two isn't really your style."

"No," the wizard said. "We're definitely going and playing nice. We have to."

"We?"

The man nodded as he poured himself some brandy. "This is too immense an opportunity to pass up even if they are forcing our hand."

"It is?"

"Did you not notice? There are three objects in the auction." He took a sip and saw Alan's look of confusion. "Unless I've misjudged the Blacks further, those three will complete the collection. And while they've announced it with the subtlety of a nesting dragon, it still is two weeks until the full moon, which is the soonest Voldemort could even attempt making another."

Alan blinked in shock.

The wizard smirked. "Even if he could, I doubt he'd succeed on his first try. His soul is too fractured."

Alan was watching the other man desperately. "Are you saying…?"

"Yes," the man in black slowly agreed. He took another sip. "Those fuckers have started the clock."

"My clock's stopped."

Albus picked up the magical device on the corner of his desk. He looked in a gap at the top curiously. "Is that…?" Albus took a careful sniff and jerked the clock away. "It smells like the owlery. Fawkes, do you know if the pooping owl is back again?"

Fawkes let out a chirp of annoyance before he realized he had shifted in his sleep and was about to fall from his perch.

"I've apologized numerous times," Albus assured the phoenix. "I never should have accused you of defecating on my desk."

Fawkes let out a stream of soft chirping as he waddled his way back to the center of the perch.

"Something in today's paper, you say?" Albus asked in surprise. He picked up the lifestyle and sports sections he had discarded earlier.

Fawkes was about to settle back into the middle of his perch when he realized the balance felt off.

Albus' eyes lost their twinkle as he read through the auction announcement several times. "I don't understand it, Fawkes. Why would Harry do this? What could they possibly gain from this auction?"

The bird gave up on figuring out what was wrong with the balance and sat back down, facing Albus. He chirped a little wondering why his tail feathers itched.

"No," Albus disagreed. "It's not about the money. I'm almost certain. This is… this is… kicking a hornets' nest to see if there are any hornets? Or to see if they will attack?"

Fawkes tilted his head, stretching out the kinks in his neck.

"You're right, of course," Albus said with a nod. "This is why the Lupins both took the next few days off from work. Harry and Sirius have clearly put some thought into this, even if we cannot divine their motivation."

Fawkes wiggled his bottom half as he slid back into a flatter position on his perch.

"Do you really think so?"

Fawkes let out a small chirp as the cold metal of the perch startled him on his sensitive under feathers.

"I know, my friend," Albus smiled at the phoenix. "I should have some faith in them. They are no doubt under an immense amount of charms and wards. And they are protecting the other Blacks, so they have a plan."

Fawkes let out several more chirps as his own body heat was countering the chilly metal he rested upon.

"My goodness, you're right," Albus gasped. "They don't… Harry never… Oh dear. Harry has no idea that Voldemort has made the Potter connection and is aware Harry and Sirius are not native to this world. This is no good."

Fawkes warbled quietly, wishing Albus wasn't so chatty today. He lifted his right wing before folding it back under in a more comfortable position.

Albus turned to the wall Fawkes pointed at. "The chocolate frog cards! You're a genius, Fawkes."

Fawkes closed his eyes and decided it was nap time.

Albus began digging into his pockets until he located his chocolate frog card. "Remus Lupin!" he clearly stated towards the small magical portrait of himself.

The surface of the card blurred and darkened, ending with only an inky color. "Albus?"

"Yes, Remus," Albus answered feeling perturbed. "I cannot see you. Can you see me?"

"No," Remus replied. "I know Harry's warded this place to high heaven. Let me ask him."

"What?" Harry's muffled voice could be barely heard. "You can hear him?"

Albus patiently listened as Remus and Harry were talking on the other side of the connection.

"What about now?" Harry distantly yelled.

"No change," Remus' voice replied. "Shouldn't you be taking some of the wards down, not putting more up?"

"What about now?"

"No," Remus shouted back. He leaned closer and clearly said, "I'm sorry about this, Albus."

"Quite alright," Albus replied. "These things happen."

"This should do it," Harry's far off cry was the last thing Albus heard before the black surface disappeared and the chocolate frog card returned to its inert state.

The holographic portrait of himself smiled and waved up at him.

Albus frowned. "You're mocking me, aren't you?"

The small picture responded by grabbing the bottom of his beard and feeding it into his own ear. After two fistfuls had been pushed in, the tip of the beard emerged out of his ear on the other side. The chocolate frog card proceeded to tug his beard left and right through his own supposedly empty head.

Albus picked the card up and spoke clearly into it again. "Remus Lupin!" After a few seconds of nothing happening, he intoned, "Tonks Lupin!"

Again there was no response, so Albus tried, "Nymphadora Lupin? Nymphadora Tonks Lupin? Auror Lupin? Auror Tonks Lupin?" Albus sighed as he was forced to accept the fact that Harry had not been adjusting his wards so they could communicate better. "That bloody annoying bastard."

The surface of the chocolate frog card darkened to blackness. The illusion of creamy off-white smoke billowed out revealing the worried face of Severus Snape. "What is it, Headmaster?"

Albus blinked. "My apologies, Severus. I did not mean to call you."

Severus was a little worried at the rare surprised look on Albus' face. "I shall return to my class."

Albus just nodded, deactivating the chocolate frog card. "I'll need to watch what I say around you."

The holographic picture just nodded as Albus stuffed the card back into one of his pockets.

Albus looked over and saw Fawkes staring at him. "They are most likely under a Fidelius charm and beyond a post owl's reach. I could ask to borrow Mr. Potter's mirror but I suspect that would upset Harry."

Fawkes doubted Albus would ever let him get any sleep and flew over to his desk, intending to express his displeasure in a way that would ruin the mystery of the pooping owl.

Albus watched the large avian lift its leg and exclaimed. "Of course! You can reach him still!"

Fawkes was startled and couldn't stop himself fast enough. He saw his pet human was engrossed in penning a short note. Fawkes took the opportunity to drag Albus' hat in small unnoticed steps, until he'd fully covered up the small accident.

Albus read through the note a second time and nodded. He folded it up and sealed the envelope with a tap of his wand. "Can you get this to Harry?"

Fawkes figured if he was going to get any sleep, he should just take the note and not put up a fight. He grabbed it in his beak and disappeared in a flash of fire.

Albus relaxed when he saw Fawkes return and settle right back into his favorite position on the perch. He decided he should warn the Minister and DMLE to be especially alert for the next few days. He stood up and turned to the large portrait of a fourteenth century Headmaster. "I believe we should prepare Hogwarts defenses."

"Wise move, Headmaster," the portrait agreed as it swung open revealing a darkened room. "Do you think they know what they are doing?"

"Let us hope so."

"Stop! Stop! You have no idea what you're doing."

Harry pulled his wand back from the portrait's surface. "I don't see you giving me any ideas."

The irate portrait of Lord Eugene Simmons growled at Harry. "I don't know the first thing about manipulating portraits and I certainly wouldn't tell you if I did."

"Please?" Harry asked hopefully.

The portrait just stared at Harry in disgust.

"Hence," Harry grinned pushing his wand onto the nameplate at the bottom of the frame. "Trial and error."

"Be honest, Harry." Sirius chided from the other side of the room.

"Okay," Harry agreed. "Error and error." He sent a burst of barely-formed magic into the portrait's frame.

The magic soaked into the carved wood, visibly flowing up the top and then cascading back down.

Harry thought he may have stumbled across something when the magic reached the nameplate at the base again and spewed fire at him, catching his sleeve. "Ahh!" he shouted as he tried to rub the small flames out. He was rubbing furiously, making little headway, when his flailing arms caught a wingback chair on fire.

Harry's wits finally came back to him and he was about to squelch the fire when he was blasted into the wall by massive stream of water from Sirius' fire hose charm.

Sirius was swinging his arm back and forth between Harry and the chair. Both were completely drenched and the fire was out, but Harry made girlish yelps every time the stream pinned him against the wall.

The fire hose charm failed when Sirius was flipped in the air and dangling by his ankle. "Harry," he whined before falling the short distance back to the ground.

"Uhh," Harry wheezed after having the wind knocked out of him by the overzealous fire-fighting.

"Oww," Sirius groaned after landing on his tailbone.

The mocking laughter of Lord Simmons reminded them they were not alone.

"What are you laughing at?" Harry grumbled as he took off his soggy robe.

Lord Simmons looked down from his frame. "I'm laughing at a pair of morons."

"Laugh it up," Sirius said standing as he rubbed his sore bum. "Then remember your families have been exposed as Death Eater scum and we took all your good shit."

A cacophony of angry ranting started cascading in from all directions.

"Nice, Padfoot."

"Sorry, Harry," Sirius said as they left the room filled with angry shouting portraits. "Our master plan of a giant portrait spy network isn't quite ready for the world."

Harry shrugged. "I figured since we were in lockdown, I might as well work on something."

He wrung his dripping robe out, before remembering Fawkes had interrupted him earlier. He dug into his robe pocket and pulled out a scorched and blurry ink-stained envelope. He tried to open the letter and just tore the soggy parchment. "Great. You ruined it."

"Don't blame me," Sirius defended. "That thing is more burnt than wet. What'd it say anyway?"

"Albus was calling us foolish and trying to talk us out of the auction, no doubt."

"No doubt?"

"I hadn't read it yet, but I think we can both guess most of it."

Sirius scratched his chin. "You think maybe he was trying to bid?"

Harry just looked at his godfather.

"Yeah, didn't think so," Sirius agreed. "So I got the portkey working on the display case."

"Oh yeah?"

Sirius nodded. "Magic detection is still finicky. But I got bored and figured we should entertain our prisoners."

"Guests, Sirius," Harry corrected. "They're called guests."

"What are you doing?" Remus questioned when he saw Tonks using the tip of her wand to dig into the surface of the kitchen table.

Tonks didn't even look up. "I'm counting the days we're imprisoned here since time has lost all meaning."

"It's not that bad," Remus reminded his adopted daughter.

Tonks kept scraping and pouted, "Have you even been listening to what they're talking about?"

Remus gave his daughter a gentle pat on the back as he turned to hear the ghost of Ginny Weasley shriek as powerfully as her mother.

"How can you joke about domestic abuse? Battered women are-"

"I'm not talking about women," Sirius interrupted the ghost. "I'm talking about men."

"Well the men probably deserved it," Bellatrix argued, belatedly noticing Remus and Tonks were also paying attention. She was dipping a large pickle into a jar of peanut butter and snapping off progressively louder bites. "I know most women do."

Tonks glanced at her father before asking Bellatrix, "You really don't know how normal people live, do you?"

Bellatrix dunked another pickle and looked to Harry and Sirius for help. "Most people don't deserve to be abused? Really?"

The two Lupins, two Lord Blacks, and ghost all looked at the woman pitifully.

"Huh," Bellatrix considered while stirring up her peanut butter. "That doesn't sound right at all."

"Anyway," Ginny said trying to get back on topic. "What were we talking about?"

"How clueless Harry is when it comes to women," Bellatrix reminded.

"I'm not clueless," Harry argued. "I know the important stuff."

Sirius nodded. "I taught him the twenty-seven primary and secondary erogenous zones."

"Is it still twenty-seven?" Remus sought a definitive answer.

"I don't think the female body has evolved recently," Harry said doubtfully.

Sirius shrugged. "Yeah, well, my astronomy professor told me Pluto was a planet and I didn't think that would change either."

Tonks turned to her dad and explained, "I know how unlikely it is that stupid has suddenly become contagious, but I'm just not sure it's worth risking."

"Be nice," he scolded with a smile.

Harry jumped up and was patting down the various pockets of his cloak, before locating the warm buzzing Lookie Talkie. The image on the handheld mirror faded away revealing Jimmy's frantic face. "Harry! Thank Merlin you're there!"

"Jimmy? What's happened?"

"Hogwarts is in lockdown because there was some sort of attack, but I can't reach Dad who never takes his auror bracelet off and I heard them talking to Mum about Potters and Sarah was in Hogsmeade and then the Headmaster-"

"Whoa! Whoa," Harry said. "Take a breath. Are you under attack right now?"

Jimmy shook his head and calmly summarized. "I'm in my room. The floo system is down. Hogwarts is surrounded by a giant dome that even blocks the secret passages."

"When did you last hear from your Dad?"

"This morning. He had to go to Malfoy Manor."

"Shit." Harry succinctly replied. "We're coming."

"Get Sarah. She was in Hogsmeade when the dome went up," Jimmy urged before deactivating his mirror. "I think this attack may be targeted at us."

Harry clicked off his Lookie Talkie and saw everyone looking at him. "Shit."

All traces of annoyance gone, Tonks was focused and ready. "Ministry?"

"Go ahead," Harry said. "But be careful and plan to come back here."

Tonks apparating away snapped Remus out of his thoughtful daze. "This is your fault."

"Yeah, it is," Harry agreed. "And now we need to fix it. Sirius?"

"Just bloody perfect," Sirius exclaimed knowing what he had to do. "I'm going solo. I don't trust apparating more than him with me."

"I'll hit Hogsmeade and see if I can find a trail," Harry agreed. "Be careful."

Sirius popped up to his room to get his gear.

"Bellatrix," Harry said. "You are not to leave these wards unless in imminent danger."

Bellatrix nodded figuring as much.

Harry winced at the look Remus was giving him. "Your chocolate frog will probably be ringing off the hook as soon as you leave these wards. But you mind doing me a favor first?"

Remus nodded but had questions of his own. "Where'd Sirius go?"

"He's gearing up before going to Malfoy Manor."

"What?"

Harry glanced at Bellatrix. "Earmuffs?"

She obediently put the peanut butter covered pickle into her mouth and covered both of her ears with her hands.

Harry turned to Remus and explained, "Sirius is still keyed into the wards at Malfoy Manor. Odds are James is trapped in a hidden dungeon, and Sirius is going to break him out."

Remus didn't want to blame Harry and Sirius for this but was failing to find reasons not to. "What makes you so sure he's still alive?"

Harry took a deep breath and saw Bellatrix was still keeping her ears covered. "Because Voldemort's planning on bidding with the lives of Potters." Harry closed his eyes as he let his magical arms out, flailing them around to taste and sense the air.

"What favor did you need?" Remus asked as he felt Harry's magic emanating around him and knew he was about to leave.

"Floo, owl, visit, or somehow check on Lord Peter Potter," Harry said calmly with his eyes shut. "Maybe get him and any other Potters to Hogwarts, if they want. Something."

"I'll check on him," Remus assured Harry.

"Thank you." Harry's eyes snapped opened. "Be careful."

With a soft pop, Harry reappeared at the primary apparition point in Hogsmeade. He waited a second ensuring Ginny's ghostly form hadn't stayed visible. Witches were herding young children out of the streets and people were taking cover, peering out storefront doors and windows.

Harry spotted smoke in the distance and attempted to apparate down the lane. He flickered right back into place and felt the echoing thump of anti-apparition wards in his head. He quickly broke into a run towards the fire.

Ducking under a spell, Harry slid to a stop and turned towards the caster. Another spell crashed right into a magical shield as he raised it. He located a lone Death Eater hiding in the shadows and began a brisk walk up to the man. "Not under orders to leave me alone?"

"Avada Kedavra!" the masked man shouted.

Harry whipped a small rock right up into the path of the killing curse as two other magical arms grabbed the Death Eater and bodily yanked him into the street.

He was fighting against the forces suspending him in air and nearly had his wand aimed at Harry. "Sapi-"

"Stop that." Harry calmly twisted the man's wrist and effortlessly ripped the wand from his hand. The wand floated into one of Harry's pockets as he held the man up. "Where is she?"

The man was struggling in Harry's arms, and whipping his head side to side to avoid Harry's gaze.

Both of the Death Eater's arms snapped, broken at the elbow, and he screamed in pain. Harry again asked, "Where is she?"

The man stopped shrieking but was still fighting Harry's grip. "You're too late. By now she-"

A massive explosion blew out the front door of Madam Puddifoot's and several shouts of distress could be heard.

Harry stunned the Death Eater before he could say anything else. From what the Death Eater was saying and the sound of fighting, Harry deduced Sarah was still in Hogsmeade, which meant keeping her here became priority. He knew altering the current portkey and apparition wards would take too long, so he quickly cast some of his own and tied them into an anchor stone he'd driven into the ground. He stunned the Death Eater once more and hid the anchor under his unconscious body.

Two more Death Eaters came out of Madam Puddifoot's and Harry charged straight for them. Neither got a shield up in time, but the one on the left managed to yell, "It's Black!" before his head hit the wall knocking him out cold.

"Go get him!" was shouted from the back of the tea shop just before a stream of better than a dozen Death Eaters came flowing to the front. Shields were up and the curses began to rain down.

Harry let an unconscious Death Eater serve as his human shield, taking the brunt of the curses headed his direction. He was about charge headfirst into the fray when his ears caught the sounds of fighting coming from the back.

"Help!"

Harry decided a change in tactics was needed once he knew she was okay and roughly her location. He launched the mangled corpse towards the largest pack of Death Eaters and ran out the front door.

Four more Death Eaters were waiting in the street and began firing uncoordinatedly. Harry returned their curses with several of his own, putting them on the defensive and knocking out one.

An invisible arm yanked the wrist of a Death Eater sending his curse directly into the face of his comrade. Another invisible arm grabbed the unconscious Death Eater by the ankle and dragged him behind Harry, as he circled around to the back of the building.

The rear door was charmed to not open, but four simultaneous well-placed punches proved the same could not be said for the door's frame.

Harry again let an unconscious floating Death Eater lead his way. Spells tore apart the robed shield, giving away the attackers' locations. Harry deftly knocked out the two Death Eaters in the back room and pocketed their wands too.

"Help!" Sarah shrieked from the next room.

Harry dropped the smoldering body and barreled his way through the side door. Two stunners took out the Death Eaters furthest from him, while a massive man had a handful of Sarah Potter's hair. She was unsuccessfully struggling to free herself.

The near giant whipped his head around faster than should be possible for a man his size. "You!"

Harry's eyes quickly determined there were no other immediate threats and he answered, "Me." A sharp crack erupted as the Death Eater's head spun around to face the other way. His body went limp and he fell forward with a loud thump.

Sarah scrambled away from the ogre's body to retrieve her wand. She looked warily at his eyes, frozen open behind the Death Eater mask. "You killed him?"

Harry was feeling slightly exhausted already and saw an opportunity. "Don't move," Harry instructed as he positioned himself right next to her. Four anchor stones floated in the air chest high, making a perfect square.

Harry held his wand perpendicular to the floor in the exact center of the square just as Death Eaters appeared at both doors. "Fidelio!"

Magic erupted into a flat plane rushing into the stones and sending magical walls growing until they met the floor and the ceiling.

All the Death Eaters that had been watching what was happening cried out in pain and clenched their eyes shut.

Sarah saw Harry relax and hunch forward, resting his hands on his knees as he caught his breath. She saw more and more Death Eaters come into the room, none of which seemed capable of locating them. She saw the magic slowly flowing up and down from the four stones, flickering intermittently between solid and a hazy opaque veil. "What is this?"

"Don't touch it, please," Harry warned when he saw Sarah was mesmerized by the look of the magic on this side. He stood up and pulled out a pair of pepper-up potions. He swallowed one dose and held out the other to her. "Pepper-up?"

Sarah accepted the potion gratefully, realizing she could take a moment to heal her ankle and numb some of her bruises.

Harry smiled as steam trickled out his ears. "This is a spell I made. Well, a friend of mine helped me but mostly I made it. I call it a Fidelius cage."

"How's it work?" Sarah asked as she trailed her wand over a cut on Harry's cheek.

Harry appreciated the quick heal and smiled at her intellectual curiosity. "It's sort of an unfinished Fidelius charm, without a secret let alone a keeper."

Sarah was impressed. "From what little I know that shouldn't be possible."

"Technically, this Fidelius only covers the thin layer of magic and not the space in between. That's why I was able to eliminate the secret keeping aspects. The spell inevitably fails because there's no capping the anchors. But as long as I keep feeding it a little magic, it keeps trying to complete the charm, protecting us in a place that can only be accessed from below and above."

She was watching the magic flowing out of view into the floor and ceiling. "How long can you keep it up?" Sarah blushed when Harry bit back a snort. "The spell, you pervert."

Harry saw the majority of the Death Eaters were still in the room, trying to locate them. "Not indefinitely, so how about we put off the rest of this discussion until later and get ready to bust our way out of here?"

"Right," Sarah agreed, before paling at the sheer number of Death Eaters currently in the room. "I don't suppose you can move the cage with us?"

Harry shook his head. "Sorry. A mobile Fidelius is still beyond me. But I have ideas on how to anchor one to the moon instead of the Earth."

"Could that help us here?"

"No."

"Then let's table that discussion too," Sarah urged, noticing more men coming back into the room. "You think we're going to get out of here?"

Harry saw there had to be two dozen men crammed in the small room and immediately beyond the doors. Harry grinned dangerously. "There's no doubt in my mind we're getting out of here. I'm just not sure how many of them will." Harry noticed Sarah frowning. "You know what they were going to do to you, right?"

Sarah swallowed to hide the lump in her throat. "I have a fair idea."

"Good. Because I'm feeling violent."

Sarah knew that feeling well, experiencing it at least once a month. "I just want to get out of here."

Harry nodded towards the door he'd burst through. "That way's shorter, but they've probably got a welcoming party waiting around the corner. I say we go through the front and if we happen to destroy a fair amount of this god forsaken place, then so be it."

Sarah thought Harry looked a little too eager. "It's a tea shop."

"It's a tool of dark witches," Harry argued.

"Discussion? Later?" Sarah reminded pointing towards the Death Eaters who appeared to be attempting group scrying in a more coordinated manner.

"Right," Harry agreed. "Okay, you? Stay behind me and stay out of my way."

"I can help," Sarah argued.

"You want to help?" Harry said taking a deep breath and getting back into the right mindset. "Stun anyone moaning in pain. The whiners really grate on my nerves. Ready?"

Sarah nodded and Harry turned his back to her. He prepared two magical arms while four others gently gripped the cage's anchor stones. "Stay close. And don't fight me when I push and pull you around."

Sirius apparated into the ward room at Malfoy Manor. He chose there because it was the place he knew best that was not currently a raging inferno. He called for Kreacher and stunned the elf immediately.

He tightened his outer chameleon cloak and disillusioned himself. He'd taken barely three steps, when he heard voices approaching. Sirius just held his breath and didn't move from the wall. He kept a shield on the tip of his tongue as two masked Death Eaters scurried by wondering, "Why the hell would they need reinforcements to grab the girl?"

Sirius silently thanked his godson and crept down the hall. He was fortunate that he and Harry had dissected the entire manor layout, so he knew where the secret passage to the dungeon was.

He snuck a glance into the drawing room spewing fire out the roof and couldn't stop grinning. The room was luckily empty as Sirius scampered across the hall into a living room with a six meter high mirror. Sirius shook his head at how fitting that was and hurried over to the grandfather clock.

Sirius pulled out his omnioculars and swore at the volume of wards covering the secret entrance behind the clock. There was no way he could get through that door without drawing a ton of notice even if he did have the Dark Mark. He twisted a couple of knobs on the omnioculars and grinned in delight at the obvious oversight.

After double-checking there was no one in the hallway headed this way, Sirius ran over to the wall just to the side of the door and pushed an illusory pin into the ground. He cast the spell storing the current appearance as the illusion he wanted before deactivating the pin. Silencing spells were rotated with blasting curses until Sirius had made his own secret tunnel.

Sirius crawled into his new hole and reactivated the illusory pin behind him. He carefully finished his tunnel ending on the fifth step from the top. After ensuring the coast was clear, Sirius vanished the debris. He pushed a second illusory pin into the ground ten steps further down. After storing the image, Sirius deactivated the pin and moved to right in front of his new wand-crafted hole. Reactivating the pin, the hole disappeared and the wall looked similar but not flawless.

Sirius knew it'd have to do, as he cleaned the dust from his disillusioned form and took the long curving flight of stairs two at a time. He slowed down as he heard a voice in the distance.

A scream of pain alerted Sirius to the fact that this wasn't a friendly chat.

"You liked that, didn't you?" Lucius Malfoy grinned in sadistic glee. "They say that one feels like rusty knives cutting across your body. Is it true? Is that what it felt like?"

Sirius didn't notice any other Death Eaters, but kept his wand ready in his wrist holster. He quietly grabbed a shovel as he snuck up to Lucius and swung it with all his might.

Lucius turned just in time to catch the shovel with his face. The blonde's nose was smashed flat and he was unconscious before he hit the floor.

"They say that one feels like a shovel to the face," Sirius said tossing the shovel onto the ground.

"Nngh!" was the extent of the warning James Potter could shout in his condition.

Sirius was ready and dove out of the way of a purple hex and sent back two of his own. The Death Eater that had been in the room, rushed forward and took cover right next to the door frame.

Sirius didn't even hesitate as he sent a blasting curse into the wall by the door. The stone exploded the Death Eater into the open and covered him in rubble as Sirius nailed him in the face with a vicious stunner.

"Anybody else?" Sirius asked, eyeing the blind corner warily.

"Nnh," James replied.

Sirius canceled the disillusionment on his cloak as he took in the full sight of the Assistant Director of the DMLE. James Potter was hurt pretty bad, hanging by his wrists, exposing his bruised and bloodied abdomen. He had a cut by his neck, and one eye swollen shut. Sirius sent a cutting curse at the chains and James fell to the floor.

"Oww," he groaned at the sudden jolt on his injuries.

"Sorry," Sirius said, not really sounding like it. He helped James remove the shackles and steadied the man as he struggled to his feet. James took a few tentative steps on his own while Sirius stunned the Death Eater again. "Damn. Broke his wand."

"I'll use Malfoy's," James said as made his way over to the unconscious man. He accidentally kicked Lucius in the balls eight times as he stood up with the man's wand. He numbed most of his bruises and applied a little basic field healing. He attempted to stun Malfoy only to get the spell reflected back. "Shit," James swore as he ducked.

"Try the shovel," Sirius cheerfully suggested.

James looked at the wand uncertainly. "You think he jinxed his wand?"

"Maybe," Sirius admitted, "But you did heal yourself. And I do know that Lord Malfoy, in Malfoy Manor, wearing the Malfoy ring, has some protection from direct magic."

James looked over at Sirius and stared for a moment. "It really is you, isn't it?"

"A thank you wouldn't be out of place," Sirius grumbled.

James took a couple of slow steps forward and offered his hand.

Sirius thought it was kind of a goofy feminine gesture but shook hands. "Sirius Black."

"Thank you, Sirius Black," James said earnestly. "Now, how long until backup arrives? Are we waiting on a signal or something?"

Sirius forced a weak smile. "No signal, no backup. Just me. And we need to hurry before they notice us."

"Just… you?" James clarified.

Sirius frowned. "I'm not really feeling the love here."

James was confused. "Why are you doing this?"

Sirius huffed. "Lily promised herself to me. Now can we go?"

"This is not the time for your jokes."

"This is the perfect time for my jokes!"

Lucius groaned in discomfort as he slowly regained consciousness. "What… what happened?"

Sirius had already picked up the shovel and swung it like a cricket bat, whomping Malfoy back into unconsciousness. "Did you see that?"

James nodded, noticing a lump forming on the top of Malfoy's head.

"Excellent time for a joke, wouldn't you say?" Sirius scratched his chin. "Something like 'Heads up!' or 'Mal-Fore!' if you're uninspired. I, myself, lean towards the 'You forgot to duck, bitch' camp."

"Mosquito," James deadpanned.

"Good one," Sirius encouraged. "I knew you had it in you. Now we really should get out of here."

James frowned looking down on Lucius. "Can we take him with us? He's just going to disappear off the grid until he can buy his freedom again."

Sirius shook his head. "I can only side-along one. That's why you get a rescue team of one."

"And I doubt I can transfigure him because of that damned ring."

"That's right," Sirius remembered. "I forgot how good you are at transfiguration. I need a Norton's Brew and a willing subject to pull off human to inanimate. I suppose you could kill him."

James seemed to be heavily considering the option.

"Hang on," Sirius said. "We just need to get that ring off."

"It'll probably poison us if we try to remove it," James argued.

"I'm just saying you could kill him," Sirius reminded James of option one with a hopeful grin. "Or we could remove his finger."

James shook his head. "Any cutting curse will bounce right off."

Sirius jerked his thumb over his shoulder. "Have you not seen how effective that shovel is?"

James looked over at the shovel and then Malfoy and then the shovel again. He figured they could delve into the ethics of apprehension by amputation once the blonde Death Eater was locked in a high-security cell. "A skilled healer could easily reattach the finger…"

"Unless we were to lose it," Sirius suggested. "It'd be a shame to get splinched because we had to carry an extra finger."

James twitched in amusement. "Okay, let's do this."

Sirius used a gloved hand to roll up all of Malfoy's non-ring fingers, while James got the shovel and positioned it right at the knuckle. Sirius took a step back but couldn't tear his eyes from the sight.

James took a deep breath and jammed the shovel down forcefully. There was an audible click sound and the singular severed digit popped about a meter up into the air before clattering on the floor.

Lucius woke up suddenly screaming in pain.

Sirius immediately cast a silencing charm on the hurting Lord Malfoy and cheered at the success of the spell.

James saw Lucius was going to try and crawl away. He took two steps towards him and swatted him viciously on the ear with the shovel.

Lucius buckled back to the ground unconscious again.

"Uh, James?" Sirius pointed out. "You could've just stunned him now."

"I know," James agreed. "But I didn't want to let you have all the fun."

Sirius guffawed at the unexpected response. "You severed his finger. I doubt I got all the fun."

James was looking away, hiding his smile. He wrapped the unattached ring finger in a piece of cloth and stuffed it into Malfoy's pocket. With a grunt of forcing the magic through an unfamiliar wand, James transfigured the unconscious Death Eater into a plain red coin. He slid the coin into his pocket and nodded at Sirius.

Sirius had taken off his chameleon cloak and was offering it to James.

"Thanks," James said accepting the cloak, unused to this kinder, gentler Lord Black.

"We need to stay hidden if we can," Sirius explained as he tapped his head and the disillusionment charm trickled down him and his dragon-hide robes. "You stink a lot more than me, so you need the cloak."

James activated the disillusionment charm on the cloak and took the lead.

"Hang on," Sirius whispered harshly. "You don't know where we're going, so you follow me."

"There's only one direction," James pointed out, not yet ready to defer to Sirius' judgment.

"And if you even touched that door up there, you'd get blasted into the wall."

"Correct me if I'm wrong, but I'm the auror here, right?" James argued as the pair had been walking up the steps side by side.

"You're the damaged victim who's been tortured for the past few hours," Sirius scolded trying to stay in the lead. "Don't overexert yourself."

"Shh!" James snapped as he stopped suddenly. "Do you hear that?"

Sirius paused and listened closer. "Someone's coming! There's a room just ahead. Quick!"

James tried to run as softly as he could, cursing the sounds of his feet, and wishing he had charmed silent boots like Sirius.

Sirius yanked James off the side, and pulled them both into a musty old cupboard. They cast silencing charms at the same time and shushed each other. They heard the footsteps getting louder when a voice spoke up.

"He was already screaming when I saw him this morning, my Lord. He's probably broken by now."

"Do not underestimate the Potters," a powerful voice hissed.

James and Sirius stared at each other in shock suddenly realizing the Dark Lord Voldemort could catch them hiding in a broom closet.

James' eyes hardened and he pulled his wand arm up. "It's him."

Sirius grabbed onto James' hand and held him back. "Yes, it's him."

"We can kill him now," James snarled looking to Sirius for help.

"Are you fucking insane?" Sirius whispered angrily. "We cannot kill him now. Trust me. All we could do is piss him off. And you need medical attention already."

"He killed my son!" James snapped loudly, pushing the two silencing charms to their limits. He deflated into a broken man as he softly added, "And he killed my best friend."

Sirius felt more twisted inside than he had since Azkaban. Hearing a James Potter echoing the same pain he'd gone through was just confusing. "There's nothing we can do. Not right now."

"You fought him," James argued petulantly. "What are you so worried about?"

"I didn't fight him," Sirius corrected. "Harry fought him. I don't care if you're Albus fucking Dumbledore, I'm not going head to head with Voldemort unless Harry's got my back."

"You're the one always acting so superior-"

"That's the point," Sirius interrupted. "Acting. Pureblood politics bollocks is mainly about who can cheat the most in a dick-measuring contest."

James had a flash of his Hogwarts days and another Sirius Black making an eerily similar statement. "Are you scared of him?"

"I'm not scared," Sirius retorted as he slowly opened the creaky cupboard door. "I just have a healthy amount of respect for his ability to squash people like me."

James couldn't help it. He snorted and started to laugh.

Sirius whipped around and shushed him. "We don't have time for this."

James wondered aloud, "When did you start acting responsibly?"

Sirius scowled and retorted softly, "Probably about the time your sense of humor came back from sabbatical."

James smiled at the barb and urged Sirius forward. "Come on."

An ear-piercing shriek echoed from down the bottom of the steps.

"Run!" Sirius instructed and he began to sprint up the steps as fast as he could. A Death Eater was blasted in the face before he even realized he was under attack.

James cast a pair of exploding curses on the stairs behind them, making it more difficult to follow.

"Don't use the door!" Sirius shouted as he saw they were nearly at the top. "Follow me."

Sirius fell to his knees and finally located the illusory pin, deactivating it with a touch of his wand. Sirius stuffed the pin in his pocket, canceled his disillusionment charm, and crawled through his homemade tunnel. He stopped and made sure James was right behind him. "As soon as we get out from under these Dark Mark targeted wards, I can apparate us."

James nodded, knowing this was a time to follow, not lead.

Sirius deactivated the last pin and crawled out of the hole. He shoved it in his pocket as he stood up and discovered he was in a room with more than two dozen masked Death Eaters staring his way. Thinking quickly, Sirius said, "What do you guys think of my disguise?"

When it appeared they weren't going to curse him immediately, he added, "Aren't I just the spitting image of the good looking Lord Black?"

"Naw, you look like the tall one," a Death Eater pointed out. "The good looking one has those hypnotic eyes."

A few other Death Eaters turned towards the vocal member curiously. "Smith? Is there something you'd like to tell us?"

Right then, a clearly bruised and dust covered disillusioned James Potter stood up behind Sirius, unable to see past him.

"Get him!" three men shouted as they all started cursing.

Sirius had already grabbed James by the arm and apparated them away before the first spell arrived.

Sarah considered herself a fair witch. Both of her parents were above average in power, and while it's true her little brother started beating her regularly in duels last year, she knew she was far from a helpless-with-a-wand, trophy witch. When the first two Death Eaters approached she managed to stun them both and run away. She'd cursed several others, leading them on a frantic chase before a table got blasted into her ankle and she was boxed in.

She admitted to feeling hopeless as they activated their portkeys only to have her prayers answered as the portkeys remained inert. She sprung into action in their confusion and took great pleasure kneeing one of them in the crotch. She'd made her way further into the back, shouting for help again after losing her wand for the second time. These were the actions of a fairly competent witch, she assured herself.

Even still, getting yanked around like a rag doll by Harry could give anyone inadequacy issues.

She had flinched when the two nearest Death Eaters slammed into the wall with a loud crunch. She barely noticed the beauty of the Fidelius cage crumbling, as the sound of two more necks breaking echoed around the room. She felt the tension in the room thicken as dozens of curses flew straight towards them.

She knew she'd be too late in getting a shield up, but she needn't have bothered as the body of a Death Eater was thrust into the path of the spells. A sudden mist of blood coated the right side of her face and she felt things were getting too close for comfort. A glance at Harry showed him completely unaffected and what she would've sworn was a smile flitted across his face.

She began to think Harry might be crazy, but was forced to admit he was commanding magic on a level she'd never match.

"I beat your Master in open air," Harry snarled, playing up their fear of him. "You really expect to take me in close quarters?"

Sarah was about to suggest less taunting when she felt something like an invisible snake wrapping around her midsection. She barely realized what was happening when she was thrust up to the ceiling. Her arms were mashed against Harry's back as they zipped from one corner of the room to the next, essentially ignoring gravity's protestations.

Bones were breaking, curses were flying, chunks of the wall and floor exploded sending dust and shrapnel everywhere. Sarah's eyes could barely keep up with carnage raining down when she and Harry landed on their feet at the door.

Harry began to stalk down the hallway, enjoying every step as the Death Eaters kept backing up, frightened of getting too close.

Sarah saw the destruction left in their wake. Blood was everywhere. The other door was hidden behind a pile of bodies and wreckage. There weren't even any patches of wall that had made it through unscathed. She remembered Harry's suggestion when she recognized how many were groaning in pain, and shrieking about misplaced body parts. She fumbled with her wand to stun them when she was again jerked to the side and a searing orange spell whizzed past her collapsing the back wall.

Sarah began to worry as she had lost her wand, and Harry appeared fully focused on the Death Eaters in front of them. Her wand came floating out from under a piece of the collapsed ceiling and it just hovered there waiting for her to grab it. That small gesture proved to her just how in control of the situation Harry was. She quickly drew on his presence and nearness as a source of comfort.

Sarah proceeded to stun all the still breathing Death Eaters, while keeping her other hand on Harry's back.

She saw Harry down another pepper-up potion while the Death Eaters just watched them fearfully from the other end of the hallway.

"You okay?" Harry asked softly out the corner of his mouth.

"Yeah," she said as she moved closer to him, pressing her body up to his back. "Let's get out of here, please."

"Sounds good to me," Harry said, wrapping an invisible arm around Sarah and magically tethering her to his back.

She caught on to what Harry wanted and wrapped her arms around his stomach. She felt Harry rock back on to his heels before launching the pair of them like a torpedo down the hall.

Drywall, plaster, chunks of stone and wood were exploding from the floor and walls. A shield in front of them deflected the only spells that came their way. Death Eaters were crushed and crumpled as Harry and Sarah span through the air with the force of a locomotive.

The half dozen or so remaining Death Eaters who could still manage it were sprinting through Madam Puddifoot's dining area and out the front door.

"Go on! Run away you pussies!" Harry shouted happily as he and Sarah flipped up and back to their feet. Harry grinned as he saw Death Eaters hustling down the street. "I think seeing them run away may be even better than beating them up."

Sarah started to relax as she picked pieces of debris from her hair. She saw the flicker of a disillusionment charm a second too late. "Harry!"

"Avada Kedavra!" Two separate voices shouted from opposite sides of the dining room.

A pair of magical arms yanked Sarah down and out of the path of a killing curse just as Harry turned in time to see the other sickly green spell line up with his heart.

Sarah gasped when she saw the two spells had sandwiched Harry in and he was unable to dodge. She could only gape in disbelief as the moment they were about to connect, Harry's body faded out of view into a ghostly incorporeal form. The curses zipped harmlessly through his body leaving only faint trails of smoke as they passed.

The two Death Eaters' faces froze permanently in shock as the errant spells slammed into each others' unprotected and disillusioned bodies.

Harry had never been more thankful for his animagus form than at that moment, and he gave the room a belated but thorough evaluation. Satisfied with his search, Harry closed his eyes and forcefully willed his body back into solid form. A gentle pop told him he'd succeeded for the first time and he opened his eyes.

He offered a hand to help a wide-eyed Sarah up. "I'd appreciate it if you didn't mention that last part to anyone."

She looked over at the two lifeless bodies and then Harry incredulously. "Okay."

Harry walked with Sarah out the front door just as the roof caved in destroying the last of the dining area. "Oops," Harry said with a little too much glee. "You okay?"

Sarah just nodded mutely, staying close to Harry. The two of them were leaning on each other for support.

Harry chuckled as they walked by a pair of aurors fighting to put out a magical fire. He could feel the adrenaline leaving his body as the danger had passed. "They were disillusioned and fired killing curses directly across from each other. Not the brightest bulbs in the bunch."

"That was pretty stupid," Sarah agreed as she let Harry lead them over to the next building.

He retrieved his anchor stone and canceled the portkey and apparition wards. He spotted Tonks running towards them and apparently his body decided that was its signal to shut down.

"Sarah!" Tonks shouted hugging the young woman she used to babysit. "You're okay?"

"I'm fine," Sarah said trying to ignore the unknown wet purple pieces of Death Eater in her hair. "Harry came and…" She trailed off when she noticed Harry was laying face first on the ground. "Harry!"

She hurriedly checked him over and concluded he was healthy enough just severely exhausted, a common reaction to multiple doses of pepper-up.

"The headmaster is about to bring down the wards," Tonks informed. "Think you get Sleeping Booty to the hospital wing?"

Sarah nodded. "Yeah, but you might want to secure the Death Eaters back there."

"How many'd you two get?" Tonks asked with a grin.

Sarah shrugged. "Not really sure. Maybe thirty?"

"That's a lot of paperwork," Tonks gulped before spotting a junior auror. "Hey Perkins! Go secure the Death Eaters in Madam Puddifoot's! I'm escorting these two to Hogwarts."

Sarah chuckled at Tonks' look of innocence. "Escorting us, eh?"

Tonks waved her wand and began to levitate the snoring Lord Black. "You know sleepyhead back there was trying to convince me he understood women? Please. If it weren't for you, I doubt he'd ever have gotten out of there alive."

"Tell me about it," Sarah agreed walking in step with Tonks. "I must have stunned at least a dozen of them."

It only took one sniff for Harry to determine where he was. The cushioned bed, the starched sheets, the oppressive sense of being smothered, and the smell all told him one thing: he was in the Hogwarts hospital wing.

A pounding headache reminded him that he'd exhausted himself, so he asked, "Hello?"

"I'm here, Harry," Sirius' voice soothed as he watched Harry crack open his eyes.

"I've got a potion for you, Lord Black," Madame Pomfrey's less than warm voice stated.

Harry accepted the sludge and realized this woman didn't know him at all. He quickly knocked it back, grimacing at the texture more than the taste. He accepted the glass of water and tried to wash the taste from his mouth. "What happened when I was out? Why did I need to come here?"

"You exhausted nearly all of your magical reserves," Poppy Pomfrey chided.

"So?" Harry asked blinking in the brightness of the room. "I do that all the time. And do you have anything for my headache?"

Poppy harrumphed. "Pepper-up potions are not candy, Lord Black. There's a reason you are supposed to wait six hours before even considering taking a second one."

"Can't you do something for my headache before you lecture me?" Harry pleaded. "If you want any of your words to get through, it'll have to be after this throbbing goes away."

"You earned that headache and you're going to keep it or you'll never learn," Poppy scolded as she retreated back towards her office.

"Thanks for pissing off my boss, Harry," Sarah humorlessly cheered from the other side.

Harry slowly began to look around the room and became aware everyone was staring at him. Jimmy was smiling, sitting on the edge of a bed next to Sirius. Tonks was grinning at him, as was Lord Peter Potter and Albus Dumbledore. On Harry's other side Sarah stood, while James Potter lay in the bed behind. Lily Potter was clutching her husband's hand tightly, but looked like a coil waiting to spring a hug on Harry.

She lunged forward and squeezed him, profusely thanking and praising him for saving her little girl.

Harry was still feeling more than a little out of it as he hugged her back.

"Lily, let the poor man breath," James chided as he sat up. "Thank you, Lord Black. If ever you need anything-"

Peter took the opportunity to interrupt. "Yes, Lord Black and Lord Black? The House of Potter is indebted to both of you individually and to the House of Black-"

"Stop, stop," Harry jumped in. "Really. It was nothing. All I want is a little quiet and for this damn headache to go away."

"POTTER!" the deafening shout came from down the hall.

Harry clenched his eyes shut and was rubbing his temples at the sound of Severus Snape bursting into the hospital wing.

"I know it was you, Potter!" Severus shrieked over the sudden loss of his hair. "You're even more arrogant than your father! Repeating the same immature, childish pranks—Are you even listening? I'm talking to you, Potter!"

Jimmy just paled, trying not to laugh at the shine on the top of his Potions Professor's head.

"Yes, I'm fucking listening, Snivellus," Harry spat out. "That snot-filled wheezing you call breathing is like acid to my ears." Harry pinched the bridge of his nose as the throbbing seemed to increase. He slowly caught on to the oppressive silence hanging in the air and looked up.

"Uh, Harry?" Jimmy warily interjected. "I think he was talking to me."

Harry saw varying degrees of confusion and shock staring back at him, aside from Albus and Sirius who were both twittering in barely restrained amusement. "Oh… bugger."